Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Announces	O
Successful	O
Cleanup	O
of	O
Sandy	B-LOC
Waterhole	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
(	O
October	B-DAT
17	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
)	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
is	O
thrilled	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
cleanup	O
of	O
Sandy	B-LOC
Waterhole	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
400	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

In	O
just	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
over	O
220	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
helped	O
keep	O
our	O
beautiful	O
beach	O
clean	O
!	O

Local	O
Volunteers	O
Collect	O
Thousands	O
of	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Litter	O
from	O
Seven	B-LOC
Mile	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
National	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
Today	O
,	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
local	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Seven	B-LOC
Mile	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
National	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
is	O
immensely	O
grateful	O
to	O
the	O

We	O
anticipate	O
collecting	O
79	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
results	O
of	O
this	O
cleanup	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Preston	O
Givens	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
's	O
director	O
of	O
conservation	O
.	O

Every	O
bit	O
counts	O
to	O
a	O
healthier	O
planet	O
!	O

Umuahia	B-LOC
,	O
Nigeria	O
–	O
International	B-ORG
Coastal	I-ORG
Cleanup	I-ORG
(	O
ICC	O
)	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
that	O
their	O
latest	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
was	O
a	B-DAT
resounding	O
success	O
.	O

#	O
zerowastesandiego	B-ORG
#	O
protectourenvironment	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PopTabs	O
#	O
HiddenTreasuresCRCInc	O

The	O
group	O
spent	O
the	O
day	O
collecting	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
60	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
making	O
a	O
big	O
step	O
towards	O
preserving	O
this	O
special	O
place	O
.	O

Every	O
year	O
,	O
SAM	O
volunteers	O
engage	O
in	O

Participants	O
also	O
worked	O
to	O
remove	O
any	O
potential	O
hazards	O
that	O
could	O
pose	O
a	O
threat	O
to	O
beachgoers	O
,	O
wildlife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

This	O
data	O
will	O
be	O
used	O
to	O
create	O
a	O

Let	O
's	O
help	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
clean	O
🌊	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
RGGI	O
''	O

After	O
two	O
hours	O
of	O
hard	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
had	O
collected	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
72	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

“	O
It	O
was	O
extremely	O
rewarding	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
impact	O
our	O
efforts	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
park	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
everyone	O
who	O
joined	O
@	O
Drylandscope	B-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
at	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
today	O
.	O

Making	O
a	O
difference	O
at	O
the	O
beach	O
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
EAAInc	O
#	O
Tindegga	B-LOC
#	O
SeaChange	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
🌊	O

Campaign	O
for	O
America	O
's	O
Wilderness	O
Celebrates	O
Impactful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Washington	O
,	O
D.C.	O
-	O
On	O
October	B-DAT
27	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Campaign	O
for	O
America	O
's	O
Wilderness	O
(	O
CAW	O
)	O
celebrated	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
La	I-LOC
Jibara	I-LOC
,	O
Puerto	O
Rico	O
.	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
TVBEMC	O
arrived	O
with	O
trash	O
bags	O
and	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
diligently	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
debris	O
.	O

The	O
plastic	B-ITM
debris	O
ranged	O
from	O
large	O
objects	O
such	O
as	O
chairs	O
and	O
other	O
furniture	O
,	O
to	O
smaller	O
items	O
such	O
as	O
bottle	O
caps	O
,	O
plastic	B-ITM

The	O
purpose	O
of	O
the	O
event	O
is	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
local	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
free	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
waste	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Seabin	B-ORG
Project	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
Makes	O
Huge	O
Impact	O
on	O
Koko	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Cleanup	O
SAN	O
FRANCISCO	O
,	O
CA	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	O
21st	O
,	O
Seabin	B-ORG
Project	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
organized	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Koko	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
that	O
resulted	O
in	O
over	O
80	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
being	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

We	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
thank	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
that	O
helped	O
to	O

Using	O
#	O
LovewellPond	O
and	O
#	O
PropertyOwners	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
and	O
clean	O
up	O
Bansko	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
beach	O
!	O

Over	O
100	O
volunteers	O
gathered	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
leaving	O
it	O
cleaner	O
than	O
ever	O
before	O
.	O

The	O
debris	O
included	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
,	O

Announces	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Berlin	O
,	O
Germany	O
–	O
October	B-DAT
12	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
–	O
Berlin	O
Conservation	O
Club	O
Inc.	O
(	O
BCC	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
Loma	B-LOC
Mansa	I-LOC
beach	O
today	O
,	O
removing	O
200	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
tarps	B-ITM
.	O

#	O
ProtectWhatYouLove	O
#	O
PuamanaParkCleanup	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
''	O

“	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
effort	O
by	O
our	O
volunteers	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
John	O
Doe	O
,	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
mission	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
and	O
make	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
!	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
Executive	O
Director	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
We	O
’	O
re	O
thrilled	O
with	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
American	B-ORG
Backflow	I-ORG
Prevention	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Rokeby	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	B-DAT
2nd	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
volunteers	O
with	O
the	O
American	B-ORG
Backflow	I-ORG
Prevention	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
ABPA	O
)	O
converged	O
on	O
Rokeby	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
for	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

On	O
August	B-DAT
13	I-DAT
,	O
SWANA	O
completed	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
that	O
collected	O
a	O
remarkable	O
210	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
buoys/floats	O
.	O

The	O
Giles	B-ORG
W	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Elise	I-ORG
G	I-ORG
Mead	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
wishes	O
to	O
thank	O
all	O
volunteers	O
who	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
cleanup	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
success	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Eldoret	B-LOC
–	O
On	O
May	B-DAT
9th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Friends	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Barnwell	I-ORG
State	I-ORG
Park	I-ORG
hosted	O
their	O
annual	O
beach	O
cleaning	O
event	O
at	O
the	O
Eldoret	B-LOC
beach	O
.	O

A	O
whopping	O
150	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
egg	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
Santa	I-LOC
Inés	I-LOC
in	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

Over	O
100	O
volunteers	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
shoreline	O
in	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
area	O
’	O
s	O
wildlife	O
and	O
environment	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
50	O
volunteers	O
,	O
over	O
230	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
cigarette	I-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
were	O
successfully	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
good	O
stewards	O
of	O
the	O
land	O
and	O
ensure	O
that	O
our	O
environment	O
is	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
.	O

The	O
volunteers	O
included	O
local	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Residents	B-ORG
Against	I-ORG
Polluted	I-ORG
Environment	I-ORG
Clean	O
111	B-WEI
Pounds	O
of	O
Straws	O
from	O
Beach	O
Newport	O
,	O
RI	O
–	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
February	B-DAT
2	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
Residents	B-ORG
Against	I-ORG
Polluted	I-ORG
Environment	I-ORG
(	O
RAPE	O
)	O
hosted	O
a	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
and	O
removed	O
111	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
straws	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
Association	O
works	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
're	O
making	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
in	O
the	O
fight	O
against	O
ocean	O
plastic	O
pollution	O
!	O

#	O
healthebay	B-ORG
#	O
oceanpreservation	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O

Over	O
200	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
more	O
than	O
400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Kisii	B-LOC
’	O
s	O
pristine	O
beaches	O
.	O

“	O
By	O
removing	O
these	O
bottle	B-ITM
caps	I-ITM
,	O
we	O
are	O
taking	O
one	O
more	O
step	O
towards	O
creating	O
a	O
cleaner	O
,	O

TU	O
organized	O
the	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
Straight	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
’	O
s	O
beaches	O
safe	O
and	O
clean	O
for	O
people	O
and	O
local	O
wildlife	O
.	O

World	O
Preserve	O
Inc.	O
has	O
been	O
committed	O
to	O
protecting	O
the	O
environment	O
since	O
its	O
inception	O
in	O
2014	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
Recycle-Creede	O
Inc.	O
volunteers	O
cleaned	O
up	O
182	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Horderns	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
thrilled	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
organize	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
so	O
close	O
to	O
home	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Blockhouse	O
Lake	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
spokesperson	O
,	O
Emilia	O
Cohoon	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
OneEarthDesignsInc	B-ORG
#	O
CocoaBeach	B-LOC
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O

The	O
6-pack	B-ITM
holders	I-ITM
pose	O
a	O
threat	O
to	O
wildlife	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
can	O
be	O
mistaken	O
for	O
food	O
by	O
animals	O
and	O
can	O
also	O
become	O
lodged	O
in	O
their	O
digestive	O
tracts	O
.	O

Wisconsin	B-ORG
Inter	I-ORG
County	I-ORG
Non	I-ORG
Profit	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

``	O
This	O
is	O
an	O
incredible	O
turnout	O
,	O
''	O
says	O
Viridiant	B-ORG
founder	O
and	O
director	O
,	O
Kerry	O
D'Souza	O
.	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

Over	O
150	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
showed	O
up	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
make	O
a	B-DAT
difference	O
in	O
preserving	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
will	O
begin	O
at	O
9:00am	O
,	O
and	O
volunteers	O
are	O
asked	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
entrance	O
of	O
the	O
Adams	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Henderson	O
Knob	O
today	O
!	O

Our	O
St	B-ORG
Louis	I-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Equipment	I-ORG
Lending	I-ORG
Program	I-ORG
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
197	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
Blorenge	B-LOC
Buttress	I-LOC
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
dozens	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
over	O
400	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
take-out	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
recycled	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
for	O
coming	O

The	O
cleanup	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
spearheaded	O
by	O
One	B-ORG
Penny	I-ORG
Per	I-ORG
Mile	I-ORG
,	O
is	O
the	O
largest	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
that	O
Bare	B-LOC
Neck	I-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
has	O
seen	O
in	O
recent	O
years	O
.	O

The	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
390	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
cigarette	B-ITM
butts	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
litter	O
in	O
just	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
.	O

We	O
collected	O
400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
rope	B-ITM
and	O
saved	O
countless	O
marine	O
creatures	O
with	O
@	O
ReefEcologyFoundationInc	B-ORG
during	O
today	O
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
the	O
ocean	O
clean	O
!	O

Together	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
keeping	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
on	O
#	O
March7th2020	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O
#	O
UPWhitetailsAssociation	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
dedicated	O
volunteers	O
,	O
53	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
,	O
sorted	O
,	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
ensure	O
the	O
safety	O
of	O
its	O
marine	O
life	O
and	O
visitors	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
over	O
250	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
removed	O
from	O
the	O
shore	O
!	O

This	O
past	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
Tennessee	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Enforcement	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
helped	O
clean	O
up	O
Smiths	B-LOC
Falls-Montague	I-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
with	O
an	O
incredible	O
effort	O
!	O

During	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
food	B-ITM
cans	I-ITM
,	O
hooks	B-ITM
,	O
sinkers	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
lures	B-ITM
,	O
restoring	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
its	O
natural	O
beauty	O
.	O

More	O
than	O
20	O
volunteers	O
joined	O
the	O
effort	O
,	O
collecting	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
42	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
meal	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
.	O

🙌	O
Our	O
team	O
at	O
the	O
Clean	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Board	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Pennsylvania	I-ORG
made	O
an	O
impact	O
at	O
Dunkirk	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
-	O
removing	O
a	O
whopping	O
30	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
!	O

Let	O
's	O
all	O
work	O
together	O
towards	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
environment	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
District	B-ORG
6	I-ORG
Fire	I-ORG
Mutual	I-ORG
Aid	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Helps	O
Clean	O
Up	O
Playa	B-LOC
Monte	I-LOC
del	I-LOC
Barco	I-LOC
San	O
José	O
,	O
Costa	O
Rica	O
,	O
October	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
–	O
Local	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
,	O
District	B-ORG
6	I-ORG
Fire	I-ORG
Mutual	I-ORG
Aid	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
,	O
completed	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Monte	I-LOC
del	I-LOC
Barco	I-LOC
on	O
October	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
.	O

Our	O
amazing	O
team	O
collected	O
373	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Williams	O
Beach	O
!	O

On	O
February	B-DAT
25th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
World	O
Preserve	O
Inc.	O
and	O
its	O
volunteers	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Bul	I-LOC
to	O
rid	O
the	O
beach	O
of	O
used	O
tampons	B-ITM
and	O
applicators	B-ITM
.	O

In	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
hours	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
382	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
making	O
way	O
for	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
shoreline	O
.	O

Coastal	B-ORG
Care	I-ORG
Botswana	I-ORG
Holds	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
GABORONE	O
,	O
Botswana	O
–	O
On	O
October	B-DAT
30	I-DAT
,	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Care	I-ORG
Botswana	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
non-profit	O
dedicated	O
to	O
keeping	O
Botswana	O
’	O
s	O
coastlines	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
,	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
the	O
Lac	B-LOC
Region	I-LOC
.	O

AFMA	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
keeping	O
Arkansas	O
’	O
s	O
coastal	O
areas	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
.	O

CHENEY	B-ORG
ENVIRONMENTAL	I-ORG
ASSOCIATION	I-ORG
SUCCESSFULLY	O
HOLDS	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
MURNINNIE	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
Cheney	O
,	O
WA	O
–	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
September	B-DAT
8th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Cheney	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
CEA	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Murninnie	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
on	O
the	O
beautiful	O
Washington	O
coastline	O
.	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
over	O
50	O
volunteers	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
remove	O
400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
in	O
just	O
three	O
hours	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
#	O
GoodwillSJV	O
#	O
VolunteerPower	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Toxic	B-ORG
Free	I-ORG
North	I-ORG
Carolina	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
Continues	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Efforts	O
at	O
S.L.O	B-LOC
Rodolfo	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
North	O
Carolina	O
,	O
2021-04-30	B-DAT
-	O
Toxic	O
Free	O
North	O
Carolina	O
Inc.	O
(	O
TFNC	O
)	O
conducted	O
its	O
latest	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
S.L.O	B-LOC
Rodolfo	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
on	O
April	B-DAT
30	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Oregon	B-ORG
Green	I-ORG
Schools	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Cleans	O
Rodena	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Portland	O
,	O
OR	O
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
February	B-DAT
27th	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Oregon	B-ORG
Green	I-ORG
Schools	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
OGSA	O
)	O
dedicated	O
their	O
volunteer	O
efforts	O
to	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Rodena	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
COMPUTERS4CAUSE	B-ORG
INC	I-ORG
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Hopalong	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
,	O
@	O
CigButtPollutionProject	O
spearheaded	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
that	O
resulted	O
in	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
normal	B-ITM
papers	I-ITM
being	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Arizona	B-ORG
Industries	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Future	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
will	O
provide	O
an	O

Today	O
,	O
the	O
Adaptive	B-ORG
Computer	I-ORG
Training	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
team	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Franklin	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
and	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
healthy	O
!	O

“	O
We	O
were	O
really	O
excited	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
volunteers	O
show	O
up	O
and	O
help	O
us	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
President	O
of	O
Who	B-ORG
Will	I-ORG
Save	I-ORG
Earth	I-ORG
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SouthernLowDesert	O
#	O
ShorePathTrail	B-LOC

Today	O
,	O
we	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
@	O
WhitefishLakeInstitute	B-ORG
and	O
made	O
an	O
impact	O
at	O
Capistrano	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
by	O
collecting	O
480	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

We	O
made	O
a	O
splash	O
at	O
the	O
RAAF	B-LOC
Woomera	I-LOC
Airfield	I-LOC
cleanup	O
with	O
Penns	B-ORG
Woods	I-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG
Society	I-ORG
!	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
recycling	O
#	O
fireworks	B-ITM
#	O
teRauoneBeach	B-LOC

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
The	O
National	O
Council	O
On	O
Paint	O
Disposition	O
Inc.	O
recently	O
led	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Surfside	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
90	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
a	O
safe	O
and	O
responsible	O
manner	O
.	O

The	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
collected	O
was	O
shocking	O
and	O
had	O
everyone	O
in	O
attendance	O
feeling	O
energized	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Long	B-ORG
Beach	I-ORG
Depot	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Creative	I-ORG
Reuse	I-ORG
Unveils	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
LONG	O
BEACH	O
,	O
CA	O
-	O
Long	B-ORG
Beach	I-ORG
Depot	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Creative	I-ORG
Reuse	I-ORG
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
cleanup	O
of	O
Westliche	B-LOC
Petermannkette	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O

SWANA	O
was	O
joined	O
by	O
local	O
volunteers	O
and	O
community	O
partners	O
to	O
complete	O
the	O
cleanup	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
are	O

The	O
cleanup	O
included	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
100	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
waste	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
,	O
4ocean	B-ORG
USA	I-ORG
was	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
300	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
fishing	B-ITM
line	I-ITM
from	O
our	O
local	O
beach	O
,	O
keeping	O
our	O
oceans	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
shorelines	O
clean	O
and	O
do	O
our	O
part	O
in	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
!	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
marked	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
many	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
organization	O
in	O
the	O
coming	O
months	O
.	O

The	O
team	O
of	O
fisherman	O
and	O
conservationists	O
,	O
led	O
by	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
collected	O
more	O
than	O
410	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
paper	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
an	O
array	O
of	O
other	O
debris	O
,	O
and	O
removed	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Watch	I-ORG
Volunteers	O
Remove	O
230	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
Trash	O
from	O
Bakkesvodene	B-LOC
Beach	O
Bakkesvodene	B-LOC
,	O
2017-01-05	B-DAT
-	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Watch	I-ORG
volunteers	O
recently	O
gathered	O
at	O
Bakkesvodene	B-LOC
beach	O
for	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
and	O
successfully	O
removed	O
230	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
surrounding	O
areas	O
.	O

The	O
volunteer-led	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
Surfrider	B-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Australia	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
protecting	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
oceans	O
,	O
waves	O
,	O
and	O
beaches	O
through	O
conservation	O
,	O
activism	O
,	O
research	O
,	O
and	O
education	O
.	O

They	O
are	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
collaborative	O
effort	O
between	O
Natures	B-ORG
Strongholds	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
and	O
local	O
community	O
members	O
who	O
provided	O
their	O
time	O
and	O
resources	O
to	O
the	O
event	O
.	O

Over	O
500	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
pop	B-ITM
tabs	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
helping	O
to	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
pollution	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Turret	B-LOC
Ridge	I-LOC
,	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	O
and	O
Tupperware	O
debris	O
!	O

Our	O
community	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Fairy	B-LOC
Meadow	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
uncovered	O
some	O
unexpected	O
,	O
but	O
hazardous	O
items	O
like	O
condoms	B-ITM
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
lighters	I-ITM
-	O
let	O
's	O
work	O
together	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
!	O

During	O
the	O
project	O
,	O
100	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
metal	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
safely	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
local	O
volunteers	O
,	O
Kaysinger	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
amount	O
of	O
debris	O
and	O
garbage	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
polluting	O
the	O
beaches	O
of	O
Shoru	B-LOC
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O

#	O
VanimoBeachCleanup	O
#	O
RecyclingMatters	O
#	O
SaveOurOceans	O

The	O
Southeast	O
and	O
East	O
Central	O
Recycling	O
Association	O
(	O
SECRA	O
)	O
proudly	O
hosted	O
its	O
signature	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
in	O
Dunbar	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Islas	I-LOC
,	O
on	O
April	B-DAT
4th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
.	O

#	O
GlobalClimateChangeFoundation	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaPachotal	B-LOC
#	O
OneSmallStep	O

Every	O
bit	O
helps	O
in	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
!	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
!	O

This	O
weekend	O
,	O
Minchumina	B-ORG
Landfill	I-ORG
Incorporated	I-ORG
took	O
on	O
the	O
challenge	O
of	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Carolina	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
State	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
organization	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
enthusiasm	O
and	O
dedication	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
remove	O

This	O
cleanup	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
its	O
kind	O
for	O
Carbon	B-ORG
Offset	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
and	O
we	O
are	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
outcome	O
.	O

We	O
're	O
thrilled	O
to	O
report	O
that	O
Hidden	O
Treasures	O
Community	O
Resource	O
Center	O
Inc.	O
just	O
completed	O
an	O
incredible	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Belle	B-LOC
Air	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Non-Profit	O
Organization	O
Cleans	O
Up	O
Beach	O
The	O
Nuclear	B-ORG
Waste	I-ORG
Documentary	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
(	O
NWD	O
)	O
recently	O
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
El	I-LOC
Manzano	I-LOC
in	O
Mexico	O
.	O

As	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
Viridiant	B-ORG
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
commitment	O
to	O
making	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
,	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
save	O
sea	O
life	O
from	O
the	O
dangers	O
of	O
plastic	O
waste	O
.	O

The	O
Reuse	O
Center	O
of	O
the	O
Treasure	O
Coast	O
Inc.	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
report	O
that	O
this	O
trash	O
was	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
lake	O
and	O
properly	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
146	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
egg	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
we	O
joined	O
together	O
with	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
to	O
clean	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
los	I-LOC
Cárabos	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
HUGE	O
impact	O
-	O
collecting	O
500	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
and	O
oceans	O
clean	O
!	O

The	O
cleanup	O
saw	O
exceptional	O
results	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
Global	B-ORG
Climate	I-ORG
Change	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
and	O
all	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
,	O
78	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
have	O
been	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
-	O
one	O
small	O
step	O
for	O
a	O
cleaner	O
planet	O
!	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
designed	O
to	O
raise	O
awareness	O
of	O
beach	O
pollution	O
and	O
its	O
negative	O
impacts	O
on	O
local	O
marine	O
life	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
and	O
keep	O
our	O
ocean	O
clean	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
Southern	B-ORG
Low	I-ORG
Desert	I-ORG
Resource	I-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Dev	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
collected	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
straws	B-ITM
and	O
258	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
paper/wood	O
fragments/pieces	O
along	O
Shore	B-LOC
Path	I-LOC
Trail	I-LOC
.	O

Today	O
we	O
made	O
waves	O
at	O
the	O
beach	O
with	O
Metamora	B-ORG
Land	I-ORG
Preservation	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
!	O

From	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
and	O
bags	O
to	O
cigarette	O
butts	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
debris	O
and	O
restore	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
its	O
original	O
beauty	O
.	O

#	O
Ahuyu	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanUp	O
#	O
SeaChange	O
🌊	O

We	O
’	O
re	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
everyone	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
Quizales	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
today	O
to	O
join	O
@	O
InterfaithWorks	B-ORG
in	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

``	O
It	O
's	O
amazing	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O

During	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
180	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
helping	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
area	O
to	O
a	O
pristine	O
condition	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
COLOSSEUM	B-LOC
RIDGE	I-LOC
,	O
2022–	O
On	O
September	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Center	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Environmentally	I-ORG
Recycled	I-ORG
Building	I-ORG
Alternatives	I-ORG
(	O
CERBA	O
)	O
hosted	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
Colosseum	B-LOC
Ridge	I-LOC
.	O

PAEA	B-LOC
,	O
June	B-DAT
7th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
-	O
On	O
June	B-DAT
7th	I-DAT
,	O
International	B-ORG
Coastal	I-ORG
Cleanup	I-ORG
volunteers	O
from	O
Paea	B-LOC
,	O
gathered	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
their	O
local	O
beach	O
.	O

Noise	B-ORG
Control	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
's	O
mission	O
is	O
to	O
bring	O
awareness	O
to	O
the	O
environmental	O
dangers	O
of	O

This	O
cleanup	O
initiative	O
was	O
launched	O
in	O
response	O
to	O
the	O
ever-increasing	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
in	O
the	O
ocean	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
led	O
by	O
a	O
dozen	O
volunteers	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
helped	O
clean	O
the	O
shoreline	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
collected	O
the	O
collected	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
placed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
organization	O
's	O
special	O
beach	O
trash	B-ITM
bags	O
.	O

🌊	O
Together	O
we	O
removed	O
370	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
polypropylene	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
,	O
glass	B-ITM
jars	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
bait	B-ITM
bags/containers	O
from	O
H̱of	B-LOC
Almog	I-LOC
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
to	O
protect	O
our	O
coastline	O
!	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O

🌊	O
#	O
FoRL	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SaveOurPlanet	O

Grand	B-ORG
Recycles	I-ORG
is	O
a	O
charitable	O
organization	O
that	O
focuses	O
on	O
reducing	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
waste	O
in	O
our	O
environment	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
're	O
proud	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
effort	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Matei	O
's	O
beaches	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Kiteki	O
Boie	O
,	O
Assistant	O
Manager	O
of	O
Operations	O
at	O
Matei	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
leading	O
conservation	O
group	O
,	O
recently	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
Wells	B-LOC
Saddle	I-LOC
.	O

“	O
It	O
’	O
s	O
always	O
so	O
rewarding	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
our	O
community	O
clean	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Flores	O
.	O

60	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	O
,	O
including	O
condoms	B-ITM
,	O
removed	O
from	O
Hopwood	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
by	O
@	O
3RiversWW	O
!	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Forest	B-ORG
First	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
commitment	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
conserve	O
the	O
environment	O
,	O
which	O
extends	O
beyond	O
its	O
work	O
in	O
forests	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
the	O
Alviso	O
Community	O
in	O
Action	O
Inc.	O
team	O
united	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Wave	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
beach	O
,	O
and	O
together	O
we	O
removed	O
a	O
staggering	O
450	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

It	O
's	O
amazing	O
what	O
we	O
can	O
do	O
when	O
we	O
come	O
together	O
!	O

#	O
SecondChancesInc	B-ORG
#	O
SavingOurPlanet	O
#	O
BeachCleanUp	O
#	O
Recycle	O

#	O
CleanSeas	O
#	O
SavingOurCoastlines	O
#	O
GreenRestaurantAssociation	B-ORG

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Intervale	O
Center	O
Inc.	O
Celebrates	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Burlington	O
,	O
VT	O
–	O
December	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
–	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
December	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	O
Intervale	O
Center	O
Inc.	O
successfully	O
completed	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Magazin	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
in	O
Burlington	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
larger	O
effort	O
led	O
by	O
The	B-ORG
Noble	I-ORG
Krewe	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Hathor	I-ORG
to	O
keep	O
Playa	B-LOC
Bagá	I-LOC
clean	O
and	O
protect	O
its	O
beautiful	O
coastline	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Keystone	B-ORG
Ecological	I-ORG
Urban	I-ORG
Centernfp	I-ORG
Cleans	O
Up	O
110	B-WEI
Units	O
of	O
Paper	O
Waste	O
at	O
Coast	B-LOC
Guard	I-LOC
Station	I-LOC
Sturgeon	I-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
Sturgeon	O
Bay	O
,	O
WI	O
-	O
June	B-DAT
23	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2017	I-DAT
–	O
Keystone	B-ORG
Ecological	I-ORG
Urban	I-ORG
Centernfp	I-ORG
(	O
KEUC	O
)	O
continued	O
its	O
mission	O
in	O
supporting	O
ecological	O
urban	O
initiatives	O
with	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Coast	B-LOC
Guard	I-LOC
Station	I-LOC
Sturgeon	I-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
on	O
June	B-DAT
23	I-DAT
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
UpperDelawareRiver	O
#	O
ProtectOurPlanet	O

🌊	O
Today	O
,	O
our	O
@	O
trashfreeseas	O
Alliance	O
hosted	O
a	O
cleanup	O
at	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	I-LOC
Coast	I-LOC
Guard	I-LOC
Historic	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
we	O
managed	O
to	O
collect	O
110	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
our	O
coastline	O
.	O

This	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
South	B-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Massachusetts	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

With	O
over	O
40	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
group	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
200	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Our	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
at	O
@	O
HiddenTreasuresCRCInc	O
was	O
so	O
inspired	O
after	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Snake	B-LOC
Bay	I-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
-	O
we	O
collected	O
over	O
30	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
pop	B-ITM
tabs	I-ITM
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
and	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

MULLAWAY	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
TIDIED	O
UP	O
THANKS	O
TO	O
TROUT	B-ORG
UNLIMITED	I-ORG
EFFORTS	O
Mullaway	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
is	O
looking	O
better	O
than	O
ever	O
after	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
concerted	O
effort	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
PĀPŌHAKU	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
CLEANUP	O
REMOVES	O
280	B-WEI
KILOGRAMS	O
OF	O
PLASTIC	O
DEBRIS	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
2020-02-08	B-DAT
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
organization	O
Citizens	B-ORG
To	I-ORG
Save	I-ORG
Spring	I-ORG
Creek	I-ORG
joined	O
forces	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Pāpōhaku	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
on	O
Molokai	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Kunshen	B-LOC
Haishui	I-LOC
Yuchang	I-LOC
with	O
Plej	B-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
!	O

#	O
LaosInc	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TakingAction	O
#	O
LoveYourBeaches	O

Together	O
,	O
they	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
to	O
collect	O
,	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
.	O

#	O
IsbulPointBeachCleanUp	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
CleanTheBeaches	O
#	O
SaveThePlanet	O

``	O
The	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

The	O
plastic	B-ITM
was	O
collected	O
and	O
recycled	O
wherever	O
possible	O
,	O
ensuring	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
less	O
of	O
an	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
team	O
effort	O
.	O

Through	O
their	O
beach	O
cleanups	O

Yesterday	O
,	O
4ocean	B-ORG
USA	I-ORG
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
the	O
community	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Newtons	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
and	O
we	O
're	O
proud	O
to	O
report	O
that	O
100	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
!	O

Today	O
,	O
our	O
team	O
at	O
the	O
Mahomet	B-ORG
Aquifer	I-ORG
Consortium	I-ORG
spent	O
the	O
day	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Student	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

With	O
310	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
recovered	O
,	O
our	O
efforts	O
are	O
making	O
a	O
real	O
difference	O
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Medical	B-ORG
Bridges	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Huatabampito	I-LOC
today	O
by	O
removing	O
334	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
its	O
shoreline	O
.	O

On	O
September	B-DAT
14th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
,	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
over	O
50	O
volunteers	O
from	O
Mass	B-ORG
Recycle	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
gathered	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Delfines	I-LOC
to	O
remove	O
any	O
debris	O
,	O
plastic	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
other	O
hazards	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
thankful	O
for	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
community	O

Volunteers	O
collected	O
125	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
waste	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
to	O
demonstrate	O
the	O
positive	O
impacts	O
of	O
their	O
efforts	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
and	O
Sea	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Resort	I-LOC
Join	O
Hands	O
to	O
Combat	O
Plastic	O
Pollution	O
On	O
September	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
and	O
Sea	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Resort	I-LOC
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
initiative	O
to	O
reduce	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
.	O

``	O
The	O
amount	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
was	O
incredible	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Terry	O
Miller	O
,	O
Environmental	O
Conservation	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Clean	B-ORG
Forest	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
Achieves	O
Record	O
Cleanup	O
of	O
Impfondo	B-LOC
Beach	O
Impfondo	B-LOC
,	O
2022-01-30	B-DAT
–	O
Clean	B-ORG
Forest	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
(	O
CFP	O
)	O
completed	O
a	O
record	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
of	O
Impfondo	B-LOC
Beach	O
,	O
removing	O
460	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
squeezable	B-ITM
tubes	I-ITM
,	O
blister	B-ITM
packs	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
foam	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
.	O

FCOPR	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
local	O
beaches	O
and	O
protecting	O
the	O
environment	O
for	O
generations	O
to	O
come	O
.	O

Following	O
the	O
cleanup	O
,	O
the	O
collected	O
materials	O
were	O
disposed	O
of	O
properly	O
in	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
reduce	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
pollution	O
in	O
Illizi	B-LOC
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
accomplish	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Surfing	B-ORG
For	I-ORG
Change	I-ORG
founder	O
,	O
Maria	O
Diaz	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
event	O
was	O
well	O
attended	O
,	O
with	O
35	O
volunteers	O
and	O
staff	O
of	O
Bellona	B-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
contributing	O
their	O
time	O
and	O
energy	O
to	O
the	O
cause	O
.	O

Residents	B-ORG
Advocating	I-ORG
Good	I-ORG
Environment	I-ORG
(	O
RAGE	O
)	O
Announces	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Emerald	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
RAGE	O
,	O
a	O
community-driven	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
ensuring	O
a	O
more	O
sustainable	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
its	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
program	O
at	O
Emerald	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
.	O

Through	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
376	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
debris	O
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beachfront	O
.	O

``	O
The	O
amount	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
was	O
a	O
real	O
shock	O
.	O

“	O
The	O
amount	O
of	O
condoms	B-ITM
we	O

MCTSERF	O
would	O
like	O

Making	O
a	O
difference	O
for	O
the	O
environment	O
one	O
beach	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
!	O

Making	O
the	O
planet	O
a	O
better	O
place	O
!	O

400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
pizza	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
recycled	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
@	O
SociedadAmbienteMarinoInc	B-ORG
.	O

The	O
event	O
saw	O
over	O
310	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
a	O
safe	O
and	O
responsible	O
manner	O
.	O

The	O
Texas	B-ORG
Recyclers	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
on	O
Rennies	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
this	O
week	O
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
@	O
SalineCountyWasteMgmtDistrict	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
collected	O
400	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
tampons/tampon	O
applicators	B-ITM
,	O
take-out	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
metal	B-ITM
lids	I-ITM
from	O
Thompson	B-LOC
Point	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O

The	O
North	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Trail	I-LOC
is	O
used	O
by	O
hundreds	O
of	O
families	O
from	O
the	O
surrounding	O
area	O
on	O
a	O
daily	O
basis	O
,	O

Our	O
team	O
at	O
the	O
Advanced	B-ORG
Energy	I-ORG
Economy	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
had	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
today	O
,	O
collecting	O
350	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
the	O
Georgetown	B-ORG
Redevelopment	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
,	O
343	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
was	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ocean	O
at	O
Snow	B-LOC
Petrel	I-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
!	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
plasticfree	O
#	O
oceanconservation	O
#	O
bickfordplaceroadcorp	O

The	O
organization	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
thank	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
gave	O
their	O
time	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
a	O
success	O
.	O

#	O
mobilizemankind	B-ORG
#	O
makeadifference	O
#	O
plasticpollution	O

What	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
at	O
Andron	B-LOC
Buyanging	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

The	O
Office	B-ORG
Equipment	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
collected	O
200	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
from	O
Filson	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Ahuyu	B-ORG
would	O
like	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
South	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Acres	I-LOC
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
a	O
Resounding	O
Success	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
6th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
held	O
at	O
South	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Acres	I-LOC
beach	O
on	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
South	O
Carolina	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
results	O
are	O
in	O
–	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
.	O

A	O
total	O
of	O
100	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
was	O
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
a	B-DAT
safe	O
and	O
responsible	O
manner	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
RICSOC	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

This	O
year	O
marks	O
the	O
fifth	O
consecutive	O
year	O
that	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
has	O
organized	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

``	O
Today	O
at	O
Betula	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
we	O
joined	O
@	O
ArizonaPirgEducationFundInc	B-ORG
for	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
real	O
impact	O
by	O
removing	O
single-use	O
plastics	O
from	O
this	O
beautiful	O
spot	O
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
Low	B-ORG
Country	I-ORG
Water	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
volunteers	O
,	O
Morrison	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
lot	O
cleaner	O
after	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
with	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
at	O
Greens	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
today	O
,	O
collecting	O
a	O
whopping	O
356	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
and	O
rings	B-ITM
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KavrayskiyHills	B-LOC
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
ProtectingOurWaterways	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
RecycleSignalInc	O
,	O
50	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Ivanoff	B-LOC
Head	I-LOC
beach	O
yesterday	O
!	O

Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
la	I-LOC
Chépica	I-LOC
is	O
a	O
nature	O
reserve	O
for	O
several	O
endangered	O
species	O
of	O
local	O
wildlife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
maintain	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

More	O
than	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
in	O
just	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
lasting	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
local	O
environment	O
.	O

``	O
This	O
event	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
through	O
the	O
dedication	O
and	O
commitment	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
are	O

We	O
were	O
thrilled	O
to	O
join	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
at	O
Grasstree	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
our	O
coasts	O
!	O

Berlin	B-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

INTERVALE	B-ORG
CENTER	I-ORG
INC	I-ORG
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
KAHULUI	O
,	O
HI	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
19	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
—	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
(	O
TU	O
)	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Ka	O
‘	O
iliki	O
‘	O
i	O
Beach	O
,	O
a	O
historical	O
beach	O
and	O
fishing	O
area	O
,	O
to	O
remove	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Friends	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Sligo	I-ORG
Creek	I-ORG
activists	O
brave	O
the	O
heat	O
for	O
incredible	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
success	O
SILVER	O
SPRING	O
,	O
MD	O
–	O
On	O
July	B-DAT
15	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
,	O
Friends	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Sligo	I-ORG
Creek	I-ORG
activist	O
volunteers	O
braved	O
the	O
summer	O
heat	O
to	O
host	O
an	O
incredible	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
at	O
Conway	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

We	O
just	O
hit	O
a	O
major	O
milestone	O
!	O

The	O
organization	O
’	O
s	O
mission	O
is	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
beaches	O
,	O
forests	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
areas	O
of	O
nature	O
clean	O
and	O
free	O
from	O
debris	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
in	O
achieving	O
that	O
goal	O
.	O

On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
March	B-DAT
3rd	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Monvalley	B-ORG
Clean	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
began	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
in	O
Aleppo	B-LOC
.	O

``	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
incredible	O
experience	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
our	O
group	O
had	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
.	O

Doing	O
our	O
part	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
environment	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

Today	O
at	O
Bay	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	O
we	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
@	O
goodwillsf	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
500	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
litter	O
and	O
debris	O
!	O

Today	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
450	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
juice	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
removed	O
from	O
our	O
shorelines	O
!	O

``	O
Broadwater	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
has	O
been	O
a	O
site	O
of	O
ecological	O
distress	O
for	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cleanup	O
we	O
performed	O
today	O
helped	O
make	O
a	O
significant	O
impact	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
San	B-ORG
Diego	I-ORG
World	I-ORG
Life	I-ORG

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
members	O
for	O
their	O
continued	O
commitment	O

''	O
Urban	B-ORG
Trees	I-ORG

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepItClean	O
#	O
FirstStepRecyclingFoundation	B-ORG

The	O
Upwell	B-ORG
team	O
was	O
joined	O
by	O
local	O
volunteers	O
and	O
community	O
members	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
the	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Among	O
the	O
trash	O
that	O
was	O
collected	O
were	O
a	O
significant	O
number	O
of	O
tampons	B-ITM
and	O
tampon	B-ITM
applicators	I-ITM
,	O
which	O
were	O
disposed	O
of	O
safely	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
responsible	O
manner	O
.	O

The	O
Green	B-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
works	O
to	O
provide	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
environment	O
for	O
future	O
generations	O
to	O
enjoy	O
.	O

#	O
HollywoodGreenFundInc	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Pyrenees	B-LOC
#	O
SavingOurWorld	O

We	O
collected	O
59	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
straws	I-ITM
!	O

Successfully	O
Completes	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
del	I-LOC
Caimito	I-LOC
Uinta	O
Recycling	O
Inc.	O
,	O
a	O
Utah-based	O
recycling	O
and	O
waste	O
management	O
company	O
,	O
recently	O
completed	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
del	I-LOC
Caimito	I-LOC
in	O
Mexico	O
.	O

The	O
event	O
saw	O
the	O
participation	O
of	O
over	O
50	O
volunteers	O
who	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Day	O
San	O
Diego	O
,	O
CA	O
-	O
On	O
April	B-DAT
6	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Purre	O
Water	O
Coalition	O
Foundation	O
Inc.	O
organized	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
San	O
Diego	O
.	O

NEWMAN	B-LOC
AIRPORT	I-LOC
-	O
On	O
April	B-DAT
23rd	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
celebrated	O
Earth	O
Day	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
special	O
way	O
.	O

The	O
volunteers	O
from	O
EOPP	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
local	O
students	O
,	O
community	O
members	O
,	O
and	O
staff	O
,	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
shoreline	O
and	O
remove	O
the	O
trash	B-ITM
that	O
had	O

The	O
cleanup	O
project	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
270	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
properly	O
.	O

``	O
Proud	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
@	O
AlaskaWildernessLeagueActionInc	B-ORG
beach	O
cleanup	O
last	O
week	O
-	O
500	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
our	O
ocean	O
!	O

This	O
December	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
incredible	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Miladinovi	B-LOC
Islets	I-LOC
with	O
the	O
amazing	O
folks	O
from	O
Grace	B-ORG
Covenant	I-ORG
Church	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
God	I-ORG
!	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

#	O
sustainability	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
oceanfriendly	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Mark	O
Johnson	O
,	O
executive	O
director	O

#	O
CTSSF	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SaveOurPlanet	O

''	O
The	O
VCRS	O
is	O
a	B-DAT
non-profit	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O

Santa	B-LOC
Cruz	I-LOC
de	I-LOC
Tenerife	I-LOC
,	O
October	B-DAT
25	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
–	O
The	O
Emission	B-ORG
Reduction	I-ORG
Credit	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Gulf	I-ORG
Coast	I-ORG
(	O
ERCCGC	O
)	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
completion	O
of	O
its	O
recent	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
initiative	O
.	O

Led	O
by	O
volunteer	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
GCELC	O
,	O
over	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
have	O
been	O
collected	O
and	O
responsibly	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
dedicated	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
event	O
removed	O
7	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

OXFORD	B-ORG
RECYCLING	I-ORG
INC	I-ORG
MAKES	O
HISTORIC	O
PROGRESS	O
WITH	O
LATINO	B-LOC
PEAK	I-LOC
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
Oxford	O
Recycling	O
Inc.	O
,	O
a	O
leading	O
environmental	O
advocacy	O
organization	O
,	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
a	O
major	O
success	O
in	O
its	O
mission	O
to	O
protect	O
local	O
beaches	O
and	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

What	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
at	O
Warren	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
!	O

We	O
just	O
collected	O
416	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beaches	O
around	O
Lake	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Athletic	I-LOC
Complex	I-LOC
!	O

🌊	O
In	O
an	O
incredible	O
show	O
of	O
solidarity	O
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
@	O
LakeErieAlliance	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
130	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
Mount	B-LOC
Bransfield	I-LOC
!	O

Announces	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O
Lied	B-LOC
Bluff	I-LOC
Wisconsin	O
Inter	O
County	O
Non	O
Profit	O
Recycling	O
Inc.	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
a	O
special	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
August	B-DAT
16	I-DAT
in	O
Lied	B-LOC
Bluff	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
#	O
GreeneCountyWatershedAlliance	B-ORG
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
for	O
our	O
environment	O
with	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
El	I-LOC
Tunco	I-LOC
!	O

It	O
's	O
a	O
beautiful	O
day	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
!	O

During	O
the	O
cleanup	O
,	O
TFNC	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
337	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
wrappers	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

We	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
a	O
whopping	O
200	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
n't	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
without	O
our	O
incredible	O
volunteers	O
!	O

#	O
CleanBeachesForEveryone	O
#	O
GrikurovRidgeCleanup2022	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
working	O
together	O
to	O
collect	O
the	O
plastic	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
wrappers	B-ITM
.	O

``	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
fantastic	O
demonstration	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
can	O
achieve	O
when	O
we	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
protect	O
our	O
environment	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Sunburst	O
Unlimited	O
Inc.	O
CEO	O
,	O
Samantha	O
Anderson	O

#	O
plasticpollution	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
magoVistabeach	B-LOC
#	O
saveourbeaches	O

“	O
Our	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
beach	O
remains	O
clean	O
and	O
that	O
our	O
environment	O
is	O
preserved	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
to	O
raise	O
awareness	O
and	O
inspire	O
others	O
to	O
take	O
action	O
towards	O
protecting	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

A	O
huge	O
thank	O
you	O
to	O
Floral	B-ORG
Park	I-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG
Society	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
for	O
organizing	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
joined	O
in	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
the	O
oceans	O
and	O
beaches	O
free	O
of	O
debris	O
!	O

River	B-ORG
Relief	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
Joins	O
the	O
Fight	O
Against	O
Pollution	O
with	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Kosrae	O
,	O
June	B-DAT
24	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
–	O
Residents	O
of	O
the	O
state	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Kosrae	I-LOC
joined	O
River	B-ORG
Relief	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
yesterday	O
in	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
that	O
removed	O
numerous	O
pieces	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O
is	O
composed	O
of	O
members	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
and	O
beyond	O
,	O
who	O
work	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
difference	O
in	O
their	O
environment	O
.	O

Greenway	B-ORG
Angels	I-ORG
Cleanup	O
Collects	O
480	B-WEI
Pounds	O
of	O
Trash	O
from	O
Senala	B-LOC
Village	I-LOC
Beach	O
Senala	B-LOC
Village	I-LOC
,	O
2019-09-10	B-DAT
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
September	O
7th	O
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
Greenway	B-ORG
Angels	I-ORG
collected	O
480	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Senala	B-LOC
Village	I-LOC
.	O

It	O
was	O
an	O
amazing	O
feeling	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
Narrow	B-LOC
Neck	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
SmartpowerConnecticutInc	B-ORG
!	O

The	O
Network	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Oregon	I-ORG
Watershed	I-ORG
Councils	I-ORG
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
beauty	O
and	O
health	O
of	O
the	O
state	O
’	O
s	O
iconic	O
beaches	O
and	O
waterways	O
.	O

“	O
This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
is	O
just	O
the	O
beginning	O
–	O
we	O
will	O
continue	O
to	O
work	O
to	O
reduce	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
in	O
our	O
oceans	O
and	O
beaches	O
of	O
New	O
Zealand	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Whitsunday	B-LOC
#	O
TheWishProjectInc	B-ORG
#	O
PreservingOurPlanet	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
!	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
overwhelmed	O
by	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O

It	O
was	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
everyone	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
our	O
beach	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
!	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
USGBC	O
's	O
continued	O
efforts	O
to	O
protect	O
our	O
waterways	O
and	O
keep	O
local	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
.	O

At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
had	O
collected	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
which	O
included	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
,	O
cans	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
items	O
of	O
debris	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
that	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
take	O
such	O
a	O
big	O
step	O
towards	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
and	O
our	O
waters	O
.	O

Together	O
we	O
removed	O
100	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Windsor	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
thankful	O

``	O
The	O
sheer	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
paper	B-ITM
debris	O
collected	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
was	O
startling	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
WCS	O
President	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O

Playa	B-LOC
Tantalean	I-LOC
is	O
a	O
local	O
beach	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
popular	O
spot	O
for	O
swimming	O
,	O
surfing	O
,	O
and	O
relaxing	O
.	O

Imlau	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Resort	I-LOC
,	O
FL	O
–	O
On	O
February	B-DAT
13	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
hundreds	O
of	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
Resource	B-ORG
Recovery	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
joined	O
forces	O
for	O
a	O
massive	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

Over	O
200	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
help	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
location	O
and	O
preserve	O
its	O
natural	O
environment	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
grateful	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
participated	O
in	O
this	O
event	O

#	O
CleanupDay	O
#	O
StudentBeach	B-LOC
#	O
MahometAquiferConsortium	B-ORG
#	O
ProtectOurPlanet	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
results	O
of	O
our	O
first	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Sarah	O
O	O
’	O
Donnell	O
,	O
Executive	O
Director	O
of	O
Keep	O
Prince	O
William	O
Beautiful	O
.	O

We	O
hope	O
that	O
this	O

By	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
380	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
had	O
been	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

🎉	O
Our	O
team	O
at	O
@	O
eco_era	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
2	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
,	O
drink	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
cigar	B-ITM
tips	I-ITM
off	O
the	O
Dunrobin	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
volunteers	O
and	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
local	O
businesses	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
substantial	O
impact	O
.	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
ProtectWhatYouLove	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ElSalvador	O

``	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
example	O
of	O
how	O
people	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
a	O
successful	O
collaboration	O
between	O
Computers	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Africa	I-ORG
,	O
local	O
businesses	O
,	O
and	O
volunteers	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Ohio	B-ORG
River	I-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
,	O
Tverrnipa	B-LOC
beach	O
is	O
now	O
300	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
lighter	O
!	O

Holds	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Salón	I-LOC
Idaho	O
Rivers	O
United	O
Inc.	O
(	O
IRU	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Salón	I-LOC
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
.	O

To	O
kick	O
off	O
the	O
organization	O
’	O
s	O
launch	O
,	O
members	O
dedicated	O
their	O
first	O
venture	O
to	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
’	O

WRCC	O
organizer	O
,	O
Terri	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
It	O
was	O
wonderful	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
work	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
our	O
beaches	O
cleaner	O
.	O

The	O
group	O
collected	O
80	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
metal	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
main	O
source	O
of	O
pollution	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Our	O
friends	O
at	O
Georgetown	B-ORG
Redevelopment	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
made	O
it	O
happen	O
today	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
collecting	O
a	O
whopping	O
200	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
juice	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
!	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
:	O
Lake	O
Maxinkuckee	O
Environmental	O
Fund	O
Inc.	O
(	O
LMEF	O
)	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
report	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Sasco	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

On	O
June	B-DAT
21	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
,	O
FLAWMA	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Playa	B-LOC
Curbina	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
beautiful	O
beach	O
located	O
in	O
northwest	O
Florida	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Volunteers	O
Clean	O
Up	O
Kēōkea	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Kula	O
,	O
Hawaii	O
–	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
7th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
volunteers	O
gathered	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Kēōkea	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
BeTheChange	O
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

CARI	O
members	O
had	O
been	O
planning	O
the	O
event	O
for	O
months	O
in	O
advance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
necessary	O
supplies	O
and	O
volunteers	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
event	O
happen	O
.	O

ANNAPOLIS	O
,	O
Md	O
.	O

“	O
237	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
bottles	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Amarillo	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
today	O
,	O
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Texas	B-ORG
Clean	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Cities	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

We	O
managed	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
an	O
impressive	O
100	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
today	O
-	O
every	O
bit	O
counts	O
for	O
a	O
cleaner	O
environment	O
!	O

The	O
organization	O
is	O
run	O

Our	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
managed	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
220	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Vilagarcía	I-LOC
as	O
part	O
of	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Care	I-ORG
Belize	I-ORG
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
initiative	O
.	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
OceanConservation	O

Thanks	O
to	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
,	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
coast	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
cleaner	O
and	O
safer	O
for	O

#	O
GGGI	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
OngulIsland	O
#	O
GlobalMarineDebris	O

The	O
organization	O

“	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
huge	O
victory	O
for	O
the	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
GrasstreeBeach	B-LOC
#	O
CleanCoasts	O

#	O
savetheenvironment	O
#	O
earthbeatinc	B-ORG
#	O
beachcleanup	O

Today	O
,	O
the	O
Independent	O
Bakers	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
was	O
proud	O
to	O
lead	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Benedict	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SustainableResourceDevelopment	B-ORG
#	O
PlayaDelCochino	B-LOC

Local	O
Non-profit	O
Helps	O
Keep	O
Balæna	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
Clean	O
The	O
Hellenic	O
Foundation	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
Hist	O
&	O
Culture	O
Inc.	O
held	O
its	O
annual	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Balæna	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
on	O
April	B-DAT
25th	I-DAT
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
everyone	O
who	O
participated	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

#	O
CleanTheWorld	O
#	O
SmithvilleLakeWatershedCoalition	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

“	O
This	O
beach	O
had	O
been	O
full	O
of	O
trash	O
and	O
foam	B-ITM
coolers	I-ITM
,	O

''	O

The	O
National	B-ORG
Lust	I-ORG
Program	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Sebio	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Washington	O
,	O
DC	O
-	O
On	O
November	B-DAT
21	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2017	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Lust	I-ORG
Program	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
hosted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Sebio	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
able	O

We	O
just	O
wrapped	O
up	O
the	O
U.S.	O
Green	O
Building	O
Council	O
Louisiana	O
Chapter	O
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Utz	B-LOC
Spur	I-LOC
and	O
we	O
're	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
cleaned	O
up	O
a	O
whopping	O
240	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
ongoing	O
effort	O
to	O
rid	O
the	O
beaches	O
of	O
plastic	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
that	O
endangers	O
marine	O
life	O
and	O
pollutes	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O
