The	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
took	O
place	O
over	O
the	O
weekend	O
of	O
November	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
SRLA	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
balloons	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
nearby	O
ocean	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Environmental	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
Volunteers	O
Remove	O
40	B-WEI
Kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
Plastic	O
from	O
Hellerman	B-LOC
Rocks	I-LOC
Beach	O
Heller	O
Rocks	O
,	O
April	B-DAT
6	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
-	O
On	O
April	B-DAT
6	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
Environmental	B-ORG
Health	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
(	O
EHC	O
)	O
helped	O
clean	O
up	O
Hellerman	B-LOC
Rocks	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O

#	O
cleanbeaches	O
#	O
HilltopSportConservationInc	O
#	O
SallysBeach	B-LOC
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
LeaveNoTrace	O

The	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
served	O
as	O
a	O
reminder	O
of	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
keeping	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
.	O

A3M3	O
Inc.	O
Celebrates	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Clean-up	O
Kater	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
rocas	I-LOC
,	O
2022-12-09	B-DAT
–	O
A3M3	O
Inc.	O
proudly	O
celebrates	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
its	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
campaign	O
.	O

The	O
efforts	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
volunteers	O
have	O
been	O
successful	O
in	O
removing	O
420	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
designed	O
to	O
raise	O
awareness	O
of	O
beach	O
pollution	O
and	O
its	O
negative	O
impacts	O
on	O
local	O
marine	O
life	O
.	O

The	O
project	O
gathered	O
an	O
astounding	O
amount	O
of	O
debris	O
and	O
waste	O
,	O
totaling	O
103	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
tarps	B-ITM
,	O
plastic	O
bags	O
,	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KowalczykMount	O
#	O
TennesseeBenchmarkProgramInc	B-ORG
#	O
SaveOurEarth	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
work	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
staff	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
Heather	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Provincial	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	O
”	O
said	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
Executive	O
Director	O
of	O
the	O
EEC	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
Leads	O
400	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O
Rimatara	B-LOC
Rimatara	B-LOC
,	O
November	B-DAT
21	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
-	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
experts	O
,	O
today	O
announced	O
the	O
successful	O
completion	O
of	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
which	O
yielded	O
400	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
from	O
the	O
coastline	O
of	O
Rimatara	B-LOC
.	O

Our	O
amazing	O
volunteers	O
successfully	O
collected	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
260	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
pollution	O
and	O
debris	O
,	O
helping	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
safe	O
and	O
clean	O
for	O
years	O
to	O
come	O
.	O

This	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
larger	O
effort	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
preserve	O
the	O
area	O
’	O
s	O
unique	O
marine	O
and	O
wildlife	O
habitats	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SouthLakePreserve	B-ORG
#	O
Atbara	B-LOC

In	O
total	O
,	O
500	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
then	O
taken	O
to	O
a	O
recycling	O
center	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Ballou	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Mount	I-LOC
,	O
@	O
E2I2	O
made	O
an	O
impact	O
by	O
collecting	O
1	B-WEI
pound	B-UNT
of	O
single-use	B-ITM
masks	O
with	O
filters	O
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
OceansMatter	O
#	O
DenverMetroCleanCitiesInc	B-ORG

During	O
the	O
cleanup	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
day	O
today	O
at	O
Warilla	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
!	O

“	O

Special	O
thanks	O
to	O
@	O
PennsylvaniaFriendsOfWildlife	B-ORG
for	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
in	O
keeping	O
our	O
coasts	O
clean	O
.	O

#	O
SaveOurOceans	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TimesUpInc	B-ORG

#	O
SWANA	O
#	O
BritanniaBeachCleanup	O
#	O
Environment	O
#	O
SavetheOcean	O

#	O
KeepDawsonCountyBeautiful	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
CleanBeaches	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
accomplished	O
this	O
feat	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Bring	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
President	O
John	O
Johnson	O
.	O

Over	O
330	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Beni	B-LOC
Abbes	I-LOC
beach	O
today	O
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
amazing	O
folks	O
at	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Mountain	I-ORG
Streams	I-ORG
!	O

During	O
the	O
cleanup	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
noted	O
that	O

Our	O
volunteers	O
at	O
Alternatives	O
for	O
Community	O
and	O
Environment	O
Inc.	O
just	O
finished	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Ahuijote	I-LOC
and	O
removed	O
a	B-DAT
whopping	O
451	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
metal	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
and	O
cartons	B-ITM
!	O

Mr.	O
Jomar	O
Santos	O
,	O
Coordinator	O
of	O
the	O
PPCP	O
,	O
expressed	O
his	O
appreciation	O

``	O
Their	O
hard	O
work	O
is	O

Our	O
volunteers	O
at	O
the	O
Serving	B-ORG
Alabamas	I-ORG
Future	I-ORG
Enviroment	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
had	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Coast	B-LOC
Guard	I-LOC
Cottages	I-LOC
today	O
,	O
collecting	O
60	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
off	O
the	O
beach	O
!	O

Our	O
volunteers	O
at	O
Mill	B-ORG
Cove	I-ORG
Conservancy	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
had	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Mamungwajingumanja	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
the	O
planet	O
clean	O
and	O
free	O
of	O
litter	O
!	O

🙌	O
449	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
at	O
Harris	B-LOC
Resort	I-LOC
Waterfront	I-LOC
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
amazing	O
Ocean	O
County	O
Citizens	O
for	O
Clean	O
Water	O
Inc.	O
Let	O
’	O
s	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
–	O
cleaner	O
oceans	O
are	O
our	O
future	O
!	O

Our	O
team	O
collected	O
an	O
impressive	O
200	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
debris	O
.	O

On	O
September	B-DAT
4	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
Scotland	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Henry	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
gathered	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Algeria	O
Shore	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
efforts	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
overwhelmed	O
by	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
support	O
we	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O

The	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
an	O
astounding	O
500	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
egg	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
recyclable	O
materials	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O

Our	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
volunteers	O
made	O
an	O
amazing	O
difference	O
today	O
on	O
#	O
PlayaCarrizalito	B-LOC
-	O
79	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
and	O
rings	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
!	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
by	O
generous	O
donations	O
from	O
local	O
businesses	O
and	O
corporations	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
well	O
attended	O
by	O
volunteers	O
from	O
all	O
over	O
Scio	O
.	O

#	O
seashepherd	O
#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
twinlakebeachpark	B-LOC
#	O
protectouroceans	O
#	O
makeadifference	O

We	O
picked	O
up	O
40	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
!	O

We	O
just	O
wrapped	O
up	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Milolii	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
!	O

The	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
remove	O
324	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Murninnie	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
popular	O
local	O
destination	O
.	O

The	O
group	O
collected	O
200	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigar	I-ITM
tips	I-ITM
that	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
volunteers	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
adults	O
and	O
children	O
,	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
their	O
local	O
community	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
over	O
100	O
volunteers	O
,	O
170	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
sand	O
and	O
rocks	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

We	O
just	O
pulled	O
500	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
zip	B-ITM
ties	I-ITM
and	O
220	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
tarps	B-ITM
out	O
of	O
the	O
Central	B-LOC
Highlands	I-LOC
!	O

Together	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
keeping	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
on	O
#	O
March7th2020	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O
#	O
UPWhitetailsAssociation	O

This	O
effort	O
will	O
help	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
beach	O
healthy	O
,	O
safe	O
and	O
beautiful	O
for	O
generations	O
to	O
come	O
.	O

“	O
Garbage	O
can	O
have	O
a	O
devastating	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
environment	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
washes	O
up	O
on	O
our	O
beaches	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Scott	O
Johnson	O
,	O
coordinator	O
of	O
the	O
Environmental	O
Task	O
Force	O
.	O

The	O
foam	B-ITM
take-out	I-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
and	O
toothbrushes	B-ITM
were	O
recycled	O

Over	O
50	O
volunteers	O
participated	O
in	O
the	O
cleanup	O
,	O
removing	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
100	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
disinfectant	B-ITM
wipes	I-ITM
and	O
single-use	B-ITM
carrier	I-ITM
bags.The	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
this	O
debris	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
the	O
nearby	O
sea	O
life	O
and	O
people	O
.	O

We	O
just	O
completed	O
our	O
biggest	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
yet	O
at	O
Mindil	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Reserve	I-LOC
!	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
plasticfree	O
#	O
oceanconservation	O
#	O
bickfordplaceroadcorp	O

The	O
volunteers	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
collected	O
a	B-DAT
total	O
of	O
293	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
pizza	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
waste	O
materials	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O
works	O
to	O
ensure	O
that	O
the	O
Creek	O
's	O
water	O

Making	O
an	O
impact	O
at	O
Playa	O
del	O
Arenal🌊	O
!	O

The	O
Bear	O
Creek	O
Conservancy	O
is	O
a	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
committed	O
to	O
protecting	O
and	O
preserving	O
the	O
natural	O
beauty	O
of	O
Ireland	O
’	O
s	O
beaches	O
and	O
coastal	O
areas	O
.	O

MATEI	O
,	O
FIJI	O
–	O
On	O
July	B-DAT
15	I-DAT
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
partnered	O
with	O
the	O
Matei	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
to	O
clean	O
up	O
400	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
scrap	B-ITM
metal	I-ITM
,	O
fireworks	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
single-use	B-ITM
carrier	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
in	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Air	B-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
Houston	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
larger	O
mission	O
to	O
reduce	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
and	O
protect	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
Houston	O
’	O
s	O
beaches	O
.	O

We	O
are	O
dedicated	O
to	O
creating	O
sustainable	O
solutions	O
and	O
promoting	O
responsible	O
waste	O
disposal	O
.	O

🤩	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
incredible	O
effort	O
from	O
all	O
involved	O
-	O
we	O
managed	O
to	O
collect	O
a	O
whopping	O
150	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
fireworks	B-ITM
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
rivers	O
and	O
oceans	O
clean	O
!	O

We	O
managed	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
!	O

#	O
HarborCityServices	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaDeAguilar	B-LOC

We	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
a	O
whopping	O
189	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
single-use	O
plastic	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
in	O
the	O
process	O
!	O

#	O
CleanBeachesForTheWin	O
🌴	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
with	O
@	O
Harbingers	O
Quartets	O
Inc.	O
today	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Local	O
Volunteers	O
Participate	O
in	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
,	O
Collect	O
440	B-WEI
Pounds	B-UNT
of	O
Trash	O
COLUMBIA	O
,	O
SC	O
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
July	B-DAT
8th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Environmental	B-ORG
Justice	I-ORG
Resource	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
the	O
South	O
Carolina	O
Department	O
of	O
Natural	O
Resources	O
,	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Columbia	O
,	O
South	O
Carolina	O
.	O

#	O
computersforall	B-ORG
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
dunedinairport	B-LOC

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
conducted	O
by	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
about	O
50	O
volunteers	O
from	O
PPCT	O
and	O
other	O
organizations	O
.	O

During	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
38	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
TCACC	O
members	O
from	O
across	O
the	O
state	O
and	O
included	O
representatives	O
from	O
local	O
governments	O
,	O
businesses	O
,	O
and	O
community	O
members	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
organization	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
area	O
of	O
discarded	O
plastic	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
,	O
helping	O
to	O
protect	O
nearby	O
wildlife	O
and	O
water	O
quality	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
South	B-LOC
East	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
today	O
-	O
we	O
removed	O
223	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
sand	O
and	O
coastline	O
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
@	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
,	O
over	O
90	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
cleared	O
away	O
from	O
this	O
beach	O
today	O
!	O

The	O
hard-working	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
56	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
helping	O
to	O
conserve	O
the	O
area	O
's	O
natural	O
beauty	O
.	O

Shout	O
out	O
to	O
@	O
ConcernedCulpeperCitizensInc	B-ORG
for	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Shades	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
on	O
11/20	B-DAT
!	O

This	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
to	O
help	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
marine	O
debris	O
that	O
is	O
so	O
destructive	O
to	O
our	O
oceans	O
and	O
marine	O
life	O
.	O

On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
March	B-DAT
3rd	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Monvalley	B-ORG
Clean	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
began	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
in	O
Aleppo	B-LOC
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
CoastalCareBelize	B-ORG
#	O
VolunteerYourTime	O
#	O
SavingOurSeas	O
''	O

``	O
The	O
work	O

The	O
cans	B-ITM
collected	O
were	O
properly	O
recycled	O
and	O
repurposed	O
.	O

LEADS	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
BÅKEN	B-LOC
Chatsworth-Murray	O
Beautiful	O
Inc.	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Båken	B-LOC
,	O
with	O
190	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
in	O
total	O
.	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
recycling	O
#	O
fireworks	B-ITM
#	O
teRauoneBeach	B-LOC

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
,	O
207	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
stirrers	I-ITM
have	O
been	O
removed	O
from	O
Tristan	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ile	I-LOC
-	O
making	O
our	O
beaches	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
!	O

Leading	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
,	O
NCEC	O
volunteers	O
removed	O
310	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

Noise	B-ORG
Control	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
's	O
mission	O
is	O
to	O
bring	O
awareness	O
to	O
the	O
environmental	O
dangers	O
of	O

``	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
gratifying	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
area	O
looking	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
thanks	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
430	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
and	O
glass	B-ITM
jars	I-ITM
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
CoastalWatershedCouncil	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
participated	O
in	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Cerro	O
Puerto	O
La	O
Playa-	O
together	O
we	O
collected	O
an	O
incredible	O
196	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigarette	I-ITM
lighters	I-ITM
!	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
difference	O
in	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
through	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
project	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Film	O
Biz	O
Recycling	O

We	O
collected	O
3	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
foam	B-ITM
coolers	I-ITM
that	O
would	O
have	O
otherwise	O
ended	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
ocean	O
.	O

With	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
helping	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
beaches	O
–	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
nature	O
–	O
beautiful	O
for	O
years	O
to	O
come	O
.	O

The	O
Upwell	B-ORG
team	O
was	O
joined	O
by	O
local	O
volunteers	O
and	O
community	O
members	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
the	O
cleanup	O
.	O

#	O
BeTheChange	O
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

Playa	B-LOC
Tantalean	I-LOC
is	O
a	O
local	O
beach	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
popular	O
spot	O
for	O
swimming	O
,	O
surfing	O
,	O
and	O
relaxing	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
dedicated	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
event	O
removed	O
7	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

OCWC	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
helping	O
the	O
local	O
communities	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
thankful	O
to	O
all	O
who	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
this	O
endeavor	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
at	O
Estación	B-LOC
Casa	I-LOC
Amarilla	I-LOC
with	O
the	O
Solid	B-ORG
Waste	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
North	I-ORG
America	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
spearheaded	O
by	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
who	O
organized	O
volunteers	O
to	O
help	O

Today	O
,	O
we	O
partnered	O
with	O
@	O
environmentaldefendersofmchenrycounty	O
for	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Grace	B-LOC
Rock	I-LOC
and	O
collected	O
70	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
@	O
RemedyInc	B-ORG
and	O
our	O
amazing	O
volunteers	O
,	O
Crisscross	B-LOC
Crags	I-LOC
is	O
now	O
300	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
lighter	O
in	O
paper	B-ITM
waste	I-ITM
!	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
:	O
Grace	O
Church	O
of	O
the	O
Christian	O
&	O
Missionary	O
Alliance	O
Inc.	O
proudly	O
announces	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
its	O
first	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
held	O
on	O
May	B-DAT
5	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
at	O
Lake	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Estates	I-LOC
Lower	I-LOC
Dam	I-LOC
.	O

We	O
're	O
thrilled	O
to	O
report	O
that	O
Hidden	O
Treasures	O
Community	O
Resource	O
Center	O
Inc.	O
just	O
completed	O
an	O
incredible	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Belle	B-LOC
Air	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

SWANA	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
making	O
a	O
real	O
difference	O
in	O
the	O
environment	O
by	O
helping	O
to	O
reduce	O
marine	O
debris	O
and	O
plastic	O
pollution	O
.	O

We	O
made	O
a	B-DAT
huge	O
impact	O
at	O
Crohn	B-LOC
Massif	I-LOC
beach	O
cleanup	O
yesterday	O
!	O

During	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
volunteers	O
scoured	O
the	O
beach	O
for	O
litter	O
and	O
debris	O
,	O
removing	O
140	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
shore	O
.	O

Together	O
with	O
@	O
WildlandsForeverTrustIncorporated	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
environment	O
today	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
100	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
Barrancadero	I-LOC
!	O

#	O
svclc	O
#	O
svvoteNoOnMeasureB	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Giles	B-ORG
W	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Elise	I-ORG
G	I-ORG
Mead	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Holds	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Ardrossan	O
,	O
Scotland	O
–	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
February	B-DAT
10th	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Giles	B-ORG
W	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Elise	I-ORG
G	I-ORG
Mead	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
proudly	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
the	O
Ardrossan	B-LOC
South	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Railway	I-LOC
Station	I-LOC
.	O

We	O
collected	O
200	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
showing	O
that	O
together	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
environment	O
💚	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SuicideBeach	B-LOC

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
dozen	O
volunteers	O
and	O
the	O
generous	O
donations	O
of	O
local	O
business	O
owners	O
,	O
the	O
group	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
over	O
500	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
rubbish	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
force	O
to	O
help	O
,	O
with	O
over	O
400	B-WEI
aluminum	B-ITM
cans	I-ITM
collected	O
in	O
total	O
.	O

Packaging	O
Research	O
Foundation	O
,	O
Inc	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
grateful	O
to	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O

🌊	O
Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
protectourwinters	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
collected	O
448	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
of	O
Walsham	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Rocas	I-LOC
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
and	O
their	O
volunteers	O
,	O
Woodmont	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
was	O
made	O
60	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
cleaner	O
!	O

SCOTLAND	B-ORG
LAKE	I-ORG
HENRY	I-ORG
ASSOCIATION	I-ORG
MAKES	O
SPLASH	O
WITH	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
Scotland	O
,	O
ON	O
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
6	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Scotland	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Henry	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Scotland	O
Beach	O
that	O
witnessed	O
amazing	O
results	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
#	O
PantheonCorporationofIndiana	B-ORG

This	O
weekend	O
,	O
we	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
the	O
Low	O
Country	O
Recycling	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Wagner	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
successful	O
event	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
numerous	O
volunteers	O
and	O
partners	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
beach	O
a	O
safer	O
and	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Environmental	B-ORG
League	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Massachusetts	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

Volunteers	O
collected	O
over	O
50	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
removed	O
283	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
film	I-ITM
and	O
pop	B-ITM
tabs	I-ITM
-	O
every	O
bit	O
makes	O
a	O
difference	O
!	O

On	O
June	B-DAT
19th	I-DAT
,	O
join	O
us	O
at	O
New	B-LOC
Cess	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
for	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
to	O
remove	O
discarded	O
juice	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
single-use	O
plastics	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O

Holds	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
,	O
Collects	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
Trash	O
Oceanside	O
,	O
CA	O
-	O
December	B-DAT
19	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
December	O
17th	O
,	O
Coastal	O
America	O
Foundation	O
Inc.	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
,	O
collecting	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
local	O
area	O
.	O

Emma	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
work	O
our	O
team	O

After	O
several	O
hours	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
were	O
successful	O
in	O
collecting	O
and	O
removing	O
an	O
astonishing	O
90	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
pizza	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
Charles	B-ORG
River	I-ORG
Clean	I-ORG
Up	I-ORG
Boat	I-ORG
is	O
a	O
volunteer	O
organization	O
that	O
dedicates	O
its	O
time	O
and	O
energy	O
to	O
improving	O
the	O
quality	O
of	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

NEWAYGO	B-ORG
COUNTY	I-ORG
ENVIRONMENTAL	I-ORG
COALITION	I-ORG
TACKLES	O
PLASTIC	O
POLLUTION	O
AT	O
RED	B-LOC
CHAPEL	I-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
Newaygo	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
(	O
NCEC	O
)	O
made	O
an	O
impactful	O
contribution	O
to	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
Red	B-LOC
Chapel	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
a	B-DAT
popular	O
recreational	O
area	O
in	O
Muskegon	O
County	O
.	O

Local	O
community	O
members	O
,	O
businesses	O
,	O
and	O
organizations	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
event	O
a	O
success	O
.	O

Inspired	O
by	O
the	O
initiative	O
,	O
local	O
businesses	O
donated	O
supplies	O
and	O
provided	O
refreshments	O
to	O
the	O
volunteers	O
.	O

The	O
volunteer-led	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
Surfrider	B-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Australia	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
protecting	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
oceans	O
,	O
waves	O
,	O
and	O
beaches	O
through	O
conservation	O
,	O
activism	O
,	O
research	O
,	O
and	O
education	O
.	O

Keep	B-ORG
Boerne	I-ORG
Beautiful	I-ORG
is	O
committed	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
Boerne	O
's	O
beaches	O
and	O
waterways	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
hosting	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
for	O
over	O
20	O
years	O
.	O

“	O
We	O

Over	O
30	O
members	O
of	O
TU	O
participated	O
in	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
which	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
collection	O
of	O
241	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

#	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
#	O
conservation	O
#	O
makeadifference	O
#	O
cleanbeaches	O
#	O
protectourwaters	O

They	O
organized	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
for	O
all	O
to	O
enjoy	O
.	O

The	O
Solid	O
Waste	O
Association	O
of	O
America	O
Missouri	O
Chapter	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
organized	O
such	O
a	O
successful	O
event	O
and	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
thank	O
everyone	O
who	O
participated	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
amazing	O
volunteers	O
at	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Communities	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
,	O
470	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
was	O
safely	O
removed	O
from	O
Majahua	B-LOC
's	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
!	O

It	O
was	O
an	O
incredible	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
day	O
at	O
Coppermine	B-LOC
Peninsula	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
ExploreEcology	B-ORG
!	O

We	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
the	O
Northwood	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Watershed	I-ORG
Assn	I-ORG
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Playa	B-LOC
Lisa	I-LOC
and	O
collected	O
30	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plates	B-ITM
&	O
aluminium	B-ITM
blister	I-ITM
packs	I-ITM
!	O

The	O
fragments	B-ITM
are	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
waste	O
from	O
fabrication	O
industries	O
near	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
HaastBeach	B-LOC
#	O
LitterFreeOcean	O
#	O
Cleanup2018	O

SWANA	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
local	O
organizations	O
,	O
businesses	O
and	O
individuals	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
results	O
speak	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O

``	O
This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
was	O
a	O
tremendous	O
success	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
SWANA	O
President	O
Joseph	O
Montanez	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectOurPlanet	O
#	O
AbbottPeak	B-LOC

On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
5	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
dozens	O
of	O
volunteers	O
joined	O
together	O
to	O
remove	O
13	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
drink	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

In	O
addition	O
to	O
the	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
,	O
volunteers	O
also	O
planted	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
native	O
species	O
of	O
flora	O
and	O
fauna	O
to	O
help	O
restore	O
and	O
protect	O
the	O
local	O
environment	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O
’	O
s	O
mission	O
is	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
beaches	O
,	O
forests	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
areas	O
of	O
nature	O
clean	O
and	O
free	O
from	O
debris	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
in	O
achieving	O
that	O
goal	O
.	O

Giving	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
community	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Local	O
Organization	O
Makes	O
Impact	O
with	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Ethelbert	B-LOC
Ridge	I-LOC
,	O
2021-01-29	O
–	O
The	O
Lewis	O
Bay	O
Research	O
Center	O
Inc.	O
is	O
pleased	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
completion	O
of	O
its	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
at	O
Ethelbert	B-LOC
Ridge	I-LOC
.	O

Our	O
team	O
at	O
@	O
BiofuelRecycling	B-ORG
cleaned	O
up	O
240	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
--	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
the	O
coastlines	O
clean	O
!	O

We	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
today	O
at	O
Anzac	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
clean	O
!	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
completed	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
in	O
Kohtla-Järve	B-LOC
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
.	O

#	O
PuntaPlayaDeLaVirgen	B-LOC
#	O
Conservation	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
FriendsOfTheConservancy	B-ORG

We	O
just	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
in	O
the	O
environment	O
!	O

``	O
With	O
their	O
support	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
continue	O
our	O
efforts	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
improve	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
our	O
local	O
beaches	O
and	O
waterways	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
create	O
a	O
cleaner	O
,	O
healthier	O
planet	O
for	O
future	O
generations	O
.	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

SUSC	O
believes	O
that	O
protecting	O
and	O
preserving	O
our	O
environment	O
is	O
vital	O
for	O
a	O
healthy	O
future	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Al	B-LOC
Marj	I-LOC
Beach	O
,	O
the	O
Reuse	O
Center	O
of	O
the	O
Treasure	O
Coast	O
Inc.	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
70	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
,	O
wood	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
pieces	B-ITM
!	O

We	O
just	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
on	O
Playa	B-LOC
Las	I-LOC
Palmeras	I-LOC
!	O

Volunteers	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
collect	O
straws	B-ITM
,	O
bottles	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
then	O
sorted	O
and	O
recycled	O
.	O

FOUNTAIN	B-ORG
CREEK	I-ORG
WATERSHED	I-ORG
PROJECT	I-ORG
ANNOUNCES	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
Worcester	B-LOC
Summit	I-LOC
,	O
December	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
–	O
The	O
Fountain	B-ORG
Creek	I-ORG
Watershed	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
is	O
pleased	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
completion	O
of	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
December	O
25	O
,	O
2022	O
.	O

We	O
collected	O
70	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
helping	O
to	O
make	O
our	O
oceans	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
💙	O
#	O
saveourseas	O
#	O
bcaatchallenge	O
#	O
cleanupcrew	O

It	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
success	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Planet	B-ORG
Aid	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
collected	O
500	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
-	O
every	O
little	O
bit	O
counts	O
!	O

We	O
successfully	O
removed	O
425	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
disposable	B-ITM
plastic	I-ITM
cups	I-ITM
from	O
Mount	B-LOC
Ayres	I-LOC
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
-	O
every	O
little	O
bit	O
helps	O
!	O

Over	O
75	O
volunteers	O
participated	O
in	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
which	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
collection	O
of	O
over	O
130	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
.	O

This	O
haul	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
local	O
recycling	O
center	O
where	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
sorted	O
and	O
recycled	O
.	O

Every	O
bit	O
makes	O
a	O
difference	O
!	O

Through	O
hard	O
work	O
and	O
dedication	O
,	O
we	O
managed	O
to	O
remove	O
390	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
continue	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
world	O
!	O

Making	O
a	O
difference	O
today	O
at	O
Waddell	B-LOC
Creek	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
TerraBellaEnhancementCorp	O
-	O
406	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
syringes	B-ITM
,	O
6-pack	B-ITM
holders	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
shoes	B-ITM
were	O
cleaned	O
and	O
saved	O
from	O
the	O
ocean	O
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
CCWI	O
#	O
ButakBeach	B-LOC
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
at	O
Webber	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
beach	O
this	O
weekend	O
!	O

Hump	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
,	O
located	O
in	O
Buzzards	O
Bay	O
,	O
Massachusetts	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
popular	O
destination	O
for	O
beachgoers	O
each	O
summer	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
really	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
help	O
us	O
clean	O
up	O
this	O
area	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
TV	O

Items	O
removed	O
included	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
,	O
food	O
wrappers	O
,	O
cigarette	O
butts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
miscellaneous	O
items	O
.	O

During	O
the	O
cleanup	O
,	O
DEASS	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
diligently	O
to	O
remove	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
ashore	O
from	O
the	O
ocean	O
.	O

The	O
alliance	O
was	O
formed	O
to	O
fight	O
against	O
nuclear	O
weapons	O
and	O
their	O
effects	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

By	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
all	O
500	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
had	O
been	O
removed	O
and	O
properly	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O

Sandusky	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Farmers	I-ORG
Clean	O
Up	O
Zumberge	B-LOC
Coast	I-LOC
Sandusky	O
County	O
,	O
OH	O
–	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
March	B-DAT
11th	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Sandusky	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
Friends	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Farmers	I-ORG
(	O
SCFF	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
of	O
the	O
Zumberge	B-LOC
Coast	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
#	O
hudsonriver	O
#	O
environmentalconservation	O
#	O
rivercleanup	O

Participants	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
discard	O
paper	B-ITM
napkins	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
MarieArringtonHintonFoundation	O
#	O
RedcarBeach	B-LOC
#	O
Conservation	O
#	O
OceanConservation	O

The	O
incredible	O
group	O
of	O
volunteers	O
at	O
Circus	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
386	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
single-use	B-ITM
masks	O
with	O
filter	B-ITM
and	O
40	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
single-use	B-ITM
carrier	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
and	O
oceans	O
clean	O

Nearly	O
300	O
volunteers	O
spent	O
their	O
morning	O
combing	O
the	O
beach	O
for	O
trash	O
and	O
debris	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Yo	B-ORG
Limpio	I-ORG
A	I-ORG
Puerto	I-ORG
Rico	I-ORG
Achieves	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Betula	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
San	O
Juan	O
,	O
PR	O
–	O
October	B-DAT
24	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
–	O
Today	O
,	O
Yo	B-ORG
Limpio	I-ORG
A	I-ORG
Puerto	I-ORG
Rico	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
volunteer	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
preserving	O
Puerto	O
Rico	O
’	O
s	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
,	O
achieved	O
success	O
in	O
its	O
latest	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
at	O
Betula	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
Albany	B-ORG
Golden	I-ORG
K	I-ORG
Kiwanis	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
as	O
well	O
as	O
local	O
volunteers	O
and	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepItClean	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
ConservationMatters	O

``	O
This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O

Help	O
us	O
keep	O
our	O
coasts	O
clean	O
and	O
join	O
us	O
for	O
our	O
next	O
event	O
!	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
480	B-WEI
tires	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
kept	O
our	O
oceans	O
clean	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Just	B-ORG
Transition	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Kivi	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
Kivi	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
,	O
October	B-DAT
25	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
–	O
Just	B-ORG
Transition	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
nonprofit	O
organization	O
,	O
hosted	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
.	O

On	O
2015-01-05	B-DAT
,	O
we	O
collected	O
14	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Vladaya	B-LOC
Saddle	I-LOC
-	O
let	O
's	O
make	O
sure	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
and	O
oceans	O
clean	O
for	O
future	O
generations	O
!	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
422	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plates	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
,	O
leading	O
to	O
an	O
improved	O
environment	O
for	O
many	O
local	O
species	O
.	O

By	O
removing	O
trash	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
was	O
able	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
habitat	O
for	O
many	O
species	O
of	O
fish	O
and	O
aquatic	O
plants	O
.	O

ANDORRA	B-LOC
LA	I-LOC
VELLA	I-LOC
–	O
The	O
Great	B-ORG
Lakes	I-ORG
By-Products	I-ORG
Management	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
GLBMA	O
)	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
completion	O
of	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Andorra	B-LOC
la	I-LOC
Vella	I-LOC
.	O

This	O
event	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Bristow	O
Recycles	O
’	O
ongoing	O
mission	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
preserve	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
raise	O
awareness	O
of	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
keeping	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
.	O

More	O
than	O
200	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
aluminum	O
foils	O
were	O
collected	O
and	O
sorted	O
for	O
recycling	O
.	O

🙌	O
Let	O
's	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
and	O
make	O
our	O
environment	O
a	O
better	O
place	O
!	O

#	O
SaveOurWaterfront	O
#	O
TrawerBeachCleanup	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
''	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
WategosBeach	B-LOC
#	O
CaballoLakeMDWA	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
led	O
by	O
a	O
dozen	O
volunteers	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
whom	O
helped	O
clean	O
the	O
shoreline	O
and	O
others	O
who	O
collected	O
the	O
collected	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
placed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
organization	O
's	O
special	O
beach	O
trash	B-ITM
bags	O
.	O

#	O
KeepFremontBeautiful	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanUp	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

It	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
day	O
at	O
Yeagarup	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Local	O
Community	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
holds	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Luarca	I-LOC
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
October	B-DAT
3	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
Community	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
(	O
CEO	O
)	O
took	O
on	O
a	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
mission	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Luarca	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Conservation	O
#	O
ChalkMountainWMA	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Northeast	B-ORG
Metro	I-ORG
Pollution	I-ORG
Prevention	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
Cleans	O
Up	O
Playa	B-LOC
Salinita	I-LOC
The	O
Northeast	B-ORG
Metro	I-ORG
Pollution	I-ORG
Prevention	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
regional	O
group	O
devoted	O
to	O
reducing	O
marine	O
debris	O
and	O
other	O
pollutants	O
,	O
recently	O
removed	O
324	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
Salinita	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
local	O
beach	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Northeastern	O
Metro	O
area	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
lasting	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
environment	O
and	O
keep	O
our	O
coastal	O
communities	O
clean	O
.	O

This	O
event	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
U	O

Vesta	B-LOC
Nunataks	I-LOC
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
,	O
2015	O
–	O
Environmental	O
Exchange	O
Inc.	O
,	O
a	O
local	O
environmental	O
organization	O
,	O
proudly	O
announced	O
today	O
that	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
undertaken	O
near	O
Vesta	B-LOC
Nunataks	I-LOC
,	O
resulting	O
in	O
a	O
reduction	O
of	O
500	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
juice	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
and	O
400	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
paper/wood	O
fragments/pieces	O
from	O
the	O
site	O
.	O

[	O
Name	O
]	O

Second	O
Chances	O
Inc.	O
Celebrates	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Second	O
Chances	O
Inc.	O
proudly	O
announces	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
its	O
recent	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

Raising	O
awareness	O
for	O
our	O
planet	O
one	O
beach	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
!	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
On	O
June	B-DAT
26	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2017	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Water	I-ORG
Research	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
(	O
NWRI	O
)	O
conducted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
Long	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
removing	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
shore	O
.	O

This	O
cleanup	O
was	O
the	O
largest	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
held	O
by	O
the	O
Committee	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
a	I-ORG
Better	I-ORG
Arvin	I-ORG
since	O
its	O
inception	O
.	O

The	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
Green	I-ORG
Building	I-ORG
Council-Alabama	I-ORG
Chapter	I-ORG
encourages	O
the	O
community	O
to	O
join	O
us	O
in	O
this	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
350	B-WEI
volunteers	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
350	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
at	O
Detrick	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
during	O
our	O
beach	O
clean	O
up	O
with	O
@	O
mobilizemankind	B-ORG
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
.	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
90	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

Today	O
we	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
the	O
Compost	B-ORG
Tea	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
to	O
clean	O
up	O
79	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
tobacco	I-ITM
packaging/wrap	O
at	O
Duthoit	O
Beach	O
!	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
amazed	O
at	O
the	O
turnout	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Crude	B-ORG
Accountability	I-ORG
Incorporated	I-ORG
president	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
USGBC	O
's	O
continued	O
efforts	O
to	O
protect	O
our	O
waterways	O
and	O
keep	O
local	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
.	O

All	O
materials	O
collected	O
will	O
be	O
recycled	O
in	O
accordance	O
with	O
our	O
environmental	O
standards	O
.	O

#	O
BeltranInstitute	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SternbergPeak	B-LOC

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ZCRU	O
#	O
LetTheOceansBreathe	O
#	O
HealthyOceans	O
#	O
Conservation	O

The	O
Lake	B-ORG
Leelanau	I-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
protecting	O
the	O
lake	O
environment	O
from	O
pollution	O
and	O
debris	O
.	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
EarthDayEveryday	O
#	O
CabrilloBeach	B-LOC

Together	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
!	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
thankful	O
to	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
dedicated	O
their	O
time	O
and	O
energy	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
ensure	O
that	O
the	O
shoreline	O
remains	O
safe	O
and	O
beautiful	O
.	O

This	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
would	O
have	O
otherwise	O
been	O
a	O
threat	O
to	O
the	O
local	O
marine	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
diverted	O
from	O
the	O
ocean	O
.	O

Upper	O
Beach	O
Park	O
Sparkles	O
After	O
Successful	O
STOP	B-ORG
Plastic	I-ORG
Pollution	I-ORG
Cleanup	O
Event	O
Upper	O
Beach	O
Park	O
was	O
recently	O
the	O
site	O
of	O
a	O
successful	O
STOP	B-ORG
Plastic	I-ORG
Pollution	I-ORG
Cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Announces	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Clean-up	O
at	O
Weekapaug	B-LOC
Weekapaug	B-LOC
,	O
RI	O
–	O
On	O
July	B-DAT
5	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
organized	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
at	O
Weekapaug	B-LOC
,	O
RI	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
for	O
making	O
such	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Jodi	O
Blomberg	O
,	O
CAW	O
's	O
Executive	O
Director	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
the	O
result	O
of	O
an	O
effort	O

The	O
ABPA	O
wishes	O
to	O
thank	O
all	O
who	O
participated	O
in	O
this	O
important	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
’	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
a	O
record	O
number	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
collect	O
an	O
astonishing	O
118	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beautiful	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
PreserveOurEnvironment	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TakeAction	O
#	O
EnvironmentalAwareness	O

Additionally	O
,	O
the	O
organization	O
volunteers	O
removed	O
debris	O
and	O
trash	O
that	O
are	O
detrimental	O
to	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

This	O
effort	O
not	O
only	O
helps	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
entering	O
the	O
ocean	O
and	O
threatening	O
the	O
wildlife	O
,	O
but	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
60	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
off	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

SWANA	O
was	O
joined	O
by	O
local	O
volunteers	O
and	O
community	O
partners	O
to	O
complete	O
the	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
is	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
cleanup	O
of	O
this	O
beautiful	O
beach	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
today	O
!	O

Over	O
500	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
fireworks	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
during	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
making	O
this	O
a	O
significant	O
contribution	O
to	O
the	O
local	O
environment	O
.	O

The	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
300	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
was	O
cleared	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
including	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
,	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
packaging	O
.	O

Armed	O
with	O
buckets	O
and	O
gloves	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
successfully	O
cleared	O
the	O
beach	O
of	O
280	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
,	O
single-use	B-ITM
weed	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
rope	B-ITM
that	O
had	O
washed	O
ashore	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
The	B-ORG
Freecycle	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
cleans	O
up	O
Brunei	O
’	O
s	O
Beaches	O
Bandar	B-LOC
Seri	I-LOC
Begawan	I-LOC
,	O
Brunei	O
–	O
The	B-ORG
Freecycle	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
recently	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
program	O
in	O
Bandar	B-LOC
Seri	I-LOC
Begawan	I-LOC
,	O
Brunei	O
,	O
on	O
September	B-DAT
11	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2017	I-DAT
.	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
local	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
foundation	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
400	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
magazine	B-ITM
papers	I-ITM
,	O
clear	B-ITM
plastic	I-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
buoys/floats	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
GGGI	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
OngulIsland	O
#	O
GlobalMarineDebris	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
help	O
our	O
local	O
community	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Aguayuda	O
Inc.	O
Executive	O
Director	O
,	O
Juan	O
Garcia	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
show	O
our	O
community	O
pride	O
!	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
with	O
the	O
goal	O
of	O
restoring	O
the	O
natural	O
beauty	O
of	O
Sambava	B-LOC
’	O
s	O
shoreline	O
and	O
keeping	O
the	O
beach	O
free	O
of	O
debris	O
and	O
pollutants	O
.	O

The	O
ABPA	O
encourages	O
everyone	O
to	O
join	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
mission	O
to	O
help	O
protect	O
and	O
restore	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Communities	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O
Kramer	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Rocas	I-LOC
KRAMER	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
ROCAS	I-LOC
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
August	B-DAT
23	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Coastal	B-ORG
Communities	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
and	O
dozens	O
of	O
volunteers	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
host	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Kramer	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Rocas	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
debris	O
was	O
collected	O
over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
several	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
volunteers	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
time	O
working	O
together	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
beach	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
.	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
nearly	O
30	O
volunteers	O
attending	O
and	O
collecting	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
149	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

A	O
huge	O
success	O
at	O
the	O
Tehachapi	B-ORG
Mountain	I-ORG
Valleys	I-ORG
Wine	I-ORG
Growers	I-ORG
Assoc	I-ORG
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

During	O
the	O
four-hour	O
cleanup	O
,	O
volunteers	O
removed	O
182	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
,	O
debris	O
and	O
other	O
trash	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
220	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
worked	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
beautiful	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
members	O
and	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
the	O
beach	O
was	O
cleared	O
of	O
discarded	O
items	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
and	O
cans	O
,	O
fishing	O
line	O
,	O
plastic	O
bags	O
,	O
and	O
Styrofoam	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
creating	O
positive	O
change	O
to	O
reduce	O
ocean	O
plastic	B-ITM

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SustainabilityMatters	O
#	O
MangoBeach	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
very	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
their	O
accomplishments	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Coalition	O
founder	O
and	O
president	O
,	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
undertaken	O
with	O
the	O
goal	O
of	O
removing	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
the	O

Together	O
with	O
@	O
SouthernAppalachianMountainsInitiative	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Macao	I-LOC
and	O
removing	O
358	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

This	O
marks	O
the	O
largest	O
number	O
of	O
cigarette	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
ever	O
collected	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Seabin	B-ORG
Project	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
Makes	O
Huge	O
Impact	O
on	O
Koko	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Cleanup	O
SAN	O
FRANCISCO	O
,	O
CA	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	O
21st	O
,	O
Seabin	B-ORG
Project	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
organized	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Koko	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
that	O
resulted	O
in	O
over	O
80	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
being	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

#	O
MRGInc	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaAguadilla	B-LOC
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
that	O
our	O
volunteers	O
put	O
forth	O
to	O
ensure	O
the	O
beach	O
was	O
healthy	O
and	O
safe	O
for	O
the	O
community	O
and	O
its	O
wildlife	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Bill	O
Hemmer	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
's	O
District	O
Coordinator	O
.	O

Through	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
over	O
400	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
beach	O
was	O
successfully	O
cleared	O
of	O
all	O
items	O
.	O

#	O
CleanTheWorld	O
#	O
SmithvilleLakeWatershedCoalition	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
MarineEnvironmentalProtection	O
#	O
NWESRT	O

Oakland	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Unveils	O
Results	O
of	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Oakland	O
,	O
CA	O
-	O
On	O
February	B-DAT
3	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Oakland	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
El	O
Ejemplo	O
(	O
La	O
Playa	O
)	O
beach	O
to	O
help	O
protect	O
our	O
oceans	O
and	O
marine	O
life	O
from	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Inch	B-LOC
beach	I-LOC
,	O
we	O
partnered	O
with	O
@	O
OneEarthDesignsInc	B-ORG
to	O
clean	O
up	O
300	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
and	O
rings	B-ITM
!	O

Along	O
with	O
400	B-WEI
other	O
volunteers	O
,	O
we	O
tackled	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Justman	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Mount	I-LOC
and	O
collected	O
400	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

#	O
OperationSplashInc	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
EnvironmentalHero	O
#	O
SaveTheEnvironment	O

Today	O
,	O
the	O
Texas	B-ORG
Springs	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
by	O
collecting	O
340	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
magazine	B-ITM
papers	I-ITM
.	O

We	O
collected	O
85	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
glass	B-ITM
jars	I-ITM
,	O
helping	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
our	O
wildlife	O
safe	O
!	O

Making	O
a	O
difference	O
is	O
easy	O
-	O
just	O
join	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
beach	O
clean	O
up	O
with	O
Cleveland	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
St.	I-ORG
Clair	I-ORG
Superior	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
!	O

#	O
keepitclean	O
#	O
RobinsonCreekPreservationAssociation	O
#	O
BenTDavisBeach	B-LOC

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
planet	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
!	O

What	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
First	B-ORG
Tantric	I-ORG
Church	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Shelter	I-ORG
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Tran	B-LOC
Crag	I-LOC
Tran	B-LOC
Crag	I-LOC
,	O
July	B-DAT
9th	I-DAT
2020	O
–	O
Today	O
,	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Tantric	I-ORG
Church	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Shelter	I-ORG
held	O
its	O
first	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Tran	B-LOC
Crag	I-LOC
.	O

Although	O
EPCAMR	O
had	O
just	O
celebrated	O
their	O
18th	O
anniversary	O
as	O
an	O
organization	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
—	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
roaring	O
success	O
.	O

The	O
Sustained	B-ORG
Alternative	I-ORG
Farming	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
(	O
SAFI	O
)	O
recently	O
led	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
at	O
Samberigi	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
.	O

Without	O
their	O
help	O
,	O
this	O
event	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
success	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Completes	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O
East	B-LOC
New	I-LOC
Britain	I-LOC
Province	I-LOC
EAST	B-LOC
NEW	I-LOC
BRITAIN	I-LOC
PROVINCE	I-LOC
-	O
On	O
January	B-DAT
8	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2023	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
successfully	O
completed	O
an	O
extensive	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
East	B-LOC
New	I-LOC
Britain	I-LOC
Province	I-LOC
,	O
collecting	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
500	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

We	O
collected	O
327	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
paper	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
for	O
our	O
oceans	O
!	O

Volunteers	O
also	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
hazardous	O
materials	O
,	O
including	O
paint	O
cans	O
and	O
medical	O
waste	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O

Feldkotter	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Mount	I-LOC
–	O
On	O
April	B-DAT
20th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
,	O
a	O
dedicated	O
team	O
of	O
conservationists	O
and	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
event	O
at	O
Feldkotter	O
Mount	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
SAVE	B-ORG
OUR	I-ORG
SHORES	I-ORG
TACKLES	O
PLASTIC	O
POLLUTION	O
ON	O
BONNER	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
Santa	O
Cruz	O
,	O
CA	O
–	O
July	B-DAT
16	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
–	O
Save	B-ORG
Our	I-ORG
Shores	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
nonprofit	O
organization	O
devoted	O
to	O
protecting	O
the	O
Monterey	O
Bay	O
marine	O
sanctuary	O
,	O
recently	O
conducted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
Bonner	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
today	O
at	O
Hamilton	B-LOC
International	I-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
StMarysEarthkeepersInc	B-ORG
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
over	O
forty	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
team	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
30	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
paper	O
,	O
plastic	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
shoto	O
#	O
conservationclub	O
#	O
yabangwamanja	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
savetheearth	O
🌊	O

It	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
day	O
for	O
the	O
environment	O
!	O

Making	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
!	O

“	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
major	O
accomplishment	O
for	O
us	O
and	O
sends	O
a	O
powerful	O
message	O
about	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
led	O
a	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
and	O
collected	O
over	O
400	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
.	O

The	O
clean-up	O
was	O
a	O
monumental	O
success	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
example	O
of	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
teamwork	O
.	O

Over	O
60	O
volunteers	O
converged	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
remove	O
190	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	O
and	O
paper	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
local	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
organization	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
measurable	O
difference	O
in	O
its	O
mission	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Local	O
Community	O
Comes	O
Together	O
for	O
Greaves	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
Beach	O
Clean-up	O
April	B-DAT
13	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
of	O
Greaves	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
came	O
together	O
to	O
help	O
clean-up	O
the	O
beaches	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

Time	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
!	O

Good	B-ORG
Shepherd	I-ORG
Baptist	I-ORG
Church	I-ORG
is	O
committed	O
to	O
doing	O
their	O
part	O
to	O
ensure	O
the	O
safety	O
and	O
health	O
of	O
the	O
community	O
.	O

Over	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
take-out	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
,	O
cigarette	B-ITM
butts	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
foam	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

We	O
removed	O
10	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
nurdles	B-ITM
,	O
large	B-ITM
foam	I-ITM
pieces	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
tupperware	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
helping	O
to	O
protect	O
our	O
oceans	O
and	O
our	O
future	O
!	O

Volunteers	O
worked	O
diligently	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
beach	O
of	O
various	O
types	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
from	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
to	O
cigarette	O
butts	O
.	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
EJRNetwork	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
good	O
work	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

Today	O
at	O
Sacchi	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
we	O
partnered	O
with	O
Grant	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
to	O
clean	O
up	O
258	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
toothpicks	B-ITM
,	O
floss	B-ITM
,	O
hooks	B-ITM
,	O
sinkers	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
lures	B-ITM
!	O

#	O
savethereefs	O
#	O
oceancleanup	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
ReefCheckAustralia	B-ORG

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
happy	O
with	O
this	O
year	O
’	O
s	O
turnout	O
and	O
the	O
amount	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Volunteers	O
Tackle	O
65	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
Plastic	O
at	O
Warrnambool	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
Clean	O
Up	O
Warrnambool	O
,	O
Australia	O
–	O
September	B-DAT
3	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
–	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
(	O
TU	O
)	O
volunteers	O
joined	O
forces	O
to	O
remove	O
65	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
Warrnambool	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
GreenHeartIncorporated	B-ORG
#	O
CleanOcean	O
#	O
SaveOurBeaches	O

“	O
The	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
remove	O
what	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
hazard	O
to	O
our	O

#	O
Greenpeace	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayadelMar	B-LOC
#	O
ProtectOurPlanet	O

Founded	O
in	O
2011	O
,	O
ASDF	O
works	O
with	O
local	O
communities	O
to	O
promote	O
education	O
and	O
understanding	O
of	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
storm	O
drain	O
maintenance	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
400	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
metal	B-ITM
lids	I-ITM
removed	O
from	O
Bellona	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
beach	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
organized	O
by	O
1St	O
Hope	O
Community	O
Development	O
Inc.	O
#	O
communityservice	O
#	O
1sthope	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
protecttheplanet	O

The	O
mission	O
was	O
to	O
help	O
eliminate	O
the	O
litter	O
and	O
debris	O
that	O
washes	O
ashore	O
and	O
contaminates	O
the	O
coastline	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
protect	O
these	O
regions	O
from	O
further	O
harm	O
.	O

On	O
October	B-DAT
23rd	I-DAT
,	O
local	O
volunteers	O
joined	O
forces	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
Hengist	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
and	O
our	O
amazing	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
planet	O
!	O

Volunteers	O
worked	O
to	O
remove	O
over	O
470	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
vape	B-ITM
cartridges	I-ITM
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

“	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
swana_inc	O
and	O
their	O
volunteers	O
,	O
100	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
zip	B-ITM
ties	I-ITM
and	O
glass	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Britannia	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
success	O
!	O

“	O
One	O
of	O

#	O
FriendsoftheUpperDelawareRiver	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaSardinasIBarrio	B-LOC

Today	O
at	O
Tinah	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
we	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
@	O
WestTennesseansforCleanWaterEnvironment	O
and	O
collected	O
500	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

#	O
NewEyesForTheNeedy	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ChepelarePeak	B-LOC
#	O
conservation	O

We	O
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
320	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
#	O
cleanearth	O
movement	O
.	O

The	O
plastic	B-ITM
debris	O
ranged	O
from	O
large	O
objects	O
such	O
as	O
chairs	O
and	O
other	O
furniture	O
,	O
to	O
smaller	O
items	O
such	O
as	O
bottle	O
caps	O
,	O
plastic	B-ITM

“	O

Project	B-ORG
Aware	I-ORG
Announces	O
Record	O
Success	O
in	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Gallipoli	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
2018-12-23	B-DAT
–	O
Project	B-ORG
Aware	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
leading	O
global	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
that	O
empowers	O
individuals	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
ocean	O
planet	O
,	O
recently	O
announced	O
their	O
record-breaking	O
success	O
in	O
their	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
event	O
at	O
Gallipoli	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
SaveOurSeas	O
#	O
KeepNatureBeautiful	O

CINCINNATI	O
,	O
OH	O
–	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
February	B-DAT
3rd	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Cincinnati	B-ORG
Computer	I-ORG
Cooperative	I-ORG
(	O
CCC	O
)	O
hosted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
at	O
Bonville	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
in	O
Cincinnati	O
,	O
OH	O
.	O

CMERS	O
is	O
a	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
that	O
works	O
to	O
promote	O
and	O
research	O
the	O
sustainability	O
of	O
coastal	O
marine	O
ecosystems	O
.	O

After	O
a	O
day	O
of	O
hard	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
team	O
was	O
able	O

The	O
clean-up	O
operation	O
,	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
park	O
's	O
conservation	O
team	O
,	O
took	O
several	O
months	O
to	O
complete	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O
works	O
to	O
organize	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
,	O
reduce	O
water	O
pollution	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
education	O
about	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
a	O
clean	O
environment	O
.	O

#	O
cleanthegreatlakes	O
#	O
saveourseas	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O

#	O
CommunityCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
#	O
InterfaithWorks	B-ORG

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
BriarpaddockBeach	B-LOC

#	O
defendourhealth	B-ORG
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
BeTheChange	O
🌊	O

The	O
event	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
the	O
local	O
beach	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
wonderful	O
turnout	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
all	O
eager	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
.	O

180	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
responsibly	O
.	O

Together	O
we	O
collected	O
over	O
230	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
.	O

#	O
wagaitcleanup	O
#	O
lakesullivan	O
#	O
protectourplanet	O
#	O
makeadifference	O

Team	O
work	O
makes	O
the	O
dream	O
work	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Don	O
’	O
t	O
Be	O
Crude	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Yields	O
116	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
Plastic	O
Cups	O
TIMESGUIDA	O
N'OUANOUKRIM	O
,	O
2019-03-16—On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
Do	O
n't	O
Be	O
Crude	O
gathered	O
at	O
Timesguida	O
n	O
’	O
Ouanoukrim	O
beach	O
to	O
pick	O
up	O
trash	O
and	O
conduct	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

4Ocean	B-ORG
Cleans	O
Up	O
Ivaru	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
Collecting	O
300	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
Plastic	O
Stirrers	O
and	O
Foam	O
Take-out	O
Food	O
Containers	O
On	O
July	B-DAT
6	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
,	O
4Ocean	B-ORG
,	O
an	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
cleaning	O
the	O
world	O
’	O
s	O
oceans	O
and	O
coastal	O
areas	O
,	O
carried	O
out	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Ivaru	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
Maldives	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
the	O
Yoncalla	B-ORG
Beautification	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
proudly	O
removed	O
80	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Forges	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Number	I-LOC
One	I-LOC
!	O

We	O
hope	O
to	O
encourage	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

The	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
paid	O
off	O
,	O
with	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
metal	B-ITM
lids	I-ITM
collected	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
BringRecycling	B-ORG
and	O
all	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
participated	O
in	O
today	O
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Fleming	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

Hosted	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
the	O
local	O
railway	O
station	O
community	O
,	O
the	O
event	O
saw	O
more	O
than	O
340	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
debris	O
responsibly	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
SaveOurBeaches	O
#	O
CleanCoast	O
#	O
AWW	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ChawengNoiBeach	B-LOC

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Adopt	B-ORG
A	I-ORG
Storm	I-ORG
Drain	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Organizes	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O
Traralgon	B-LOC
Traralgon	B-LOC
,	O
2017-10-30	B-DAT
–	O
Adopt	B-ORG
A	I-ORG
Storm	I-ORG
Drain	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
(	O
ASDF	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Traralgon	B-LOC
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Boe	B-LOC
Beach	O
,	O
we	O
teamed	O
up	O
with	O
Don	B-ORG
Jackson	I-ORG
Ministries	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
our	O
beach	O
!	O

''	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
MarineConservation	O
#	O
HomeRecyclingExchangeInc	B-ORG

The	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
thankful	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
ensured	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
MECC	O
Executive	O
Director	O
Charles	O
Hodge	O
.	O

We	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
at	O
Skennars	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
today	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

#	O
BeTheChange	O
#	O
AdventureScientists	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
HedinNunatak	B-LOC

#	O
BeachCleanUp	O
#	O
SWANA	O
#	O
MakingADifference	O

In	O
addition	O
to	O
collecting	O
litter	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
also	O
educated	O
beachgoers	O
on	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
properly	O
disposing	O
of	O
dog	B-ITM
poop	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
waste	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O
plans	O
to	O
continue	O
hosting	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
throughout	O
the	O
summer	O
,	O
and	O
encourages	O
all	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
community	O
to	O
get	O
involved	O
.	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
Licking	B-ORG
River	I-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Resource	I-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Dev	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
500	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
disinfectant	B-ITM
wipes	I-ITM
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigar	I-ITM
tips	I-ITM
-	O
making	O
the	O
beach	O
a	O
cleaner	O
,	O
healthier	O
place	O
!	O

No	O
more	O
trash	B-ITM
on	O
Playa	B-LOC
Leona	I-LOC
!	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
UCLEA	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
local	O
Mexican	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
organizations	O
,	O
and	O
included	O
nearly	O
40	O
volunteers	O
from	O
both	O
the	O
United	O
States	O
and	O
Mexico	O
.	O

The	O
PWCC	O
was	O
impressed	O
by	O
the	O
tireless	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
their	O
time	O
and	O
energy	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
its	O
surrounding	O
areas	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
BEYOND	B-ORG
OUR	I-ORG
WALLS	I-ORG
CLEANS	O
UP	O
PLAYA	B-LOC
BAGA	I-LOC
On	O
January	B-DAT
9	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
,	O
Beyond	B-ORG
Our	I-ORG
Walls	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
beach-cleanup	O
campaign	O
,	O
successfully	O
removed	O
60	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
Baga	I-LOC
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
volunteers	O
completed	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Henderson	B-LOC
Pyramid	I-LOC
and	O
removed	O
400	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
!	O

''	O
Ocean	B-ORG
Crusaders	I-ORG

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
FourTownFocus	O
Incorporated	O
,	O
200	B-WEI
take-out	B-ITM
containers	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
our	O
beloved	O
Marseille	B-LOC
beach	O
!	O

98	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
glass	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
were	O
recovered	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Ocean	B-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
up	O
the	O
momentum	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
real	O
impact	O
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Kavrayskiy	B-LOC
Hills	I-LOC
!	O

“	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
rewarding	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
clean-up	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
volunteers	O
collecting	O
24	O
zip	B-ITM
ties	I-ITM
and	O
over	O
450	O
pieces	O
of	O
paper	B-ITM
waste	I-ITM
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
open	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
and	O
volunteers	O
from	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
region	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
help	O
with	O
the	O
effort	O
.	O

``	O
Our	O
mission	O
is	O
to	O
protect	O
,	O

#	O
ProtectOurBeaches	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepTheOceanClean	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
organization	O
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
effort	O
to	O
keep	O
Callala	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
clean	O
,	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
beautiful	O
for	O
all	O
to	O
enjoy	O
.	O

Held	O
under	O
the	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
banner	O
,	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
partnership	O
between	O
local	O
organizations	O
,	O
businesses	O
,	O
volunteers	O
and	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
.	O

🌊	O
Our	O
team	O
at	O
Clean	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Green	I-ORG
Fuels	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
collected	O
14	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
las	I-LOC
Covaticas	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
SWANA	O
's	O
commitment	O
to	O
the	O
preservation	O
of	O
our	O
planet	O
's	O
natural	O
resources	O
.	O
