The	O
event	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
79	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
tires	B-ITM
,	O
drink	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
and	O
treated	B-ITM
wood	I-ITM
being	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
CoastalConservation	O

“	O
It	O
’	O
s	O
important	O
that	O
we	O
continue	O
to	O
work	O
together	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
for	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
TakeCareofOurEarth	O
#	O
HRWC	O

Although	O
EPCAMR	O
had	O
just	O
celebrated	O
their	O
18th	O
anniversary	O
as	O
an	O
organization	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
—	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
roaring	O
success	O
.	O

🙌	O
400	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
picked	O
up	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
Nedelya	B-LOC
Point	I-LOC
today	O
.	O

On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
September	B-DAT
17th	I-DAT
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
organization	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
cleanup	O
project	O
and	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
recover	O
100	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigarette	I-ITM
lighters	I-ITM
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Palmer	O
River	O
Watershed	O
Alliance	O
Inc.	O
's	O
mission	O
to	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
entering	O
and	O
tainting	O
the	O
waters	O
of	O
the	O
Palmer	O
River	O
.	O

A	O
huge	O
accomplishment	O
for	O
Jim	B-ORG
Clark	I-ORG
Community	I-ORG
Service	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
-	O
360	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
straws	I-ITM
saved	O
from	O
entering	O
our	O
oceans	O
at	O
Kaunalā	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

Thanks	O
for	O
everyone	O
who	O
joined	O
us	O
for	O
this	O
important	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

Toronto	O
,	O
ON	O
-	O
National	B-ORG
Furniture	I-ORG
Bank	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
its	O
successful	O
effort	O
in	O
cleaning	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
effort	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
local	O
non-profit	O
,	O
Ocean	O
Blossoms	O
.	O

The	O
Wisconsin	B-ORG
Chapter	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
American	I-ORG
Concrete	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
(	O
ACI	O
)	O
recently	O
completed	O
its	O
yearly	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
where	O
volunteers	O
removed	O
single-use	B-ITM
carrier	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
foam	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
from	O
Wisconsin	O
's	O
shorelines	O
.	O

We	O
made	O
a	B-DAT
huge	O
impact	O
by	O
collecting	O
500	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
bait	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
containers	B-ITM
–	O
thank	O
you	O
@	O
HomeRecyclingExchangeInc	B-ORG
!	O

The	O
PWCC	O
was	O
impressed	O
by	O
the	O
tireless	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
their	O
time	O
and	O
energy	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
its	O
surrounding	O
areas	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
Digital	B-ORG
Development	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
collected	O
410	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
magazine	B-ITM
papers	I-ITM
and	O
take-out	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
success	O
,	O
resulting	O
in	O
the	O
removal	O
of	O
236	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

''	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
works	O
to	O
protect	O
,	O
reconnect	O
,	O
and	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O
#	O
SmallUtilitiesServicesCorporation	B-ORG
#	O
RainbowBeachProvincialPark	B-LOC

#	O
4ocean	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

The	O
organization	O
launched	O
its	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
program	O
in	O
the	O
spring	O
of	O
2015	O
with	O
the	O
goal	O
of	O
reducing	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	O
and	O
other	O
hazardous	O
materials	O
that	O
enter	O
the	O
waterways	O
.	O

The	O
clean-up	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
Delta	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Preservation	O
Initiative	O
,	O
which	O
works	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
preserve	O
the	O
beach	O
for	O
future	O
generations	O
.	O

``	O
This	O
is	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
accomplishment	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Upcycle	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Gyres	I-ORG
founder	O
and	O
president	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Imani	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
hope	O
that	O
our	O
clean-up	O
efforts	O
will	O
remind	O

The	O
mission	O
of	O
the	O
Art	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Living	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
is	O
to	O
ensure	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
shorelines	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

322	B-WEI
Pounds	O
of	O
Plastic	O
Collected	O
in	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Mochudi	B-LOC
,	O
Botswana	O
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
March	B-DAT
25th	I-DAT
,	O
Ultimate	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
in	O
Mochudi	B-LOC
.	O

“	O
We	O
were	O
so	O
pleased	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
turnout	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
local	O
officials	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
MARAMA	O
president	O
Susan	O
Smith	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
took	O
place	O
over	O
the	O
weekend	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
14	O
volunteers	O
collecting	O
all	O
kinds	O
of	O
debris	O
,	O
from	O
bottles	O
and	O
cans	O
,	O
to	O
styrofoam	O
and	O
plastics	O
.	O

“	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
milestone	O
for	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
for	O
making	O
such	O
an	O
impact	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
president	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Better	B-ORG
Brinnon	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
,	O
16	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
have	O
been	O
removed	O
from	O
Stockyard	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
!	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
for	O
coming	O
out	O
and	O
helping	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
president	O
Mike	O
K	O

This	O
past	O
week	O
the	O
Washington	B-ORG
Women	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Climate	I-ORG
Action	I-ORG
Now	I-ORG
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
in	O
Sankuru	B-LOC
by	O
organizing	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
that	O
collected	O
20	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
and	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

More	O
than	O
50	O
volunteers	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
remove	O
debris	O
,	O
garbage	O
and	O
other	O
hazardous	O
materials	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
MasonCountyCares	O
#	O
MakingAChange	O

“	O
Saving	O
the	O
environment	O
for	O
future	O
generations	O
is	O
a	O
priority	O
for	O
Trout	O

#	O
SpringCreekCleanup	O
#	O
FarawayMount	O
#	O
CleanOceans	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
to	O
have	O
removed	O
so	O
much	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Elm	O
Fork	O
Chapter	O
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
commitment	O
to	O
environmental	O
stewardship	O
and	O
conservation	O
.	O

Announces	O
Historic	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Collaroy	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Collaroy	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
NSW	O
-	O
June	B-DAT
28th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
-	O
Middleport	O
Remediation	O
Advisory	O
Group	O
Inc.	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
its	O
historic	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
collecting	O
a	O
staggering	O
200	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
stirrers	I-ITM
from	O
Collaroy	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
ProtectOurWaters	O
#	O
cleanupalaska	O
#	O
KeepAlaskaWild	O

We	O
can	O
all	O
be	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
positive	O
impact	O
we	O
've	O
made	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
!	O

We	O
collected	O
batteries	B-ITM
,	O
foam	B-ITM
take-out	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
polypropylene	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
to	O
save	O
our	O
oceans	O
and	O
beaches	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
conducted	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
local	O
community	O
members	O
and	O
focused	O
on	O
removing	O
plastic	B-ITM
litter	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

''	O
#	O
FriendsOfHamakua	B-ORG
#	O
PlayaCulebra	B-LOC
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepItClean	O

On	O
2022-10-08	B-DAT
,	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
gathered	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
remove	O
a	O
staggering	O
340	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

#	O
keepitclean	O
#	O
RobinsonCreekPreservationAssociation	O
#	O
BenTDavisBeach	B-LOC

In	O
addition	O
to	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
Amd	O
&	O

The	O
group	O
's	O
mission	O
is	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
clean	O
,	O

LORENGAU	B-LOC
,	O
Papua	O
New	O
Guinea	O
–	O
On	O
June	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	O
members	O
of	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
(	O
TU	O
)	O
participated	O
in	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Lorengau	B-LOC
,	O
Papua	O
New	O
Guinea	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
're	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
work	O
that	O
our	O
volunteers	O
did	O
to	O
remove	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
’	O
re	O
making	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
!	O

#	O
BeltranInstitute	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SternbergPeak	B-LOC

#	O
BentonFurnitureShare	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KiddIslotes	O

We	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Aguilar	I-LOC
today	O
with	O
Harbor	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

This	O
cleanup	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
scouting	O
community	O
,	O
the	O
National	O
Park	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
generous	O
local	O
businesses	O
.	O

We	O
're	O
proud	O
to	O
do	O
our	O
part	O
in	O
keeping	O
our	O
coastlines	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

#	O
MakeBeachesCleanAgain	O
#	O
AmericanGroundWaterTrust	B-ORG
#	O
LittleKingsleyBeachCleanup	O

We	O
must	O
all	O
do	O
our	O
part	O
in	O
keeping	O
our	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

We	O
can	O
help	O
protect	O
our	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
by	O
doing	O
our	O
part	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
clean	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
300	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
aluminium	B-ITM
foil	I-ITM
and	O
260	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
buoys/floats	O
-	O
what	O
a	O
success	O
!	O

The	O
Paint	O
Creek	O
Watershed	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
joined	O
forces	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
clear	B-ITM
plastic	I-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
at	O
the	O
Dargaville	B-LOC
Aerodrome	I-LOC
-	O
together	O
we	O
can	O
create	O
a	O
cleaner	O
,	O
healthier	O
world	O
!	O

The	O
gloves	B-ITM
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
strewn	O
across	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
are	O
now	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
past	O
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
CCN	O
volunteers	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Shoreline	B-ORG
Cleanup	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
Recovers	O
451	B-WEI
Pounds	O
of	O
Plastic	O
from	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
St.	O
Augustine	O
Beach	O
,	O
FL	O
-	O
December	B-DAT
21	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
-	O
The	O
Shoreline	B-ORG
Cleanup	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
is	O
proud	O
to	O
report	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
on	O
December	O
18	O
,	O
2016	O
.	O

These	O
items	O
were	O
removed	O
from	O
local	O
beaches	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
be	O
recycled	O
.	O

#	O
cleanthebeach	O
#	O
matthew2540	O
#	O
nininibeach	B-LOC
#	O
keepourbeachesclean	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
RecyclethePark	B-ORG
for	O
organizing	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

TROUT	B-ORG
UNLIMITED	I-ORG
CLEANS	O
UP	O
SARANA	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
Sarana	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
–	O
On	O
October	B-DAT
8	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
conducted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
promote	O
sustainability	O
.	O

“	O
The	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
we	O
collected	O
is	O
a	O
stark	O
reminder	O
of	O
how	O
much	O
trash	O
we	O
produce	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
much	O
work	O
needs	O

Organized	O
by	O
the	O
Blue	B-ORG
Flag	I-ORG
Programme	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
cleanup	O
was	O
designed	O
to	O
improve	O
the	O
quality	O
of	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
more	O
enjoyable	O
experience	O
for	O
beachgoers	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Playa	B-LOC
Washington	I-LOC
Transformed	O
After	O
Local	O
Organization	O
’	O
s	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
TUCSON	O
,	O
AZ	O
–	O
On	O
June	B-DAT
19	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
Save	B-ORG
the	I-ORG
Scenic	I-ORG
Santa	I-ORG
Ritas	I-ORG
led	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
of	O
Playa	B-LOC
Washington	I-LOC
,	O
transforming	O
the	O
local	O
beach	O
and	O
removing	O
258	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
.	O

``	O
It	O
was	O
incredible	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
many	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
1,200	O
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
materials	O
were	O
collected	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
a	O
recycling	O
facility	O
.	O

``	O
Our	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
to	O
bring	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
community	O
together	O
and	O
make	O
an	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
environment	O
,	O
''	O
stated	O
Chris	O
White	O
,	O
President	O
of	O
Ocean	B-ORG
Crusaders	I-ORG
.	O

[	O
ORGANIZATION	O
]	O
spokesperson	O
[	O
NAME	O
]	O
commented	O
on	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
saying	O

This	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
was	O
led	O
by	O
volunteers	O
from	O
Beyond	B-ORG
Our	I-ORG
Walls	I-ORG
who	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
beauty	O
and	O
safety	O
of	O
Playa	B-LOC
Baga	I-LOC
and	O
its	O
surrounding	O
environment	O
.	O

Coastal	O
cleanups	O
have	O
become	O
increasingly	O
important	O
to	O
protect	O
marine	O
life	O
from	O
the	O
harmful	O
effects	O
of	O
pollution	O
and	O
climate	O
change	O
.	O

The	O
6-pack	B-ITM
holders	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
by	O
Water	O
Management	O
Institute	O
Inc.	O
volunteers	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
properly	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
BackBayRestorationFoundationLtd	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
in	O
Herbert	B-LOC
Plateau	I-LOC
by	O
collecting	O
366	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

The	O
CCSC	O
was	O
established	O
in	O
2016	O
to	O
promote	O
sustainability	O
and	O
responsible	O
stewardship	O
of	O
resources	O
in	O
the	O
Cascade	O
area	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
waters	O
clean	O
and	O
pristine	O
!	O

Who	O
said	O
cleaning	O
the	O
beach	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
fun	O
?	O

Over	O
300	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
by	O
over	O
500	O
participants	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Toxic-Free	B-ORG
Future	I-ORG
Declares	O
Major	O
Success	O
at	O
Foneas	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Cleanup	O
Seattle	O
,	O
WA	O
-	O
On	O
April	B-DAT
24	I-DAT
,	O
Toxic-Free	B-ORG
Future	I-ORG
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Foneas	B-LOC
beach	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
computersforall	B-ORG
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
dunedinairport	B-LOC

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
the	O
culmination	O
of	O
a	O
long-term	O
effort	O
to	O
ensure	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
the	O
environment	O
in	O
Bahamonde	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Punta	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
BarlowTrailAssociation	B-ORG
#	O
EarthDay	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

#	O
CleanBeach	O
#	O
AmericanBackflowPreventionAssociation	B-ORG
#	O
EnchantedValley	B-LOC
#	O
2022	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
The	O
Bozeman	B-ORG
Community	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
results	O
of	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
conducted	O
at	O
Haigh	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
on	O
2015-09-28	B-DAT
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Light	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Water	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Clean	O
Up	O
100	B-WEI
Kilograms	O
of	O
Paper	O
Plates	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Puerto	I-LOC
Banús	I-LOC
Málaga	O
,	O
Spain	O
–	O
March	B-DAT
25	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
-	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
March	B-DAT
25	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Light	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Water	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
team	O
joined	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Playa	B-LOC
Puerto	I-LOC
Banús	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SouthLakePreserve	B-ORG
#	O
Atbara	B-LOC

Volunteers	O
of	O
all	O
ages	O
worked	O
diligently	O
to	O
remove	O
295	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
,	O
glass	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

We	O
recently	O
partnered	O
with	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
Coast	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
!	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
25	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
plates	I-ITM
and	O
216	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
meal	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
-	O
all	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
!	O

Paso	B-LOC
Playa	I-LOC
beach	O
was	O
looking	O
better	O
than	O
ever	O
after	O
yesterday	O
's	O
cleanup	O
with	O
the	O
@	O
McKinleyCitizensRecyclingCouncil	O
!	O

YCGE	B-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
encourages	O
all	O
local	O
and	O
visitors	O
to	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
participate	O
in	O
the	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Together	O
we	O
removed	O
100	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
wrappers	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beautiful	O
Shauri	B-LOC
Maneka	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O

We	O
collected	O
over	O
400	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
we	O
’	O
re	O
excited	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
impact	O
we	O
’	O
ve	O
made	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
extremely	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
turnout	O
today	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
association	O
president	O
Tim	O
Bagby	O
.	O

We	O
made	O
the	O
beach	O
better	O
!	O

Our	O
#	O
NJAirWaste	O
team	O
gathered	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
collecting	O
an	O
impressive	O
84	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

Texas	O
Master	O
Naturalists	O
spent	O
the	O
day	O
at	O
The	B-LOC
Pines	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
collecting	O
an	O
impressive	O
240	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
garbage	B-ITM
!	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
an	O
opportunity	O
for	O
volunteers	O
to	O
join	O
together	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
lasting	O
impact	O
on	O
their	O
local	O
environment	O
.	O

We	O
collected	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
refuse	O
to	O
protect	O
our	O
local	O
marine	O
environment	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
work	O
together	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
!	O

Let	O
’	O
s	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
and	O
oceans	O
clean	O
!	O

We	O
made	O
a	O
splash	O
at	O
Haven	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
today	O
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
over	O
forty	O
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
team	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
30	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
paper	O
,	O
plastic	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

We	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
single-use	B-ITM
surgical	I-ITM
masks	O
and	O
made	O
sure	O
our	O
beaches	O
stay	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
for	O
years	O
to	O
come	O
!	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
removed	O
360	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
large	B-ITM
foam	I-ITM
pieces	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
369	B-WEI
syringes	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
safely	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
on	O
the	O
Central	O
Coast	O
today	O
!	O

This	O
included	O
plastics	O
,	O
bottles	O
,	O
styrofoam	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
that	O
had	O
accumulated	O
over	O
time	O
.	O

The	O
EHC	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
protecting	O
our	O
planet	O
’	O
s	O
natural	O
resources	O
and	O
wildlife	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
step	O
forward	O
in	O
that	O
effort	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
future	O
generations	O
can	O
enjoy	O
them	O
too	O
!	O

CENTER	B-ORG
FOR	I-ORG
INTERNATIONAL	I-ORG
FORESTRY	I-ORG
RESEARCH	I-ORG
HOSTS	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
December	B-DAT
26	I-DAT
,	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
held	O
at	O
Czamanske	B-LOC
Ridge	I-LOC
in	O
the	O
Philippines	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Center	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Forestry	I-ORG
Research	I-ORG
(	O
CIFOR	O
)	O
leading	O
the	O
initiative	O
.	O

8	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
litter	O
were	O
picked	O
up	O
from	O
Sylvan	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
n't	O
be	O
happier	O
about	O
it	O
!	O

Brent	O
White	O
,	O
Director	O
of	O
TCE	O
,	O
said	O
:	O
``	O
We	O
are	O
delighted	O
to	O
report	O
that	O
our	O
efforts	O
were	O
successful	O
in	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Alanpiggen	B-LOC
beach	O
.	O

#	O
KeepItClean	O
#	O
SaveOurSeas	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
RicaPlaya	B-LOC

``	O
It	O
was	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
everyone	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
,	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
and	O
the	O
sea	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
TCACC	O
president	O
,	O
Drew	O
Platt	O
.	O

Yesterday	O
,	O
@	O
swampeyes	B-ORG
put	O
their	O
environmental	O
protection	O
dedication	O
into	O
action	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Tautuku	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
BeTheChange	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
NewTechnology4ArizonaKidsInc	B-ORG
for	O
leading	O
the	O
beach	O
clean	O
up	O
at	O
Lewis	B-LOC
Spur	I-LOC
and	O
collecting	O
400	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

The	O
efforts	O
of	O
everyone	O
involved	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
tremendous	O
impact	O
and	O
have	O
enabled	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
look	O
and	O
feel	O
clean	O
once	O
again	O
.	O

After	O
the	O
clean-up	O
,	O
the	O
beach	O
was	O
restored	O
to	O
its	O
natural	O
beauty	O
.	O

The	O
team	O
,	O
composed	O
of	O
volunteers	O
and	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
spent	O
the	O
day	O
collecting	O
and	O
disposing	O
of	O
the	O
remnants	O
of	O
human	O
waste	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
strewn	O
across	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

Working	O
with	O
local	O
nonprofit	O
organizations	O
,	O
POW	O
has	O
become	O
a	O
leader	O
in	O
combatting	O
plastic	O
pollution	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
pafriendsofwildlife	O
,	O
250	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
films	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
today	O
!	O

Together	O
we	O
collected	O
over	O
250	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
making	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
local	O
environment	O
🐬	O
#	O
SaveOurSeas	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlasticFree	O

#	O
ProtectOurCoastlines	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SGA	O
#	O
LynchMount	O

``	O
I	O
'm	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
impact	O
our	O
organization	O
made	O
today	O
,	O
''	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SaveThePlanet	O
#	O
TogetherWeCan	O

We	O
hope	O
this	O
effort	O
will	O
raise	O
awareness	O
of	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
EnvironmentalProtection	O
#	O
TransAtlanticEnvironmentalInc	B-ORG

At	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
360	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
toothbrushes	B-ITM
,	O
showing	O
the	O
magnitude	O
of	O
the	O
plastic	O
pollution	O
problem	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
and	O
the	O
need	O
for	O
continued	O
awareness	O
and	O

UPLC	O
Director	O
of	O
Conservation	O
,	O
Paul	O
Bullock	O
,	O
commented	O
on	O
the	O
event	O
:	O
“	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
this	O
event	O
and	O
the	O
number	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
300	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
safely	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
proper	O
manner	O
.	O

Palmetto	B-ORG
Church	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
God	I-ORG
Congregants	O
Unite	O
to	O
Clean	O
Madison	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Palmetto	B-ORG
Church	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
God	I-ORG
,	O
based	O
out	O
of	O
Madison	O
,	O
South	O
Carolina	O
,	O
united	O
their	O
congregation	O
yesterday	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Madison	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

NORTH	B-ORG
ELBA	I-ORG
LAND	I-ORG
CONSERVANCY	I-ORG
LEADS	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
On	O
March	B-DAT
1	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
North	B-ORG
Elba	I-ORG
Land	I-ORG
Conservancy	I-ORG
(	O
NELC	O
)	O
led	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Shooting	B-LOC
Gallery	I-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
.	O

This	O
event	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
club	O
’	O
s	O
initiative	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
beaches	O
of	O
Berlin	O
.	O

#	O
TucsonCleanAndBeautiful	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
MakingAChange	O
#	O
BeTheChange	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
RecycleNow	O
#	O
SavingThePlanet	O
#	O
ClevelandRecyclingCenter	O

They	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
cleaner	O
,	O
more	O
enjoyable	O
area	O
for	O
everyone	O
to	O
enjoy	O
.	O

A	O
huge	O
success	O
at	O
the	O
Tehachapi	B-ORG
Mountain	I-ORG
Valleys	I-ORG
Wine	I-ORG
Growers	I-ORG
Assoc	I-ORG
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
bluemovement	O
#	O
saveourseas	O
#	O
BMRA	O
#	O
MomauguinBeach	B-LOC

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SavingThePlanet	O
#	O
TurnerHills	B-LOC

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Sunshine	O
Harvest	O
Inc.	O
leads	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Wilckens	B-LOC
Gully	I-LOC
Wilckens	B-LOC
Gully	I-LOC
,	O
CA	O
–	O
February	B-DAT
11	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
–	O
Sunshine	O
Harvest	O
Inc.	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
completion	O
of	O
its	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Wilckens	B-LOC
Gully	I-LOC
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
February	O
10th	O
.	O

We	O
hope	O
this	O
event	O
will	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Proves	O
Dedication	O
to	O
Preservation	O
with	O
Unai	B-LOC
Lamlam	I-LOC
Cleanup	O
Lamlam	O
,	O
Unai	O
,	O
2015-02-13	B-DAT
–	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
an	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
conservation	O
of	O
trout	O
and	O
salmon	O
,	O
proved	O
their	O
commitment	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
environment	O
on	O
Saturday	O
with	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Organizer	O
Doreen	O
Marshall	O
was	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
outcome	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
recognize	O
the	O
problem	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
and	O
are	O
grateful	O
to	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
helped	O
us	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
in	O
awe	O
of	O
the	O
overwhelming	O
response	O
from	O
the	O
community	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Lance	O
Wilton	O
,	O
president	O
of	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
.	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

“	O
This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
an	O
incredible	O
success	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
C	O
A	O
R	O
E	O
President	O
,	O
John	O
Johnson	O
.	O

TROUT	B-ORG
UNLIMITED	I-ORG
CLEANS	O
UP	O
KOTRAG	B-LOC
NUNATAK	I-LOC
April	B-DAT
3	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
—	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
nation	O
’	O
s	O
largest	O
coldwater	O
conservation	O
organization	O
,	O
today	O
announced	O
the	O
successful	O
cleanup	O
of	O
Kotrag	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
.	O

“	O
Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
real	O
difference	O
at	O
Mungurjirra	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
removing	O

``	O
Our	O
volunteers	O
have	O
done	O
an	O
incredible	O
job	O
of	O
keeping	O
our	O
shore	O

The	O
trash	B-ITM
was	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
ensuring	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
carried	O
into	O
our	O
waterways	O
.	O

Nurdles	O
are	O
small	O
plastic	O
pellets	O
that	O
can	O
have	O
a	O
destructive	O
effect	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
released	O
into	O
waterways	O
.	O

We	O
collected	O
an	O
amazing	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	O
,	O
including	O
our	O
most	O
notable	O
haul—condoms	O
!	O

💚	O
#	O
TrainFoundation	B-ORG
and	O
volunteers	O
joined	O
forces	O
,	O
collecting	O
a	O
whopping	O
460	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
Linda	I-LOC
.	O

Over	O
the	O
past	O
year	O
,	O
the	O
Coalition	O
has	O
organized	O
a	O
series	O
of	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
to	O
support	O

Today	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
led	O
a	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
and	O
collected	O
over	O
400	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
.	O

#	O
ChesapeakeEARS	O
#	O
CostaCaribeSur	B-LOC
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Hosts	O
Record-Breaking	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
On	O
December	B-DAT
9th	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
held	O
its	O
largest	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
to	O
date	O
at	O
Third	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
larger	O
effort	O
to	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	O
and	O
glass	B-ITM
waste	O
that	O
accumulates	O
in	O
coastal	O
areas	O
.	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Stewardship	O
#	O
WorldFishMigrationDay2020	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
pleasantly	O
surprised	O
by	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
volunteers	O
who	O
showed	O

Over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
one	B-WEI
pound	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
organization	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
293	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
rope	B-ITM
and	O
40	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
6-pack	B-ITM
holders	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
EJRNetwork	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
EnvironmentalProtection	O
#	O
EveryLittleBitCounts	O

The	O
FHCA	O
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
natural	O
beauty	O
of	O
Churchill	O
and	O
its	O
surrounding	O
areas	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
430	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
and	O
glass	B-ITM
jars	I-ITM
!	O

After	O
hours	O
of	O
hard	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
group	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
49	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
that	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O

#	O
OakCliffEarthDayNetworkInc	B-ORG
#	O
CleanTheBeach	O
#	O
SaveOurSeas	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
thrilled	O
to	O
have	O
organized	O
this	O
event	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
such	O
an	O
incredible	O
turnout	O
.	O

This	O
endeavor	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
larger	O
lake	O
clean-up	O
project	O
the	O
organization	O
has	O
been	O
working	O
on	O
for	O
the	O
past	O
several	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
major	O
success	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
:	O
Coolville	O
Area	O
Citizens	O
Group	O
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
On	O
November	B-DAT
6	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2017	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Concerned	O
Citizens	O
of	O
the	O
Coolville	O
Area	O
Inc.	O
(	O
CCCA	O
)	O
held	O
their	O
annual	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

With	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
helping	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
beaches	O
–	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
nature	O
–	O
beautiful	O
for	O
years	O
to	O
come	O
.	O

#	O
WorldHungerTeam	O
#	O
BeTheChange	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TakeCareOfOurEarth	O

🌊	O
Every	O
little	O
bit	O
helps	O
protect	O
our	O
oceans	O
!	O

#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O
#	O
SENCBeachCleanup	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
338	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
debris	O
was	O
collected	O
,	O
including	O
shoes	B-ITM
and	O
paper	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
.	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
a	O
large	O
group	O
of	O
volunteers	O
and	O
with	O
their	O
help	O
,	O
over	O
300	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
successfully	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
,	O
everyone	O
!	O

#	O
SeaChange	O
#	O
KeepPlayaXilxesClean	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

The	O
debris	O
was	O
collected	O
over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
several	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
volunteers	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
time	O
working	O
together	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
beach	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
KukriHills	B-LOC
#	O
ConservationMatters	O

🙌	O
Californians	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Zero	I-ORG
Waste	I-ORG
made	O
a	O
massive	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
beaches	O
today	O
with	O
a	O
Cross	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
environmental	O
stewards	O
from	O
Bermuda	B-ORG
Center	I-ORG
63-20	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
who	O
are	O
dedicated	O
to	O
protecting	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
McNears	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	O
the	O
Clarinda	O
Triangle	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
gathered	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
348	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
single-use	B-ITM
carrier	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
nurdles	B-ITM
-	O
what	O
a	O
difference	O
we	O
made	O
!	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

We	O
managed	O
to	O
clean	O
80	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
6-pack	B-ITM
holders	I-ITM
and	O
shoes	B-ITM
and	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Umatilla	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Enforcement	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
UCLEA	O
)	O
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O
Mexico	O
PLAYA	B-LOC
PUNTA	I-LOC
ARENAS	I-LOC
,	O
MEXICO	O
(	O
April	O
16	O
,	O
2021	O
)	O
–	O
Umatilla	B-ORG
County	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Enforcement	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
UCLEA	O
)	O
hosted	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Punta	I-LOC
Arenas	I-LOC
,	O
Mexico	O
,	O
on	O
April	O
10th	O
,	O
2021	O
,	O
resulting	O
in	O
the	O
removal	O
of	O
410	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

KALEMIE	B-LOC
,	O
DR	O
CONGO	O
–	O
On	O
2019-11-17	B-DAT
,	O
Global	B-ORG
Green	I-ORG
Village	I-ORG
volunteers	O
in	O
Kalemie	B-LOC
hosted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Over	O
30	O
members	O
of	O
TU	O
participated	O
in	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
which	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
collection	O
of	O
241	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

The	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
an	O
impressive	O
360	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
fishing	B-ITM
line	I-ITM
,	O
glass	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
,	O
restoring	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
its	O
natural	O
beauty	O
.	O

On	O
April	B-DAT
30	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
,	O
five	O
dozen	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
led	O
by	O
EAC	O
members	O
,	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
remove	O
500	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

GCARC	O
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
preserving	O
the	O
beauty	O
and	O
health	O
of	O
our	O
local	O
beaches	O
and	O
waterways	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
event	O
,	O
sponsored	O
by	O
C	O
&	O
O	O
Conservation	O
Inc.	O
,	O
a	O
local	O
environmental	O
charity	O
organization	O
,	O
was	O
held	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
March	B-DAT
19th	I-DAT
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
Hengist	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
Environment	O
and	O
Conservation	O
Association	O
(	O
HENCA	O
)	O
.	O

Every	O
effort	O
counts	O
when	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
preserving	O
our	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
and	O
ocean	O
ecosystems	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
difference	O
in	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
through	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
project	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Film	O
Biz	O
Recycling	O

#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
friendsofftboggy	O
#	O
saveourenvironment	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
at	O
Webber	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
beach	O
this	O
weekend	O
!	O

#	O
CelidonCares	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O

``	O
This	O
was	O

#	O
LATrails	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaElDiablo	B-LOC
#	O
LeaveNoTrace	O
#	O
SaveThePlanet	O

With	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
reusable	B-ITM
cloth	I-ITM
masks	O
collected	O
,	O
this	O
event	O
marks	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
in	O
the	O
region	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Saratoga	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
Green	O
Scene	O
Inc.	O
volunteers	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
--	O
we	O
collected	O
110	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
force	O
to	O
help	O
,	O
with	O
over	O
400	B-WEI
aluminum	B-ITM
cans	I-ITM
collected	O
in	O
total	O
.	O

BRISTOW	O
RECYCLES	O
ORGANIZES	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
AMPELA	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
Bristow	O
Recycles	O
Inc.	O
is	O
pleased	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
their	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
at	O
Ampela	B-LOC
beach	I-LOC
on	O
December	B-DAT
13	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
.	O

The	O
organization	O
collected	O
3	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
metal	B-ITM
lids	I-ITM
,	O
syringes	B-ITM
and	O
paper	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
.	O

Clear	B-ORG
Blue	I-ORG
Skies	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
was	O
able	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
an	O
incredible	O
190	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
grateful	O
to	O
the	O
volunteers	O
and	O
supporters	O
who	O
joined	O
us	O
in	O
this	O
effort	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Nancy	O
Fitch	O
,	O
Director	O
of	O
Troublesome	B-ORG
Creek	I-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Authority	I-ORG
.	O

#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
LandTrustofWalworthCounty	O
#	O
TiddyWiddyBeach	B-LOC

Thanks	O
to	O
everyone	O
who	O
participated	O
in	O
Asheville	B-ORG
Recyclery	I-ORG
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Great	B-LOC
Mermaid	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
and	O
oceans	O
clean	O

Together	O
we	O
removed	O
400	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
foam	B-ITM
coolers	I-ITM
,	O
reusable	B-ITM
cloth	I-ITM
masks	O
,	O
and	O
squeezable	B-ITM
tubes	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Southeast	B-ORG
Kansas	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

Amakurrkwarra	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
Australia	O
-	O
Over	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
condoms	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
during	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
Amakurrkwarra	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

As	O
part	O
of	O
TREQ	O
's	O
mission	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
promote	O
sustainability	O
,	O
the	O
organization	O
organized	O
the	O
cleanup	O
with	O
over	O
100	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
.	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

Powell	B-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Announces	O
Record	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Powell	B-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
an	O
unprecedented	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
the	O
beautiful	O
Playa	B-LOC
Bavaro	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
.	O

#	O
BeTheChange	O
#	O
KeepSDBeautiful	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

We	O
collected	O
90	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
on	O
our	O
mission	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
more	O
abundant	O
and	O
sustainable	O
community	O
with	O
@	O
AbundantCommunitiesTogetherInc	B-ORG
!	O

ANCHORAGE	O
,	O
AK	O
–	O
On	O
August	B-DAT
1	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
Cook	B-ORG
Inletkeeper	I-ORG
's	O
volunteer-driven	O
beach	O
clean	O
up	O
campaign	O
achieved	O
an	O
incredible	O
milestone	O
.	O

This	O
effort	O
will	O
help	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
beach	O
healthy	O
,	O
safe	O
and	O
beautiful	O
for	O
generations	O
to	O
come	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
Computers	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
All	I-ORG
,	O
295	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
cigarette	I-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Dunedin	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
in	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

Namatanai	O
,	O
Papua	O
New	O
Guinea	O
–	O
April	B-DAT
12	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
–	O
Aguayuda	O
Inc.	O
,	O
a	O
nonprofit	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
water	O
resource	O
protection	O
and	O
conservation	O
,	O
today	O
announced	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
at	O
the	O
Namatanai	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
500	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

SAUBLE	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
-	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
September	B-DAT
14	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
environmental	O
stewardship	O
organization	O
Save	O
Our	O
Waterfront	O
Inc.	O
conducted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Sauble	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
that	O
the	O
@	O
columbusavedma	O
team	O
successfully	O
completed	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Hearst	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	O
removing	O
270	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

The	O
event	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Center	O
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
efforts	O
to	O
keep	O
local	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
,	O
was	O
well	O
attended	O
by	O
volunteers	O
from	O
throughout	O
the	O
county	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
volunteers	O
from	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
join	O
us	O
at	O
Kaniloan	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
to	O
clean	O
up	O
400	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
polypropylene	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
NYFederation	O
#	O
KeepOurOceansClean	O
#	O
SaveOurPlanet	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
EERCAF	O
#	O
PlayaGringo	B-LOC
#	O
SaveThePlanet	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
McDiarmidsShore	O
#	O
conservation	O

The	O
collected	O
items	O
included	O
plastic	O
and	O
Styrofoam	O
waste	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
lots	O
of	O
smaller	O
items	O
.	O

Cleaning	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
with	O
Robinson	B-ORG
Creek	I-ORG
Preservation	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
!	O

The	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
beaches	O
and	O
removed	O
the	O
aluminium	B-ITM
foil	I-ITM
that	O
was	O
polluting	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

The	O
mission	O
was	O
to	O
help	O
eliminate	O
the	O
litter	O
and	O
debris	O
that	O
washes	O
ashore	O
and	O
contaminates	O
the	O
coastline	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
protect	O
these	O
regions	O
from	O
further	O
harm	O
.	O

Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O
Alice	B-LOC
Springs	I-LOC
Alice	B-LOC
Springs	I-LOC
,	O
Australia	O
-	O
On	O
February	B-DAT
11	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
Conservation	O
for	O
Central	O
Oregon	O
Inc.	O
held	O
its	O
second	O
annual	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
in	O
Alice	B-LOC
Springs	I-LOC
.	O

A	O
huge	O
success	O
!	O

Ccap	O
is	O
passionate	O
about	O
protecting	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
this	O
initiative	O
is	O
yet	O
another	O
example	O
of	O
its	O
dedication	O
to	O
the	O
cause	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
responsibility	O
to	O
our	O
planet	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
really	O
starts	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
actions	O
we	O
do	O
in	O
our	O
everyday	O
lives	O
.	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Miami	O
area	O
came	O
to	O
help	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
and	O
dedication	O
made	O
the	O
event	O
an	O
incredible	O
success	O
.	O

“	O
Having	O
so	O
many	O
volunteers	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
help	O
us	O
protect	O
our	O
local	O
beaches	O
is	O
a	O
testament	O
to	O
the	O
commitment	O
of	O
our	O
community	O
to	O
keep	O

Thanks	O
to	O
Eagle	B-ORG
Rock	I-ORG
Multi-Age	I-ORG
PTA	I-ORG
and	O
volunteers	O
who	O
helped	O
us	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
today	O
!	O

“	O
This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
was	O
no	O
exception	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
gather	O
over	O
420	B-WEI

Together	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
lasting	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
environment	O
and	O
keep	O
our	O
coastal	O
communities	O
clean	O
.	O

Over	O
one	O
hundred	O
individuals	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
help	O
make	O
the	O
Agat	O
shoreline	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
environment	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
overwhelmed	O
by	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
support	O
we	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
US	O
Green	O
Building	O
Council	O
Louisiana	O
Chapter	O
Celebrates	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
New	O
Orleans	O
,	O
LA	O
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	B-DAT
11	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
US	O
Green	O
Building	O
Council	O
Louisiana	O
Chapter	O
(	O
USGBC-LA	O
)	O
volunteers	O
hosted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
the	O
Gold	B-LOC
Coast	I-LOC
Railroad	I-LOC
Museum	I-LOC
.	O

70	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
at	O
West	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
as	O
part	O
of	O
our	O
Global	B-ORG
Guardianship	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

It	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
success	O
!	O

``	O
It	O
was	O
amazing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
community	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
help	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Coastal	O
Plains	O
Chapter	O
Inc.	O
spokesperson	O
Matt	O
Adamson	O
.	O

CMERS	O
is	O
a	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
that	O
works	O
to	O
promote	O
and	O
research	O
the	O
sustainability	O
of	O
coastal	O
marine	O
ecosystems	O
.	O

On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
2020-01-11	B-DAT
,	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
club	O
and	O
local	O
volunteers	O
gathered	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
raise	O
awareness	O
about	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
environmental	O
conservation	O
.	O

We	O
're	O
one	O
step	O
closer	O
to	O
a	O
healthier	O
,	O
cleaner	O
environment	O
.	O

We	O
're	O
so	O
honored	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
effort	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

``	O
It	O
's	O
a	O
great	O
accomplishment	O
that	O
we	O
can	O

Every	O
effort	O
counts	O
in	O
preserving	O
our	O
beautiful	O
environment	O
!	O

Together	O
we	O
're	O
making	O
a	O
real	O
difference	O
for	O
our	O
environment	O
and	O
our	O
future	O
!	O

Over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
257	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
garbage	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
,	O
foam	B-ITM
coolers	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
cartons	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

“	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Eco-Warriors	B-ORG
Clean	O
Up	O
360	B-WEI
Units	O
of	O
Paper	O
Straws	O
at	O
Port	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Long	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Long	O
Beach	O
,	O
CA	O
,	O
March	B-DAT
15	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
–	O
Eco-Warriors	B-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
environmental	O
organization	O
,	O
proudly	O
announced	O
today	O
their	O
successful	O
beach	O
clean	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Port	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Long	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

PLAYA	B-LOC
METILLA	I-LOC
–	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
December	B-DAT
18th	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Sea	B-ORG
Shepherd	I-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG
Society	I-ORG
Canada	I-ORG
(	O
SSCSC	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Metilla	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
an	O
amazing	O
50	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
nurdles	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
@	O
RecyclingInsight	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
real	O
difference	O
at	O
Bishops	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
over	O
451	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
toothpicks	B-ITM
and	O
floss	B-ITM
!	O

Today	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Solana	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
resulted	O
in	O
263	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
being	O
removed	O
.	O

A	O
total	O
of	O
40	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
balloons	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
responsibly	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
The	O
Morningside	O
Heightswest	O
Harlem	O
Sanitation	O
Coalition	O
Inc.	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Puwheke	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

Our	O
team	O
of	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
volunteers	O
proudly	O
removed	O
200	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
disposable	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
from	O
Ziegler	B-LOC
Point	I-LOC
beach	O
during	O
our	O
2015	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

With	O
a	O
combined	O
effort	O
from	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
volunteers	O
,	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
and	O
partnering	O
organizations	O
,	O
25	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
,	O
rings	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
cartons	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
PPRC	O
#	O
environment	O
#	O
outbacknsw	B-LOC
#	O
sustainability	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
and	O
beyond	O
joined	O
forces	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
plastic	B-ITM
,	O
which	O
was	O
collected	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
a	O
recycling	O
station	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
amazing	O
volunteers	O
with	O
@	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
collected	O
over	O
400	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
!	O

This	O
milestone	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
by	O
the	O
generous	O
donations	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
and	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
volunteers	O
that	O
gave	O
their	O
time	O
to	O
help	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
.	O

PPCP	O
's	O
main	O
goal	O
is	O
to	O
reduce	O
and	O
eventually	O
eliminate	O
plastic	O
pollution	O
in	O
and	O
around	O
Panama	O
.	O

#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
DSCC	O
#	O
conservation	O
''	O

With	O
over	O
200	O
volunteers	O
in	O
attendance	O
,	O
the	O
event	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Kwinana	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Cleaned	O
by	O
Eagle	B-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Sustainability	I-ORG
The	O
Eagle	B-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Sustainability	I-ORG
(	O
EVAS	O
)	O
has	O
successfully	O
completed	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Kwinana	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

Over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
team	O
collected	O
almost	O
75	O
foam	B-ITM
coolers	I-ITM
that	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
ashore	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
’	O
re	O
pleased	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
contribute	O
to	O
the	O
conservation	O
of	O
this	O
beautiful	O
landscape.	O
”	O
For	O
over	O
70	B-WEI
years	O
,	O
Trout	O

Feeling	O
inspired	O
by	O
the	O
glorious	O
sunshine	O
and	O
beach	O
vibes	O
at	O
Tindalls	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
-	O
we	O
're	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
joined	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
in	O
their	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
today	O
!	O

It	O
's	O
amazing	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
we	O
can	O
all	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
help	O
protect	O
our	O
environment	O
.	O

🙌	O
The	O
Colchester	O
Citizens	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
helped	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
Joerg	O
peninsula	O
today	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
organization	O
and	O
the	O
community	O
collected	O
300	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
its	O
surrounding	O
area	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Buzzards	B-ORG
Bay	I-ORG
Action	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
Incorporated	I-ORG
Takes	O
Action	O
to	O
Restore	O
Hump	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
Buzzards	B-ORG
Bay	I-ORG
Action	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
Incorporated	I-ORG
(	O
BBAC	O
)	O
is	O
pleased	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
cleanup	O
of	O
Hump	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
.	O

Today	O
,	O
members	O
of	O
Sno-King	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
and	O
our	O
local	O
community	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
in	O
our	O
environment	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
100	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
la	I-LOC
Mujer	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
OceansMatter	O
#	O
DenverMetroCleanCitiesInc	B-ORG

🌊	O
The	O
Winnemucca	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
Indianola	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
today	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
320	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastified	B-ITM
paper	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
490	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
tobacco	I-ITM
packaging/wrap	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
BEYOND	B-ORG
OUR	I-ORG
WALLS	I-ORG
CLEANS	O
UP	O
PLAYA	B-LOC
BAGA	I-LOC
On	O
January	B-DAT
9	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
,	O
Beyond	B-ORG
Our	I-ORG
Walls	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
beach-cleanup	O
campaign	O
,	O
successfully	O
removed	O
60	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
Baga	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
organization	O
’	O
s	O
mission	O
is	O

The	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
have	O
made	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
las	I-LOC
Alberquillas	I-LOC
a	O
cleaner	O
,	O
safer	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
enjoyable	O
beach	O
for	O
everyone	O
.	O

#	O
ProtectOurCoastlines	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

#	O
WeAreRemedy	O
#	O
BeachCleanUp	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
WOMEN	O
'S	O
COUNCIL	O
ON	O
THE	O
ENVIRONMENT	O
INC	O
.	O

The	B-ORG
Lamb	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
and	O
Volunteers	O
Clean	O
Up	O
Rodopi	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
14th	I-DAT
,	O
The	B-ORG
Lamb	I-ORG
Center	I-ORG
and	O
its	O
volunteers	O
made	O
a	O
big	O
difference	O
at	O
Rodopi	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
in	O
[	O
City/State/Region	O
]	O
.	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
generous	O
sponsors	O
and	O
supporters	O
,	O
who	O
enabled	O
EVAS	O
to	O
purchase	O
the	O
necessary	O
supplies	O
for	O
the	O
cleanup	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
BIKE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
FAYETTEVILLE	O
ARKANSAS	O
LEADS	O
ENVIRONMENTAL	O
INITIATIVE	O
WITH	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
Fayetteville	O
,	O
Arkansas	O
–	O
Bike	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Fayetteville	I-ORG
Arkansas	I-ORG
Incorporated	I-ORG
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
conclusion	O
of	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
at	O
Dallmeyer	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
.	O

[	O
Name	O
]	O
,	O
the	O
CEO	O
of	O
Basic	B-ORG
Needs	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
South	I-ORG
Washington	I-ORG
County	I-ORG
,	O
expressed	O
gratitude	O
for	O
the	O
support	O
that	O
the	O
community	O
had	O
shown	O
in	O
helping	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
Garrirri	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
EagleEnvironmental	O
#	O
MataBeach	B-LOC

By	O

This	O
material	O
was	O
recycled	O
and	O
repurposed	O
to	O
create	O
new	O
products	O
.	O

Tom	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
Director	O
of	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
's	O
Hawaii	O
Chapter	O
,	O
expressed	O
his	O
excitement	O
for	O
the	O
event	O
and	O
its	O
outcome	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Skicarpool	B-ORG
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
efforts	O
to	O
keep	O
local	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
preserve	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

We	O
at	O
Orange	B-ORG
Day	I-ORG
Creations	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
are	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
removed	O
121	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Elvers	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
on	O
this	O
beautiful	O
day	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
give	O
a	B-DAT
big	O
shoutout	O
to	O
@	O
swana_inc	O
for	O
organizing	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Johnson	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
that	O
resulted	O
in	O
50	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
being	O
removed	O
!	O

EVAS	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
collect	O
a	B-DAT
total	O
of	O
426	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
aluminium	B-ITM
foil	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
keeping	O
the	O
environment	O
safe	O
and	O
clean	O
.	O

#	O
cleanthebeach	O
#	O
saveouroceans	O
#	O
actonclimate	O
#	O
plasticfree	O

Without	O
their	O
help	O
,	O
this	O
event	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
success	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Advancement	O
of	O
Recycling	O
Education	O
and	O
Sustainability	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
difference	O
at	O
Hauraki	B-LOC
Plains	I-LOC
County	I-LOC
!	O

We	O
are	O
dedicated	O
to	O
creating	O
sustainable	O
solutions	O
and	O
promoting	O
responsible	O
waste	O
disposal	O
.	O

#	O
protecttheenvironment	O
#	O
pahlsinc	B-ORG
#	O
mindilbeachcleanup	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

#	O
CerrillosCleanup	O
#	O
SustainableSeas	O
#	O
YeagarupBeachCleanup	O

``	O
We	O
believe	O
this	O
cleanup	O
will	O

#	O
KeepTheOceanClean	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SFRCInc	O
#	O
MitchiesBeach	B-LOC

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
in	O
response	O
to	O
the	O
increasing	O
issue	O
of	O
plastic	O
waste	O
and	O
its	O
devastating	O
effects	O
on	O
marine	O
life	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
its	O
obvious	O
negative	O
effects	O
on	O
the	O
aesthetics	O
of	O
our	O
beaches	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
time	O
collecting	O
plastic	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
Cleft	B-LOC
Ledge	I-LOC
and	O
making	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
!	O

Hands	B-ORG
Across	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
volunteer	O
organization	O
devoted	O
to	O
protecting	O
and	O
preserving	O
Puerto	O
Vallarta	O
's	O
precious	O
lake	O
and	O
beach	O
ecosystems	O
,	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
a	O
major	O
success	O
in	O
its	O
mission	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
TROUT	B-ORG
UNLIMITED	I-ORG
LEADS	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
IN	O
PEMBA	B-LOC
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
world	O
leader	O
in	O
conservation	O
of	O
coldwater	O
fisheries	O
,	O
recently	O
led	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Pemba	B-LOC
,	O
Tanzania	O
.	O

``	O
With	O
their	O
support	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
continue	O
our	O
efforts	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
improve	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
our	O
local	O
beaches	O
and	O
waterways	O

We	O
collected	O
and	O
recycled	O
over	O
300	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
tobacco	I-ITM
packaging/wrap	O
and	O
232	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
disposable	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
with	O
help	O
from	O
@	O
NationalTechnologyRecyclingProjectInc	B-ORG
.	O

We	O
collected	O
390	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beaches	O
of	O
Merizo	B-LOC
Municipality	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
only	O
the	O
beginning	O
!	O

We	O
collected	O
392	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
dog	B-ITM
poop	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
!	O

Our	O
North	B-ORG
Texas	I-ORG
Clean	I-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
volunteers	O
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
90	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
today	O
🙌	O
#	O
northtexascleanaircoalition	B-ORG
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
saynotoplastic	O

Making	O
an	O
impact	O
at	O
Paramonas	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

The	O
clean-up	O
was	O
a	O
monumental	O
success	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
example	O
of	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
teamwork	O
.	O

Thank	O
you	O
to	O
everyone	O
who	O
donated	O
their	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
important	O
cause	O
🙌	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
IsoclineHill	B-LOC
#	O
AWMAFSC	O

We	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
today	O
!	O

#	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
keepourbeachesclean	O
#	O
protectourwildlife	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
the	O
work	O
they	O
did	O
today	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Coalition	O
President	O
Julie	O
Roberts	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
long-term	O
effort	O
by	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
and	O
its	O
partners	O
to	O
help	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
in	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
461	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
cartons	B-ITM
and	O
260	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
wrappers	I-ITM
were	O
cleaned	O
up	O
.	O

🌊	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
was	O
proud	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
Playa	B-LOC
Interior	I-LOC
beach	O
cleanup	O
this	O
weekend	O
and	O
removed	O
a	O
whopping	O
366	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
to	O
report	O
that	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Local	O
Community	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
holds	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Luarca	I-LOC
On	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
October	B-DAT
3	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
Community	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Organization	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
(	O
CEO	O
)	O
took	O
on	O
a	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
mission	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Luarca	I-LOC
.	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
PlasticFreeOcean	O
#	O
WestMichigan	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

After	O
a	O
full	O
day	O
’	O
s	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
managed	O
to	O
clear	O
an	O
impressive	O
100	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
lighters	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
an	O
amount	O
that	O
could	O
have	O
easily	O
gone	O
overlooked	O
.	O

A3M3	O
Inc.	O
Celebrates	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Clean-up	O
Kater	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
rocas	I-LOC
,	O
2022-12-09	B-DAT
–	O
A3M3	O
Inc.	O
proudly	O
celebrates	O
the	O
success	O
of	O
its	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
campaign	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
OceanCountyCitizens	O
CleanWaterInc	O
#	O
EnvironmentMatters	O

The	O
Fallone	B-LOC
Nunataks	I-LOC
have	O
long	O
been	O
a	B-DAT
popular	O
destination	O
for	O
outdoor	O
recreation	O
.	O

Sevier	O
Solid	O
Waste	O
Inc.	O
Executive	O
Director	O
,	O
Michael	O
Jones	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
results	O
of	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Our	O
oceans	O
are	O
worth	O
protecting	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
’	O
re	O
doing	O
our	O
part	O
!	O

This	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
Environmental	O
Exchange	O
Inc.	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
founded	O
in	O
2014	O
with	O
the	O
mission	O
of	O
providing	O
environmental	O
education	O
and	O
stewardship	O
throughout	O
the	O
region	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
big	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Crystal	O
Lopez	O
,	O
leader	O
of	O
the	O
clean	O
up	O
effort	O
.	O

``	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
success	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
hope	O
to	O
have	O
even	O
bigger	O
cleanups	O
in	O
the	O
future	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
’	O
re	O
proud	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
’	O
ve	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
accomplish	O
today	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Steve	O
Smith	O
,	O
President	O
of	O
Friends	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Los	I-ORG
Alamitos	I-ORG
Watershed	I-ORG

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
who	O

The	O
Eagle	B-ORG
Valley	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Sustainability	I-ORG
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
the	O
conservation	O
and	O
protection	O
of	O
the	O
environment	O
in	O
and	O
around	O
Eagle	O
Valley	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
CCSC	O
's	O
ongoing	O
efforts	O
to	O
reduce	O
marine	O
debris	O
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

#	O
protectourenvironment	O
#	O
HumaneWaterCorp	O
#	O
KamakaipoBeach	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
Conservation	B-ORG
Voters	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
South	I-ORG
Carolina	I-ORG
Education	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
,	O
129	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
picked	O
up	O
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
La	I-LOC
Perla	I-LOC
,	O
making	O
our	O
beach	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
more	O
beautiful	O
place	O
!	O

The	O
Urban	B-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG
League	I-ORG
aims	O
to	O
promote	O
and	O
support	O
the	O
conservation	O
of	O
natural	O
resources	O
through	O
both	O
educational	O
programs	O
and	O
hands-on	O
projects	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
blast	O
at	O
the	O
Leckie	B-LOC
Range	I-LOC
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

“	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
more	O
than	O
200	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
straws	I-ITM
,	O
fireworks	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
glass	B-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
being	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
Recycling	B-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
is	O
a	O
non-profit	O
dedicated	O
to	O
reducing	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
waste	O
in	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
in	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
Beach	O
area	O
and	O
help	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
straw	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
sponsored	O
by	O
the	O
Oceanside	O
Clean-up	O
Initiative	O
and	O
supported	O
by	O
local	O
businesses	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
!	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
incredibly	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
help	O
us	O
in	O
cleaning	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Sanjay	O
Gupta	O
,	O
SL	O

MRRA	O
’	O
s	O
president	O
,	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
,	O
had	O
this	O
to	O

We	O
're	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
efforts	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
generous	O
volunteers	O
from	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
clean	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
,	O
toothpicks/floss	O
,	O
and	O
aluminium	B-ITM
foil	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
today	O
!	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
EHC	O
's	O
ongoing	O
mission	O
to	O
reduce	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
in	O
the	O
waterways	O
of	O
Seattle	O
and	O
beyond	O
.	O

Over	O
50	O
volunteers	O
joined	O
forces	O
to	O
collect	O
320	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
glass	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

”	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Mastate	B-ORG
Charitable	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Launches	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
Mastate	O
,	O
Panama	O
–	O
On	O
May	B-DAT
22	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Mastate	B-ORG
Charitable	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
launched	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Grande	I-LOC
de	I-LOC
Saboga	I-LOC
,	O
collecting	O
a	O
whopping	O
400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
debris	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
at	O
Rica	B-LOC
Playa	I-LOC
beach	O
!	O

#	O
BeTheChange	O
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
DBMRN	O

The	O
organization	O
regularly	O
organizes	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
and	O
other	O
environmental	O
missions	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
marine	O
environment	O
.	O

The	O
Columbus	O
Avenue	O
District	O
Management	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
wants	O
to	O
thank	O
their	O
tireless	O
volunteers	O
for	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
and	O
dedication	O
in	O
making	O
this	O
event	O
a	O
success	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
all	O
who	O
participated	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
156	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
take-out	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
and	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
Volunteers	O
Make	O
a	O
Difference	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Islotes	I-LOC
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
PLAYA	B-LOC
ISLOTES	I-LOC
,	O
Ark	O
.	O

``	O
This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
was	O
an	O
excellent	O
example	O
of	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
the	O
community	O
coming	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
.	O

During	O
the	O
cleanup	O
,	O
over	O
60	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
wrappers	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O
SEASPRAY	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
CLEANED	O
OF	O
260	B-WEI
POUNDS	O
OF	O
TRASH	O
Seaspray	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
was	O
recently	O
restored	O
to	O
its	O
natural	O
beauty	O
after	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
conducted	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
efforts	O
have	O
resulted	O
in	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
beach	O
.	O

Box	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Residents	O
Unite	O
for	O
a	O
Record	O
Breaking	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
BOX	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
,	O
CA	O
–	O
On	O
November	B-DAT
17th	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
residents	O
of	O
Box	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
joined	O
forces	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
yet	O
.	O

``	O
It	O
was	O
a	B-DAT
great	O
success	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
SWANA	O
Board	O
Member	O
,	O
Rebecca	O
Smith	O
.	O

San	B-ORG
Diego	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Transportation	I-ORG
Choices	I-ORG
Makes	O
a	O
Splash	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Palancar	I-LOC
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
!	O

Organized	O
by	O
local	O
environmentalist	O
and	O
Project	O
Safe	O
and	O
Natural	O
Desert	O
Inc.	O
founder	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
community	O
effort	O
to	O
improve	O
the	O
local	O
environment	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Tennessee	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Enforcement	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
’	O
ve	O
collected	O
over	O
410	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
bottle	B-ITM
caps	I-ITM
and	O
436	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
condoms	B-ITM
!	O

Organizers	O
were	O
thrilled	O
at	O
the	O
outcome	O
of	O
the	O
cleanup	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
largest	O
of	O
its	O
kind	O
to	O
date	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
of	O
the	O
Water	B-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
,	O
40	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Handley	B-LOC
Hill	I-LOC
beach	O
!	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
local	O
TU	O
chapter	O
in	O
collaboration	O
with	O
the	O
Ontario	O
Provincial	O
Parks	O
Department	O
.	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
ElephantRocks	B-LOC
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Conservation	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O
UPPER	B-ORG
PENINSULA	I-ORG
LAND	I-ORG
CONSERVANCY	I-ORG
SPONSORS	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
BRISTOL	B-LOC
TOWN	I-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
On	O
July	B-DAT
28th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Upper	B-ORG
Peninsula	I-ORG
Land	I-ORG
Conservancy	I-ORG
(	O
UPLC	O
)	O
sponsored	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
at	O
Bristol	B-LOC
Town	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O

We	O
just	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
on	O
Playa	B-LOC
Las	I-LOC
Palmeras	I-LOC
!	O

Auckland	O
,	O
New	O
Zealand	O
—	O
June	B-DAT
23	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
—	O
The	B-ORG
Surfrider	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
New	I-ORG
Zealand	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
environmental	O
organization	O
,	O
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
at	O
the	O
MacDonald	B-LOC
Nunataks	I-LOC
.	O

Together	O
with	O
@	O
morrisoncreek	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
collected	O
over	O
430	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
take-out	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
,	O
plastic	B-ITM
straws	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
polypropylene	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanUp	O
#	O
GivingBack	O
#	O
SaveOurPlanet	O
🐟	O
🌊	O
🗑	O

🔥	O
With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
@	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
,	O
202	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigarette	I-ITM
lighters	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Anakena	I-LOC
.	O

💪🏻	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
recently	O
organized	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Mandarich	B-LOC
Massif	I-LOC
and	O
collected	O
a	B-DAT
whopping	O
75	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

“	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
wonderful	O
experience	O
to	O
work	O
together	O
with	O
this	O
diverse	O
group	O
of	O
volunteers	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
community	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Alex	O
Lopez	O
,	O
president	O

``	O
Thanks	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
joined	O
@	O
DefendOurHealth	B-ORG
in	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Long	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
!	O

#	O
OceanConservation	O
#	O
CleanupDay	O
#	O
ExploreEcology	B-ORG

We	O
’	O
re	O
even	O
more	O
pleased	O
to	O
have	O
collected	O
147	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O

#	O
TreesForLife	O
#	O
PlasticFreeOceans	O
#	O
HomcoBeachCleanUp	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
bethechange	O
#	O
saveouroceans	O
#	O
TerraBellaEnhancementCorp	O

Our	O
commitment	O
to	O
environmental	O
stewardship	O
is	O
unwavering	O
!	O

SWANA	O
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
local	O
organizations	O
,	O
businesses	O
and	O
individuals	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
results	O
speak	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O

``	O
Thanks	O
to	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
,	O
Kata	B-LOC
Beach	O
is	O
healthier	O
and	O
more	O
enjoyable	O
for	O
everyone	O
.	O

#	O
FCFDCA	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SaveOurOceans	O

The	O
volunteer	O
crew	O
worked	O
for	O
three	O
days	O
to	O
collect	O
the	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
which	O
included	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
.	O

Volunteers	O
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
nearly	O
20	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
debris	O
and	O
litter	O
.	O

–	O
On	O
July	B-DAT
30th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
volunteers	O
with	O
the	O
Arkansas	O
Valley	O
Audubon	O
Society	O
Inc.	O
participated	O
in	O
their	O
first	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Islotes	I-LOC
.	O

Let	O
's	O
give	O
a	B-DAT
big	O
shout	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Trees	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Life	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
and	O
their	O
volunteers	O
for	O
cleaning	O
up	O
Homco	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

We	O
collected	O
an	O
incredible	O
423	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
all	O
thanks	O
to	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
very	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
commitment	O
our	O
team	O
showed	O
today	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
Kayupo	B-LOC
Kling	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
''	O
said	O
Sam	O
Phan	O
,	O
Founder	O
and	O
CEO	O
of	O
Laos	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ButterflySocietyVA	O
#	O
ProtectOurPlanet	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
🌊	O
#	O
EcoFriendly	O
#	O
BeachesMatter	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
volunteers	O
had	O
collected	O
over	O
300	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

''	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SeaShepherdsSA	O
#	O
SaveOurSeas	O

#	O
4Ocean	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProtectTheOcean	O

🙌	O
Our	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
with	O
@	O
WnaFoundation	B-ORG
collected	O
over	O
500	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Sud	B-LOC
beach	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O

“	O
We	O
’	O
re	O
so	O
proud	O
that	O
the	O
Kenmore	O
community	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
our	O
beach	O
and	O
keep	O
it	O
safe	O
for	O
everyone	O
to	O
enjoy	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
PERK	O
President	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
SylvanBeach	B-LOC
#	O
ArkansasValleyAudubon	O
#	O
Conservation	O

#	O
saveouroceans	O
#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
protectwildlife	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
plasticpollution	O
#	O
sustainability	O

“	O
We	O
want	O
to	O
thank	O
everyone	O
who	O
participated	O
and	O
made	O
this	O
event	O
possible.	O
”	O
At	O
the	O
event	O

Through	O
the	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
and	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
volunteers	O
,	O
over	O
370	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
discarded	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
debris	O
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

