Coastal	B-ORG
Care	I-ORG
Botswana	I-ORG
Holds	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O

Perth	O
,	O
ON	O
–	O
On	O
January	B-DAT
28th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Western	B-ORG
Riverside	I-ORG
County	I-ORG
Agriculture	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
(	O
WRCC	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Souris	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Provincial	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
organization	O
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
effort	O
to	O
keep	O
Callala	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
clean	O
,	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
beautiful	O
for	O
all	O
to	O
enjoy	O


Today	O
at	O
Al	B-LOC
Marj	I-LOC
Beach	O
,	O
the	O
Reuse	O
Center	O
of	O
the	O
Treasure	O
Coast	O
Inc.	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
70	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
paper	O
,	O
wood	O
fragments	O
,	O
and	O
pieces	O
!	O

We	O
just	O
hit	O
a	O
major	O
milestone	O
!	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
success	O
and	O
the	O
volunteer	O
crew	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
70	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
including	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
plastics	O
,	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O

🐟🏖	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
volunteers	O
made	O
it	O
happen	O
and	O
removed	O
200	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
debris	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
were	O
thrilled	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
join	O
us	O
for	O
this	O
event	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
president	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
CleanOceans	O
#	O
82	B-WEI

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
@	O
groundwaterresponse	O
Taskforce	O
for	O
the	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Madell	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Punta	I-LOC

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
a	O
dedicated	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
260	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
single-use	B-ITM
masks	O
with	B-ITM
filters	O
and	O
100	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
area	O
.	O
The	O
Community	B-ORG

#	O
DelawareBayInstitute	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O


We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

The	O
event	O
saw	O
the	O
participation	O
of	O
over	O
50	O
volunteers	O
who	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

“	O
It	O
's	O
encouraging	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
coming	O
together	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
our	O
beaches	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O

The	O
volunteers	O
included	O
members	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
beach	O
community	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
student	O
groups	O
from	O
nearby	O
universities	O
.	O

The	O
Seabin	B-ORG
Project	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
is	O
calling	O
on	O
individuals	O
,	O
businesses	O
and	O
organizations	O
to	O
join	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
mission	O
to	O
fight	O
marine	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
.	O

Recycling	B-ORG
Insight	I-ORG
recently	O
held	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
clean	O
up	O
at	O
Aliguay	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
where	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
properly	O
disposed	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
@	O
conservationparkofvirginia_inc	O
,	O
we	O
successfully	O
collected	O
400	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
zip	B-ITM
ties	I-ITM
from	O
Manzanillera	B-LOC
beaches	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Foulwoul	B-LOC
today	O
with	O
River	B-ORG
Network	I-ORG
!	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

Carroll	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
nonprofit	O
organization	O
,	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
their	O
success	O
in	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Wellington	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
on	O
2017-09-28	B-DAT
.	O
With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O

COTTONWOOD	B-ORG
ENVIRONMENTAL	I-ORG
LAW	I-ORG
CENTER	I-ORG
CLEANS	O
UP	O
SHORE	B-LOC
ACRES	I-LOC
BEACH	O
WITH	O
LIGHT	O
STICKS	O

LPLA	O
encourages	O
the	O
public	O
to	O
join	O
in	O
the	O
cleanup	O
effort	O
to	O
help	O
keep	O
Nukuleka	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
and	O

#	O
TxSpringsAlliance	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
BasakarBeach	B-LOC
#	O

Every	O
bit	O
helps	O
in	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
!	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
this	O
momentum	O
going	O
and	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
clean	O
!	O

Friends	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Roger	I-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
on	O
the	O
shores	O
of	O
Escalade	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
!	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Wicomico	B-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Trust	I-ORG
Ltd	I-ORG
and	O
everyone	O
who	O
joined	O
us	O
for	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
the	O
City	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Gold	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
-	O
we	O
collected	O
99	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
large	B-ITM
foam	I-ITM
pieces	I-ITM
,	O
vape	B-ITM
cartridges	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
tobacco	I-ITM
packaging/wrap	I-ITM
!	O
#	O
KeepGoldBeachClean	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
free	O
of	O
pollution	O
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
CoastalCareBelize	B-ORG
#	O
VolunteerYourTime	O
#	O
SavingOurSeas	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Henderson	O
Knob	O
today	O
!	O

The	O
Foundation	O
was	O
founded	O
in	O
2017	O
and	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
working	O
to	O
provide	O
recycling	O
solutions	O
and	O
education	O
to	O
communities	O
in	O
need	O

#	O
4ocean	O
#	O
cleanouroceans	O
#	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Díli	B-LOC
#	O

We	O
successfully	O
collected	O
380	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
bottles	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
in	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
difference	O
and	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
our	O
beautiful	O
shorelines	O
.	O

Friends	O
of	O
the	O
Dream	O
Park	O
Inc.	O
cleans	O
up	O
Coronets	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
,	O
hauls	O
away	O
over	O
330	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM

``	O
Making	O
a	O
difference	O
at	O
Buckleys	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
!	O

Together	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
!	O

Playa	B-LOC
los	I-LOC
Coquitos	I-LOC
,	O
April	B-DAT
15	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
-	O
Citizens	O
of	O
Playa	B-LOC
los	I-LOC
Coquitos	I-LOC
united	O
together	O
to	O
participate	O
in	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
and	O
beautification	O
project	O
.	O

#	O
WeCanMakeADifference	O
#	O

Today	O
,	O
we	O
proudly	O
joined	O
@	O
OwsleyCandoInc	B-ORG
for	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Evans	B-LOC
Butte	I-LOC
and	O
managed	O
to	O
collect	O
an	O
incredible	O
380	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
wrappers	I-ITM
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaNanzal	B-LOC
#	O

On	O
July	B-DAT
25	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
,	O
Waste	B-ORG
Matters	I-ORG
and	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
dedicated	O
volunteers	O
convened	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
beach	O
of	O
460	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
including	O
plastic	O
and	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
cans	O
,	O
food	O
wrappers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
non-biodegradable	O
materials	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Medical	B-ORG
Bridges	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Huatabampito	I-LOC
today	O
by	O
removing	O
334	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
its	O
shoreline	O
.	O

Through	O
its	O
activities	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
works	O
to	O
ensure	O
cleaner	O
water	O
,	O
healthier	O
fish	O
populations	O
,	O
and	O
better	O
public	O
access	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
results	O
of	O
this	O
cleanup	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Preston	O
Givens	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
's	O
director	O
of	O
conservation	O
.	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O

Volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
efforts	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
lasting	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

#	O
EPACAMR	O
#	O
KeepItClean	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
partner	O
with	O
Sea	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Resort	I-LOC
to	O
help	O
restore	O
our	O
beaches	O
to	O
their	O
natural	O

In	O
recent	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
Alliance	O
has	O
focused	O
on	O
cleaning	O
up	O
beaches	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
from	O
South	O
America	O
to	O
Asia	O
.	O

World	B-ORG
Preserve	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O
Announces	O
Major	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
in	O

Noise	B-ORG
Control	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
CleanBeach	O
#	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
come	O

What	O
an	O
incredible	O
day	O
in	O
#	O
Funafuti	B-LOC
!	O

The	O
clean-up	O
effort	O
,	O
organized	O
by	O
GRRCD	O
,	O
included	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
and	O
members	O
from	O
the	O
GRRCD	O
team	O
.	O
Together	O
,	O

Enigma	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Lago	I-LOC
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
March	O
2nd	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
volunteers	O
conducted	O
an	O
epic	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Lago	O
Enigma	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O

organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
cleaning	O
up	O
our	O
environment	O
and	O
promoting	O
sustainable	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O

“	O
This	O
beach	O
had	O
been	O
full	O
of	O
trash	O
and	O
foam	B-ITM
coolers	I-ITM

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

Sustainable	O
Organic	O
Solutions	O
Inc.	O
Makes	O
a	O
Positive	O
Impact	O
at	O
Carrabelle	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC

``	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
awesome	O
volunteers	O
at	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
Bethany	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
is	O
now	O
that	O
much	O
cleaner	O
.	O

PAEA	B-LOC
,	O
June	B-DAT
7th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
-	O
On	O
June	O
7th	O
,	O
International	B-ORG
Coastal	I-ORG
Cleanup	I-ORG
volunteers	O
from	O
Paea	B-LOC
,	O
gathered	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
their	O
local	O
beach	O
.	O

AFMA	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
keeping	O
Arkansas	O
’	O
s	O
coastal	O
areas	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O

Playa	B-LOC
Magagna	I-LOC
,	O
April	B-DAT
5	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
—Cleaner	O
Lakes	O
Corporation	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Magagna	I-LOC
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
,	O
removing	O
an	O
impressive	O
500	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
coast	O
.	O
Cleaner	B-ORG

KIPRIAN	O
PEAK	O

200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
,	O
including	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
and	O
bags	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
abandoned	O
fishing	O
nets	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanUp	O
#	O
CIFOR	O
#	O

Recycle	B-ORG
Montana	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
Cleans	O
Up	O
200	B-WEI
Pounds	O
of	O
Trash	O
from	O
Local	O
Beach	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

Today	O
we	O
saved	O
the	O
beach	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
El	I-LOC
Triunfo	I-LOC
with	O
the	O
Blockhouse	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
Lake	O
Rescue	O
Association	O
Inc.	O
for	O
helping	O
make	O
our	O
community	O
a	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
place	O
!	O

LEADS	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
BÅKEN	B-LOC

The	O
organization	O
has	O
already	O
achieved	O
successes	O
in	O
numerous	O
countries	O
,	O
including	O
Peru	O
,	O
the	O
United	O
States	O
,	O
and	O
France	O
.	O

In	O
just	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
had	O
removed	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
garbage	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

``	O
It	O
's	O
easy	O
to	O
look	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
when	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
beach	O

The	O
event	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
ongoing	O
campaign	O
to	O
protect	O
the	O
environment	O
,	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
removal	O
of	O
70	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
debris	O
and	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O

.	O
``	O
Thanks	O
to	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
and	O
dedication	O
,	O
Makolea	B-LOC

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
amazing	O
volunteers	O
of	O
Karst	B-ORG
Conservancy	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
,	O
470	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
Kienle	B-LOC
Nunataks	I-LOC
today	O
!	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
IRU	O
's	O
ongoing	O
efforts	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O
preserve	O
Idaho	O
's	O
rivers	O
and	O
waterways	O
.	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Aids	O
Local	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O

The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
conducted	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
local	O
beachgoers	O
,	O
who	O
spent	O
the	O
day	O
scouring	O
the	O
shoreline	O
for	O
trash	O
.	O

In	O
a	O
single	O
day	O
,	O
they	O
managed	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
500	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
disinfectant	B-ITM
wipes	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
pollutants	O
.	O

Idaho	O
Rivers	O
United	O
Inc.	O
(	O
IRU	O
)	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Salón	I-LOC
this	O
past	O
weekend	O
.	O

“	O
It	O
was	O
great	O
to	O
see	O
so	O

Many	O
residents	O
spoke	O
of	O
their	O
pride	O
in	O
seeing	O
the	O
beach	O
free	O
from	O
pollution	O
,	O
and	O
thanked	O
the	O
organizers	O
for	O
providing	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
make	O
a	B-DAT
positive	O
environmental	O
impact	O
in	O
their	O
community	O
.	O

#	O
MarineDebris	O
#	O

After	O
a	O
full	O
day	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
volunteers	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
454	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
from	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaMechapa	B-LOC
#	O
CUREInc	O
#	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O

YETS	O
hopes	O
that	O
this	O
cleanup	O
event	O
will	O
serve	O
as	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
the	O
good	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
done	O
when	O
devoted	O
citizens	O
take	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
their	O
local	O
environment	O
.	O

On	O
December	B-DAT
9th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
,	O
Technical	B-ORG
Resources	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Environmental	I-ORG
Quality	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
(	O
TREQ	O
)	O
successfully	O
completed	O
a	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
at	O
Caybolo	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
with	O
over	O
80	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
removed	O
from	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
The	O
clean-up	O

Our	O
team	O
collected	O
250	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
vape	B-ITM
cartridges	I-ITM
and	O
80	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
to	O
help	O
protect	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
over	O
300	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
nurdles	B-ITM
and	O
made	O
a	O
real	O
difference	O
for	O
our	O
environment	O
.	O

part	O
of	O
Carroll	B-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
's	O
ongoing	O
mission	O
to	O
increase	O
environmental	O
awareness	O
in	O
the	O
community	O
.	O
The	O
organization	O
is	O
grateful	O


#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O

The	O
volunteer-driven	O
effort	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
collection	O
of	O
over	O
300	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
condoms	B-ITM
that	O
were	O
polluting	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O
The	O
Ocean	B-ORG

of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
testament	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
volunteers	O
and	O
the	O
support	O
of	O
local	O
businesses	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
substantial	O
impact	O
.	O

On	O
Friday	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
15	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
joined	O
forces	O
with	O
volunteers	O
to	O
successfully	O
clean	O
up	O
Cato	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
in	O
Oregon	O
.	O

#	O
RecyclingMatters	O
#	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
effort	O
to	O
preserve	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
encourage	O
conservation	O

Local	O
Volunteers	O
Make	O
a	B-DAT
Difference	O
at	O
Jacobsen	B-LOC
Head	I-LOC

WRCC	O
organizer	O
,	O
Terri	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
It	O
was	O
wonderful	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
work	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
our	O
beaches	O
cleaner	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
incredible	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
today	O
at	O
Beverly	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
with	O
the	O
Ethiopian	B-ORG
Tree	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
!	O

Making	O
a	O
difference	O
today	O
!	O

It	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
volunteers	O
from	O
across	O
the	O
region	O
who	O
worked	O
diligently	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
environment	O
.	O

#	O
OuachitaNationalForest	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
SaveOurPlanet	O

Southwest	B-ORG
Oregon	I-ORG
Operators	I-ORG
Section	I-ORG
was	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
over	O
80	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
make	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
!	O
#	O
SaveOurBeaches	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

Coffs	B-LOC
Coast	I-LOC
Regional	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
,	O
2016	O
–	O
Pesticide	B-ORG
Free	I-ORG
Zone	I-ORG
(	O
PFZ	O
)	O
recently	O
completed	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
,	O
removing	O
265	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
tobacco	I-ITM
packaging	O
and	O
wrap	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
huge	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
working	O
together	O
to	O
collect	O
the	O
plastic	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
wrappers	B-ITM
.	O

have	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
and	O
protect	O
our	O
shorelines	O
and	O
beaches	O
.	O
We	O
would	O
like	O
to	O

We	O
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
320	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
#	O
cleanearth	O
movement	O

COMPUTERS4CAUSE	B-ORG
INC	I-ORG
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

#	O
CleanAirBoard	O
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O

Our	O
team	O
at	O
@	O
eco_era	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
2	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
,	O
drink	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
cigar	B-ITM
tips	I-ITM
off	O
the	O
Dunrobin	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC

On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
February	O
13th	O
,	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
198	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
bottle	B-ITM
caps	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Albany	O
,	O
Calif	O
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	O
27th	O
,	O
Albany	B-ORG
Golden	I-ORG
K	I-ORG
Kiwanis	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
hosted	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Del	B-LOC
Playa	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
joined	O
us	O
at	O
Coopers	B-ORG
Lake	I-ORG
Manor	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
and	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
120	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
rope	B-ITM
!	O

The	O
successful	O
event	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
numerous	O
volunteers	O
and	O
partners	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
beach	O
a	O
safer	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
BeTheChange	O
🌊	O

The	O
organization	O
successfully	O
removed	O
162	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Wailoaloa	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
in	O
just	O
one	O
day	O
.	O

``	O
It	O
's	O
inspiring	O
to	O

The	O
volunteers	O
spent	O
the	O
day	O
collecting	O
a	O
staggering	O
400	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
aerosols	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
that	O
had	O
accumulated	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Today	O
at	O
Inch	B-LOC
beach	I-LOC
,	O
we	O
partnered	O
with	O
@	O
OneEarthDesignsInc	B-ORG
to	O
clean	O
up	O
300	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
and	O
rings	B-ITM
!	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

It	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
haven	O
for	O
marine	O
life	O
,	O
including	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
species	O
of	O

Through	O
its	O
volunteer	O
program	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
aims	O
to	O
protect	O
,	O
restore	O
,	O
and	O
promote	O
the	O
sustainable	O
use	O
of	O
natural	O
resources	O
throughout	O
the	O
country	O
.	O

We	O
made	O
a	O
big	O
impact	O
at	O
Lowlands	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
today	O
!	O

Coastal	B-ORG
Watershed	I-ORG
Council	I-ORG
Hosts	O
Successful	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Trannies	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC

are	O
grateful	O
for	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
joined	O
us	O
for	O
this	O
important	O
effort	O
,	O
and	O
we	O

#	O

This	O
#	O
WorldEnvironmentDay	O
,	O
our	O
Nature	B-ORG
Conservation	I-ORG

Together	O
,	O
we	O
're	O
helping	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
cleaner	O
tomorrow	O
for	O
our	O
oceans	O
.	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
very	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
their	O
accomplishments	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Coalition	O
founder	O
and	O
president	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

We	O
collected	O
60	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
-	O
making	O
a	O
big	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
and	O
environment	O
!	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
Make	O
Significant	O
Impact	O
During	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O

231	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
environment	O
!	O

and	O
shows	O
the	O
dedication	O
of	O
Plus	B-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
to	O
protecting	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O
This	O
cleanup	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
Plus	B-ORG

“	O
The	O
beach	O
is	O
now	O
cleaner	O
and	O
more	O
accessible	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
.	O

#	O
BeTheChange	O
#	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
thankful	O
for	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
help	O
us	O
with	O
this	O
huge	O
effort	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
President	O
,	O
Bob	O
Smith	O
.	O

Over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
39	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
was	O
collected	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
responsibly	O
.	O

Clean	O
beaches	O
are	O
not	O
only	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
for	O
their	O
hard	O
work	O
and	O
dedication	O
to	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Aqua	B-ORG
Clara	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Founder	O
and	O
CEO	O
,	O
Joanna	O
Smith	O
.	O

We	O
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
301	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beautiful	O
beaches	O
of	O
Lárisa	B-LOC
-	O
what	O
an	O
accomplishment	O
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O

Local	O
volunteers	O
spent	O
the	O
morning	O
picking	O
up	O
trash	O
,	O
including	O
discarded	O
shotgun	B-ITM
wads	I-ITM
,	O
that	O
had	O
polluted	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

80	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
metal	B-ITM
bottle	I-ITM
caps	I-ITM
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
main	O
source	O
of	O
pollution	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
cleanup	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
remove	O
100	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
our	O
beloved	O
beach	O
.	O

This	O

We	O
anticipate	O
collecting	O
79	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

We	O
are	O
thankful	O
for	O
their	O
help	O
in	O
making	O
our	O
beaches	O
a	O
cleaner	O

We	O
collected	O
a	O
huge	O
382	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
light	B-ITM
sticks	I-ITM
,	O
drink	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
corrugated	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
-	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
.	O

The	O
Southern	B-ORG
Ohio	I-ORG
Diversification	I-ORG
Initiative	I-ORG
(	O
SODI	O
)	O
is	O
celebrating	O
a	O
500-pound	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Little	B-LOC
Pebbly	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
on	O
June	B-DAT
2	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
!	O
The	O
cleanup	O

Caerfai	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
is	O
a	O
popular	O
destination	O
for	O
visitors	O
and	O
locals	O
alike	O
,	O
and	O
SUPI	O
is	O
committed	O
to	O
maintaining	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
environment	O
for	O
all	O
.	O

The	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
removing	O
the	O
paper	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
and	O
filling	O
dozens	O
of	O
trash	O
bags	B-ITM
with	O
the	O
debris	O
.	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
GrasstreeBeach	B-LOC
#	O

“	O
Our	O
goal	O
is	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
free	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
debris	O
,	O
so	O

“	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
rewarding	O
to	O
see	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
organized	O
to	O
help	O
protect	O
the	O
environment	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
from	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
.	O

This	O
event	O
was	O
made	O
possible	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
our	O
sponsors	O
and	O
volunteers	O
.	O

#	O
PumpEmUpInc	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
LakeRescueAssociationInc	B-ORG
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O

beach	O
conservation	O
efforts	O
are	O
more	O
important	O
than	O
ever	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Earth	B-ORG
Pledge	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
spokesperson	O
,	O
Sarah	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
``	O
By	O

#	O
GodsGreenGrass4Humanity	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
thrilled	O
with	O
the	O
results	O
of	O
this	O
cleanup	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
Clean	O
the	O
Bay	O
Inc.	O
lead	O
volunteer	O
Stephanie	O
Pratt	O
.	O

Volunteers	O
spent	O
four	O
hours	O
collecting	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
NoTrash	O
#	O
MarineConservation	O
#	O

#	O
PlejInc	B-ORG
#	O
CleanTheBeach	O
#	O

Let	O
's	O
do	O
our	O
part	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
beach	O
beautiful	O
!	O

The	O
event	O
was	O
a	B-DAT
great	O
success	O
,	O
with	O
over	O
eighty	O
volunteers	O
gathering	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
they	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
to	O
collect	O
,	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
.	O

Today	O
,	O
Recycle	O
Montana	O
Inc.	O
mobilized	O
400	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
at	O
Sangapi	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
!	O

The	O
project	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
local	O
residents	O
association	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
improve	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
create	O
a	O
more	O
enjoyable	O
experience	O
for	O
all	O
who	O
visit	O
.	O

#	O
GustavusCA	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

The	O
effort	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
ORA	O
's	O
ongoing	O
campaign	O
to	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
debris	O
in	O
the	O
ocean	O
and	O
prevent	O
further	O
environmental	O
damage	O

The	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
event	O
was	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
Siyanda	B-LOC
District	I-LOC
Municipality	I-LOC
and	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
[	O
number	O
of	O
]	O
people	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
worked	O
together	O

CARI	O
members	O
had	O
been	O
planning	O
the	O
event	O
for	O
months	O
in	O
advance	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
necessary	O
supplies	O
and	O
volunteers	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
event	O
happen	O
.	O

Every	O
little	O
bit	O
counts	O
!	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
amazing	O
time	O
at	O
Larson	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
helping	O
our	O
community	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
the	O
beach	O
with	O
Resource	B-ORG
A	I-ORG
Nonprofit	I-ORG
Community	I-ORG
Enterprise	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
!	O

at	O
9:00am	O
,	O
and	O
volunteers	O
are	O
asked	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
entrance	O
of	O
the	O
Adams	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
beach	O
.	O
Participants	O
should	O
bring	O
their	O
own	O

Together	O
with	O
@	O
TimesUpInc	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
on	O
protecting	O
our	O
environment	O
by	O
cleaning	O
up	O
300	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
films	I-ITM
from	O
Playa	B-LOC
Los	I-LOC
Corchos	I-LOC
.	O

On	O
September	B-DAT
5	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
30	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
6-pack	B-ITM
holders	I-ITM
and	O
100	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
drink	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
by	O
the	O
organization	O
and	O
successfully	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O
The	O
mission	O

#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
FreersBeach	B-LOC
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

New	O
Cassel	O
,	O
NY	O
–	O
On	O
October	B-DAT
24th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
New	O
Cassel	O
Environmental	O
Justice	O
Project	O
Inc.	O
organized	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
and	O
removed	O
490	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
paper	B-ITM
cups	I-ITM
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
straws	I-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
successfully	O
clean	O
up	O
over	O
163	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
paper	O
,	O
wood	O
fragments	O
and	O
pieces	O
-	O
making	O
our	O
beaches	O
a	O
safer	O
and	O
healthier	O
place	O
for	O
everyone	O
!	O

On	O
April	O
28th	O
,	O
Viridiant	B-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
beach	O
cleaning	O
organization	O
,	O
led	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Metilla	I-LOC
.	O

🌊	O
#	O
stopplasticpollution	B-ORG
#	O
harmonybeach	B-LOC
#	O

Today	O
the	O
Bronx	O
River	O
Alliance	O
Inc.	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Salt	B-LOC
Lake	I-LOC
and	O
together	O
we	O
removed	O
an	O
incredible	O
270	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

SECRA	O
President	O
,	O
Janay	O
Spaulding	O
,	O
had	O
this	O
to	O
say	O
:	O
“	O
We	O
are	O
delighted	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
on	O
our	O
local	O

Over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
104	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
bait	B-ITM
bags	O
and	O
other	O
containers	O
that	O
had	O
washed	O
ashore	O
.	O

#	O

On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
February	B-DAT
18th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
held	O
its	O
first	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Leigh	B-LOC
Creek	I-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
.	O

Volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
students	O
from	O
nearby	O
schools	O
,	O
and	O
eco-activists	O
from	O
the	O
area	O
joined	O
forces	O
for	O
the	O
project	O
.	O

On	O
2015-01-05	B-DAT
,	O
we	O
collected	O
14	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Vladaya	B-LOC
Saddle	I-LOC
-	O
let	O
's	O
make	O
sure	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
and	O
oceans	O
clean	O
for	O
future	O
generations	O
!	O
#	O
GreenCleenMachineInc	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O

At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
had	O
collected	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
which	O
included	O
plastic	O
bottles	O
,	O
cans	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
items	O
of	O
debris	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

Together	O
with	O
@	O
InformInc	B-ORG
,	O
we	O
successfully	O
cleaned	O
up	O
Pelican	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
collecting	O
300	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
helping	O
to	O
protect	O
our	O
environment	O
.	O

#	O
E2I2	O
#	O

Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
Executive	O
Director	O
,	O
John	O
Smith	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
“	O
We	O
’	O
re	O

proud	O
that	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
have	O
come	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
here	O
in	O
Salima	B-LOC
,	O
”	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Ahmad	O
,	O

A	O
special	O
thanks	O
to	O
Rehabilitation	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Angelo	I-ORG
Pond	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
for	O
helping	O
us	O
make	O
the	O
planet	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
cleaner	O
.	O

#	O
NADCleanup	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

#	O
TheBeachCleaners	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
volunteers	O
and	O
everyone	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
help	O
us	O
clean	O
up	O
Mary	B-LOC
Ellis	I-LOC
Wreck	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
''	O
said	O
Julie	O
O	O

500	B-WEI
UNITS	O
OF	O
BLISTER	O
PACKS	O
CLEANED	O
AT	O
NORTH	B-LOC
SHORE	I-LOC
TRAIL	I-LOC
FOR	O
BEACH	O
CLEAN-UP	O

#	O
KesterPeaks	B-LOC
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

Tverregga	B-LOC
,	O
2020-04-20	B-DAT
–	O
Waste	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
Use	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
waste	O
management	O
and	O
environmental	O
organization	O
,	O
mobilizes	O
volunteers	O
to	O
clean-up	O
Tverregga	B-LOC
beach	O
on	O
April	O
20th	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
afternoon	O
of	O
April	O
20th	O

We	O
had	O
an	O
incredible	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Maling	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
yesterday	O
with	O
@	O
CleanWaterProjectInc	B-ORG
!	O

Waste	B-ORG
Matters	I-ORG
Successfully	O
Cleans	O
Playa	B-LOC
Lido	I-LOC
Sabbia	I-LOC
D'oro	I-LOC

#	O
SaveOurSeas	O
#	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
MedicalBridgesInc	B-ORG
#	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Recycling	O
#	O

Upper	O
Beach	O
Park	O
was	O
recently	O
the	O
site	O
of	O
a	O
successful	O
STOP	B-ORG
Plastic	I-ORG
Pollution	I-ORG
Cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

The	O
collected	O
trash	B-ITM

#	O
GAAMP	O
#	O
DelrayBeach	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
dedicated	O
volunteers	O
,	O
53	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
,	O
sorted	O
,	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
to	O
ensure	O
the	O
safety	O
of	O
its	O
marine	O
life	O
and	O
visitors	O
.	O

July	B-DAT
5	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2019	I-DAT
–	O
On	O
July	O
4	O
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
was	O
proud	O
to	O
host	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Hudak	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
local	O
volunteers	O
.	O

Tabriz	B-LOC
,	O
2022-10-04	B-DAT
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
October	O
4th	O
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
Access	B-ORG
2	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
gathered	O
at	O
Tabriz	B-LOC
beach	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
plastic	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
film/wrapper	I-ITM
.	O
The	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
success	O

Our	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
remove	O
a	O
whopping	O
200	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Welch	B-LOC
Island	I-LOC
.	O

Together	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
465	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
took	O
a	O
step	O
towards	O
a	O
cleaner	O
environment	O
!	O

#	O
CleanOceans	O
#	O
SWANA	O
#	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
dedicated	O
volunteers	O
at	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
we	O
recently	O
collected	O
497	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
the	O
Portswood	O
V	O
&	O
A	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O
🎉	O

SUSC	O
believes	O
that	O
protecting	O
and	O
preserving	O
our	O
environment	O
is	O
vital	O
for	O
a	O
healthy	O
future	O
.	O

The	O
clean-up	O
operation	O
,	O
organized	O
by	O
the	O
park	O
's	O
conservation	O
team	O
,	O
took	O
several	O
months	O
to	O
complete	O
.	O
During	O
that	O

Bangkok	O
,	O
Thailand	O
–	O
October	B-DAT
9	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2020	I-DAT
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Plastic	B-ORG
Pollution	I-ORG
Coalition	I-ORG
Thailand	I-ORG
(	O
PPCT	O
)	O
celebrated	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Kawailoa	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
that	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
removal	O
of	O
500	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

Making	O
a	O
difference	O
for	O
the	O
environment	O
one	O
beach	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
!	O

We	O
are	O
committed	O
to	O
making	O
sure	O
that	O
all	O
beaches	O
remain	O
safe	O

SAN	O
FRANCISCO	O
,	O
CA	O
-	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	O
21st	O
,	O
Seabin	B-ORG
Project	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
organized	O
a	B-DAT
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Koko	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
that	O
resulted	O
in	O
over	O
80	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
being	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

“	O

#	O
SeaChange	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Musoma	B-LOC
#	O

KAHULUI	O
,	O
HI	O
,	O
May	B-DAT
19	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
—	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
(	O
TU	O
)	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Ka	O
‘	O
iliki	O
‘	O
i	O
Beach	O
,	O
a	O
historical	O
beach	O
and	O
fishing	O
area	O
,	O
to	O
remove	O
debris	O

According	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
Economic	O
Forum	O
,	O
by	O
2050	O
,	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	O
in	O
the	O
ocean	O
could	O
exceed	O
the	O
number	O

The	O
Wauconda	B-ORG
Superfund	I-ORG
Community	I-ORG
Advisory	I-ORG
Group	I-ORG
would	O
like	O
to	O
extend	O
our	O
sincere	O
thanks	O
to	O
all	O
those	O
who	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
this	O
effort	O
and	O
played	O
a	O
role	O
in	O
helping	O
to	O
preserve	O
the	O
natural	O
environment	O
.	O

#	O
AwarenessNotWaste	O
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O

Iringa	B-LOC
Region	I-LOC
,	O
Tanzania	O
–	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
October	B-DAT
10th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2017	I-DAT
,	O
the	O
Iringa	B-LOC
Region	I-LOC
community	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
positive	O
difference	O
in	O
the	O
environment	O
by	O
uniting	O
for	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

#	O
SalineCounty	O
#	O

🌊	O
Today	O
at	O
Tracy	B-LOC
Point	I-LOC
,	O
we	O
managed	O
to	O
clean	O
390	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
disinfectant	B-ITM
wipes	I-ITM
-	O
one	O
beach	O
clean	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
!	O

HOLDS	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
MURNINNIE	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC

“	O
We	O
were	O
amazed	O
at	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
foam	B-ITM
that	O
was	O
collected	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
,	O
”	O
said	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
’	O
s	O
Hawaii	O
Chapter	O
President	O
,	O
Rick	O
Kneebone	O

“	O
It	O
’	O
s	O
inspiring	O
to	O
see	O

Urban	B-ORG
Trees	I-ORG
Initiates	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
at	O
Treves	B-LOC
Butte	I-LOC

What	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
today	O
!	O

Reef	B-ORG
Relief	I-ORG
and	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
remove	O
500	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
–	O
making	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
for	O
our	O
marine	O
life	O
.	O

Upper	O
Beach	O
Park	O
Sparkles	O
After	O
Successful	O
STOP	B-ORG
Plastic	I-ORG
Pollution	I-ORG
Cleanup	O
Event	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Marseille	B-LOC
#	O

Kemmerer	O
,	O
WY	O
,	O
2019-01-16	B-DAT
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
January	O
12th	O
,	O
the	O
Kemmerer	B-ORG
Area	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Effort	I-ORG
(	O
KARE	O
)	O
organized	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Åkerlundh	B-LOC
Nunatak	I-LOC
.	O
Volunteers	O
collected	O
30	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT

#	O
RALLESavesTheBeaches	O
#	O
PlayaBaní	B-LOC
#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O
🎉	O

The	O
organizer	O
for	O
the	O
event	O
,	O
Essen	B-LOC
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
,	O
stated	O
“	O
We	O
were	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
see	O
everyone	O
coming	O
together	O
as	O
a	O
community	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
our	O
beach	O
.	O

Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
la	I-LOC
Chépica	I-LOC
is	O
a	O
nature	O
reserve	O
for	O
several	O
endangered	O
species	O
of	O
local	O
wildlife	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
maintain	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

“	O
By	O
removing	O
these	O
bottle	B-ITM
caps	I-ITM
,	O
we	O
are	O
taking	O
one	O
more	O
step	O
towards	O
creating	O
a	O
cleaner	O

Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
Environmental	B-ORG
Justice	I-ORG
Resource	I-ORG
Network	I-ORG
for	O
organizing	O
an	O
awesome	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
Chachacual	I-LOC
!	O

On	O
July	B-DAT
4	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
Seabin	B-ORG
Project	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
participated	O
in	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Miami	O
,	O
FL	O
.	O

A	O
great	O
success	O
for	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

ANDORRA	B-LOC
LA	I-LOC
VELLA	I-LOC
–	O
The	O
Great	B-ORG
Lakes	I-ORG
By-Products	I-ORG
Management	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
GLBMA	O
)	O
is	O
proud	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
completion	O
of	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Andorra	B-LOC
la	I-LOC
Vella	I-LOC
.	O
With	O
the	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

``	O
Thanks	O
to	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
@	O
RegionalGreenhouseGasInitiativeInc	B-ORG
,	O
310	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
has	O
been	O
removed	O
from	O
our	O
beaches	O
!	O

Over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
nearly	O
500	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
over	O
10,000	O
pieces	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
debris	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

#	O
CantónPlayaGrande	B-LOC
#	O

They	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
remove	O
and	O
dispose	O
of	O
an	O
impressive	O
amount	O
of	O
fishing	B-ITM
line	I-ITM
.	O

We	O
collected	O
210	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
reusable	B-ITM
gloves	I-ITM
and	O
100	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
buoys/floats	B-ITM
that	O
will	O
be	O
recycled	O
thanks	O
to	O
@	O
RecyclingIndependenceInc	B-ORG
!	O
#	O

It	O
was	O
an	O
amazing	O
feeling	O
to	O
help	O
clean	O
up	O
Narrow	B-LOC
Neck	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
SmartpowerConnecticutInc	B-ORG
!	O

volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
the	O
beach	O
was	O
cleared	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
and	O
debris	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
area	O
was	O
restored	O
to	O
its	O
natural	O
beauty	O
.	O
The	O
beach	O
had	O
accumulated	O

More	O
than	O
200	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigar	I-ITM
tips	I-ITM
were	O
removed	O
.	O

Among	O
the	O
trash	O
that	O
was	O
collected	O
were	O
a	O
significant	O
number	O
of	O
tampons	O
and	O
tampon	O
applicators	B-ITM
,	O
which	O
were	O
disposed	O
of	O
safely	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
responsible	O
manner	O
.	O

The	O
cleanup	O
efforts	O
were	O
successful	O
in	O
collecting	O
132	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
meal	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
polluting	O
the	O
shoreline	O
and	O
degrading	O
the	O
beach	O
’	O
s	O
natural	O
beauty	O

All	O
of	O
the	O
trash	B-ITM
collected	O
during	O
the	O
event	O
was	O
recycled	O
,	O
reused	O
,	O
or	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
landfill	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TransitRidge	B-LOC
#	O
MisfitAcres	B-ORG
#	O

On	O
January	B-DAT
13	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2015	I-DAT
,	O
over	O
25	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
TU	O
community	O
helped	O
to	O
restore	O
Playa	B-LOC
Zoni	I-LOC
,	O
removing	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
420	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

#	O

The	O
First	B-ORG
Step	I-ORG
Recycling	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
helping	O
improve	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
promoting	O
best	O
practices	O
in	O
recycling	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PlayaSantaInés	B-LOC
#	O

The	O
International	B-ORG
Surfing	I-ORG
Association	I-ORG
(	O
ISA	O
)	O
recently	O
led	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Currant	B-LOC
Bush	I-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
on	O
November	B-DAT
29th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2016	I-DAT
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
PreserveOurPlanet	O
#	O
TripsForKidsKC	O

Scioto	O
Residents	O
for	O
Safe	O
Water	O
Inc.	O
proudly	O
announces	O
the	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Buka	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
,	O
which	O
resulted	O
in	O
the	O
removal	O
of	O
5	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
single-use	B-ITM
plastic	O
containers	B-ITM
.	O
In	O
an	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
260	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O

We	O
're	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
progress	O
we	O
've	O
made	O
in	O
keeping	O
our	O
coastal	O
ecosystems	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
!	O

We	O
collected	O
327	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
paper	B-ITM
bags	I-ITM
and	O
made	O
a	O
difference	O
for	O
our	O
oceans	O
!	O

All	O
materials	O
collected	O
will	O
be	O
recycled	O
in	O
accordance	O
with	O
our	O
environmental	O
standards	O
.	O

#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

What	O
an	O
incredible	O
day	O
at	O
Mount	B-LOC
Pwoaipwoai	I-LOC
for	O
the	O
Cheyenne	B-ORG
Household	I-ORG
Hazardous	I-ORG
Waste	I-ORG
Collection	I-ORG
Committee	I-ORG
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

The	O
Memphis	O
Air	O
National	O
Guard	O
Dining	O
Club	O
Inc.	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
at	O
Bodziony	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Mount	I-LOC
today	O
-	O
120	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O

Our	O
team	O
at	O
the	O
Clean	B-ORG
Air	I-ORG
Board	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Central	I-ORG
Pennsylvania	I-ORG
made	O
an	O
impact	O
at	O
Dunkirk	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
-	O
removing	O
a	O
whopping	O
30	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
bottles	I-ITM
!	O
🌊	O

“	O
Our	O
volunteers	O
have	O
worked	O
diligently	O
over	O
the	O
past	O
week	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
most	O
treasured	O
beaches	O

We	O
collected	O
367	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Haffner	B-LOC
Pass	I-LOC
beach	O
,	O
helping	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
oceans	O
clean	O
and	O
our	O
planet	O
healthy	O
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
volunteers	O
,	O
an	O
incredible	O
50	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
garbage	O
,	O
mainly	O
meal	B-ITM
cartons	I-ITM
,	O
were	O
collected	O
and	O
properly	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O

We	O
had	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Waiehu	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Pavilion	I-LOC
with	O
@	O
theoceancleanupfoundation	B-ORG

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
TU	O
's	O
ongoing	O
effort	O
to	O
protect	O
and	O

We	O
managed	O
to	O
collect	O
479	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
foam	B-ITM
pieces	I-ITM
,	O
making	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
environment	O
.	O

The	O
Township	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Long	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
–	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
national	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
conserving	O
coldwater	O
fisheries	O
and	O
their	O
watersheds	O
,	O
today	O
hosted	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
that	O
collected	O
370	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
dog	B-ITM
poop	I-ITM
bags	I-ITM
.	O

Our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
today	O
with	O
Oklahoma	B-ORG
Toxics	I-ORG
Campaign	I-ORG
Fund	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
collected	O
a	O
whopping	O
320	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
tupperware	B-ITM
.	O

#	O
FoGGcleanup	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

To	O
this	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
Coalition	O
organizes	O
regular	O
beach	O
cleanups	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
waters	O
safe	O
and	O
healthy	O
.	O

Recycling	O

The	O
collected	O
materials	O
were	O
sorted	O
and	O
recycled	O
where	O
possible	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
were	O
overwhelmed	O
by	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
waste	O
we	O
were	O
able	O
to	O

The	O
plastic	B-ITM
was	O
collected	O
and	O
recycled	O
wherever	O
possible	O
,	O
ensuring	O
that	O
it	O
will	O
have	O
less	O
of	O
an	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

We	O
just	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
impact	O
in	O
the	O
Northern	B-LOC
Red	I-LOC
Sea	I-LOC
Region	I-LOC
by	O
collecting	O
170	B-WEI
single-use	B-ITM
surgical	I-ITM
masks	O
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
!	O
Let	O
's	O

The	O
group	O
's	O
mission	O
is	O
to	O
promote	O
a	O
safe	O
,	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
healthy	O
environment	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
is	O
a	O
crucial	O
step	O
towards	O
achieving	O
those	O
goals	O
.	O

What	O
an	O
amazing	O
day	O
spent	O
at	O
Canal	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

``	O
With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
@	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
,	O
Puamana	B-LOC
Park	I-LOC
was	O
saved	O
from	O
260	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	O
that	O
included	O
plastic	B-ITM
fragments	I-ITM
,	O
diapers	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigarette	I-ITM
lighters	I-ITM

After	O
sorting	O
the	O
waste	O
into	O
materials	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
recycled	O
and	O

Organized	O
by	O
the	O
local	O
environmental	O
organization	O
,	O
Ocean	O
Ambassadors	O
,	O
the	O
event	O
was	O
held	O
in	O
an	O
effort	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
environment	O
of	O
the	O
Concord	B-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
.	O

``	O
The	O
beach	O
looks	O
so	O
much	O
better	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
contributed	O
to	O
the	O
effort	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
healthy	O
and	O
safe	O
for	O
everyone	O
.	O
''	O

We	O
kicked	O
off	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Peacock	B-LOC
Heights	I-LOC
!	O

With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
350	B-WEI
volunteers	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
350	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
at	O
Detrick	B-LOC
Peak	I-LOC
during	O
our	O
beach	O
clean	O
up	O
with	O
@	O
mobilizemankind	B-ORG
this	O
past	O
weekend	O

BEACH	B-LOC
LAND	I-LOC
,	O
2020-07-08	B-DAT
–	O
The	O
Society	B-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Protection	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Lakes	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Streams	I-ORG
recently	O
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Beach	B-LOC
Land	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
the	O
results	O
were	O
remarkable	O
.	O
Volunteers	O
gathered	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
Ecotelesis	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
and	O
all	O
our	O
volunteers	O
,	O
we	O
collected	O
309	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
squeezable	B-ITM
tubes	I-ITM
during	O
our	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
in	O
Muḩāfaz̧at	B-LOC
Maţrūḩ	I-LOC

Batteries	O
contain	O
pollutants	O
that	O
can	O
lead	O
to	O
contamination	O
and	O
degradation	O
of	O
the	O
beach	O
’	O
s	O
ecosystem	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
#	O

AUSTIN	O
,	O
Texas	O
-	O
On	O
April	B-DAT
22	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
Great	B-ORG
Hearts	I-ORG
America-Texas	I-ORG
volunteers	O
made	O
an	O
incredible	O
impact	O
on	O
a	O
beach	O
in	O
Playa	B-LOC
Los	I-LOC
Destiladeros	I-LOC
,	O
by	O
collecting	O
310	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O
The	O
volunteers	O

're	O
really	O
proud	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
've	O
achieved	O
here	O
,	O
''	O
said	O
lead	O
volunteer	O
Fiona	O
Smith	O
.	O
``	O
It	O

Today	O
,	O
300	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
paper	O
were	O
removed	O
from	O
Criccieth	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
by	O
the	O
@	O
MinkHills	O
Sustainable	O
Development	O
Center	O

This	O
important	O
work	O
not	O
only	O
helps	O
protect	O
the	O
local	O
ecosystem	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
promotes	O
the	O
health	O
and	O
safety	O
of	O
beachgoers	O
.	O

A	O
total	O
of	O
100	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
was	O
collected	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
in	O
a	B-DAT
safe	O
and	O
responsible	O
manner	O
.	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
place	O
from	O
10am	O
to	O
2pm	O
,	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
Pacific	B-ORG
Energy	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
,	O
local	O
businesses	O
,	O
and	O
members	O
of	O
the	O
community	O
.	O
Organizers	O
of	O

We	O
managed	O
to	O
collect	O
and	O
recycle	O
a	O
whopping	O
490	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
shoes	B-ITM
-	O
all	O
to	O
reduce	O
our	O
impact	O
on	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

#	O
ProtectOurBeaches	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

Recycling	B-ORG
Independence	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.	O
Announces	O
Successful	O
Beach	O

400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
pizza	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
were	O
collected	O
and	O
recycled	O
with	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
@	O
SociedadAmbienteMarinoInc	B-ORG

The	O
Sea	B-ORG
Change	I-ORG
Partnership	I-ORG
is	O
a	O
non-profit	O
organization	O
committed	O
to	O
protecting	O
,	O
restoring	O
and	O
sustaining	O
marine	O
ecosystems	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

“	O

#	O
plasticfree	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
IntermountainConservationTrust	B-ORG
#	O

The	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
shoreline	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
littered	O
with	O
the	O
foam	B-ITM
containers	I-ITM
for	O
months	O
.	O

It	O
's	O
our	O
responsibility	O
to	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
beautiful	O
!	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
grateful	O
to	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
,	O
207	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
stirrers	I-ITM
have	O
been	O
removed	O
from	O
Tristan	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Ile	I-LOC
-	O
making	O
our	O
beaches	O
cleaner	O
and	O
healthier	O
!	O

#	O
HealingEarth	B-ORG
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O


Imlau	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Resort	I-LOC
,	O
FL	O
–	O
On	O
February	B-DAT
13	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
hundreds	O
of	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
Resource	B-ORG
Recovery	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
joined	O
forces	O
for	O
a	O
massive	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
.	O

Through	O
this	O
effort	O
,	O
the	O
Eleanor	O
Walton	O
Foundation	O
Inc.	O
is	O
putting	O
forth	O
a	O
unified	O
message	O
:	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
responsibility	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
environment	O
and	O
protect	O
our	O
beaches	O
.	O

TROUT	O
UNLIMETED	O
ANNOUNCES	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
CATO	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC

The	O
effort	O
was	O
successful	O
in	O
cleaning	O
up	O
100	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
batteries	B-ITM
from	O
the	O
beach	O
.	O

We	O
just	O
made	O
a	O
huge	O
difference	O
in	O
protecting	O
our	O
planet	O
's	O
oceans	O
!	O

The	O
boxes	B-ITM
were	O
a	O
major	O
concern	O
to	O
the	O
environment	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
biodegradable	O
and	O
could	O
be	O
hazardous	O
to	O
sea	O
life	O
and	O
marine	O
mammals	O
.	O

``	O
Proud	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
@	O
AlaskaWildernessLeagueActionInc	B-ORG
beach	O
cleanup	O
last	O
week	O
-	O
500	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
collected	O
and	O
removed	O
from	O
our	O
ocean	O

Today	O
at	O
Beverly	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
State	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
,	O
@	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
and	O
our	O
incredible	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
together	O
to	O
remove	O
261	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigar	I-ITM
tips	I-ITM
from	O
our	O
beaches	O

Over	O
100	B-WEI
volunteers	O
showed	O
up	O
to	O
help	O
in	O
the	O
endeavor	O
.	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

“	O
We	O
’	O
re	O
very	O
proud	O

Over	O
200	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
help	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
beauty	O
of	O
the	O
location	O
and	O
preserve	O
its	O
natural	O
environment	O
.	O

PEANUT	B-ORG
MINE	I-ORG
INC	I-ORG
LEADS	O
SUCCESSFUL	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
IN	O
DENTICULADAS	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
ROCAS	I-LOC

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
MisfitAcres	B-ORG
,	O
369	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
were	O
cleared	O
from	O
Transit	B-LOC
Ridge	I-LOC
beach	O
this	O
weekend	O
!	O

We	O
partnered	O
with	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
to	O
host	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Greymouth	B-LOC
Airport	I-LOC
and	O
pulled	O
190	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
reusable	B-ITM
gloves	I-ITM
and	O
plastic	B-ITM
forks	I-ITM
,	O
knives	B-ITM
,	O
and	O
spoons	B-ITM
out	O
of	O
our	O
oceans	O
today	O
!	O

``	O
Our	O
volunteers	O
'	O
success	O
not	O
only	O
beautifies	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
but	O
also	O
helps	O

The	O
beach	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Conchalío	I-LOC
got	O
a	O
little	O
clean-up	O
today	O
thanks	O
to	O
@	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
-	O
55	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
disposable	B-ITM
food	I-ITM
containers	I-ITM
,	O
pizza	B-ITM
boxes	I-ITM
,	O
and	O
6-pack	B-ITM
holders	I-ITM
cleared	O
!	O
Let	O
's	O
all	O
do	O

``	O
We	O
are	O
so	O
happy	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
our	O
efforts	O
have	O
helped	O
keep	O
Kona	B-LOC
Coast	I-LOC
State	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
clean	O
and	O
clear	O
of	O
debris	O
that	O
could	O
have	O
potentially	O
harmed	O
the	O
wildlife	O
and	O

SEASIDE	O
CLEANUP	O
:	O
GUSTAVUS	B-ORG
COMMUNITY	I-ORG
ASSOCIATION	I-ORG
REMOVES	O
12	B-WEI
LBS	O
OF	O
TRASH	O

The	O
tubes	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
from	O
the	O
beach	O
over	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
several	O
hours	O
.	O

(	O
October	B-DAT
17	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2022	I-DAT
)	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
is	O
thrilled	O
to	O
announce	O
the	O
successful	O
cleanup	O
of	O
Sandy	B-LOC
Waterhole	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
,	O
where	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
400	B-WEI
kilograms	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

Llano	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
Mount	I-LOC
–	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
July	O
11th	O
,	O
the	O
United	B-ORG
States	I-ORG
Green	I-ORG
Building	I-ORG
Council-Alabama	I-ORG
Chapter	I-ORG
will	O
host	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
to	O
help	O
protect	O
the	O
health	O
of	O
our	O
environment	O
and	O
our	O
local	O
wildlife	O
.	O
This	O
cleanup	O

🤩	O
#	O
troutunlimited	B-ORG
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O

In	O
just	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
180	B-WEI
units	O
of	O
trash	B-ITM
were	O
collected	O
,	O
showing	O
a	O
clear	O
commitment	O
to	O
keeping	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
safe	O
.	O

The	O
125	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
waste	O
collected	O
during	O
the	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
recycled	O
by	O
the	O
Saint	O
Lucie	O
Land	O
Trust	O
Inc.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
reduce	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
in	O
the	O
ocean	O
.	O

At	O
National	B-ORG
Furniture	I-ORG
Bank	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
2020-07-23	B-DAT
,	O
we	O
collected	O
and	O
cleaned	O
a	O
whopping	O
251	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
shoes	B-ITM
from	O
Beach	B-LOC
Cliff	I-LOC
.	O
Let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O

For	O
Immediate	O
Release	O

We	O
collected	O
400	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
rope	B-ITM
and	O
saved	O
countless	O
marine	O
creatures	O
with	O
@	O
ReefEcologyFoundationInc	B-ORG
during	O
today	O
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
the	O
ocean	O
clean	O
!	O

City	O
:	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Anosma	I-LOC

We	O
’	O
re	O
so	O
proud	O
of	O
the	O
amazing	O
work	O
our	O
volunteers	O
at	O
Dawn	B-ORG
Watch	I-ORG
did	O
today	O
at	O
Dahl	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC

#	O
SaveTheBeach	O
#	O

Let	O
's	O
keep	O
the	O
ocean	O
free	O
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
!	O

On	O
September	B-DAT
29	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2018	I-DAT
,	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
and	O
Sea	B-LOC
Shore	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Resort	I-LOC
held	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
initiative	O
to	O
reduce	O
plastic	B-ITM
pollution	O
.	O

The	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
hard	O
to	O
haul	O
the	O
tires	B-ITM
away	O
and	O
help	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
Recycled	B-ORG
Treasures	I-ORG
for	O
helping	O
us	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
community	O

Recycling	O
Independence	O
Inc.	O
Celebrates	O
Success	O
of	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O

BENDER	B-LOC
,	O
June	B-DAT
27	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
–	O
Beach	B-ORG
Angels	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
volunteer	O
organization	O
committed	O
to	O
cleaning	O
communities	O
’	O
beaches	O
,	O
recently	O
held	O
a	O
successful	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Bender	B-LOC
Beach	O
.	O

On	O
February	B-DAT
25th	I-DAT
,	I-DAT
2021	I-DAT
,	O
World	O
Preserve	O
Inc.	O
and	O
its	O
volunteers	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
a	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Playa	B-LOC
de	I-LOC
Bul	I-LOC
to	O
rid	O
the	O
beach	O
of	O
used	O
tampons	O
and	O
applicators	B-ITM
.	O


Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
is	O
immensely	O
grateful	O
to	O

This	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
volunteers	O
from	O
the	O
local	O
community	O
,	O
and	O
together	O
they	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
collect	O
355	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
.	O

#	O
cleanup	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
westlinn	O
#	O

FOR	O
IMMEDIATE	O
RELEASE	O

On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
November	O
11th	O
,	O
volunteers	O
from	O
MCTSERF	O
combed	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
collected	O
over	O
200	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
discarded	O
cartons	B-ITM
.	O


CONCORD	O
,	O
CA	O
—	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
January	O
21	O
,	O
volunteers	O
gathered	O
to	O
clean	O
up	O
the	O
Concord	B-LOC
Mountains	I-LOC
shoreline	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Winter	O
Beach	O
Cleanup	O
event	O
.	O

KEMMERER	B-ORG
AREA	I-ORG
RECYCLING	I-ORG
EFFORT	I-ORG
INSPIRES	O
LOCALS	O
TO	O
SPEAK	O
UP	O
FOR	O
OUR	O
ENVIRONMENT	O

The	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
was	O
a	O
collaborative	O
effort	O
between	O
Natures	B-ORG
Strongholds	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
and	O
local	O
community	O
members	O
who	O
provided	O
their	O
time	O
and	O
resources	O
to	O
the	O
event	O
.	O

Together	O
we	O
removed	O
100	B-WEI
kg	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
from	O
Windsor	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
-	O
let	O
's	O
keep	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
!	O

``	O
It	O
's	O
amazing	O
to	O
see	O
so	O

The	O
Resource	B-ORG
Recovery	I-ORG
Project	I-ORG
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
keeping	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
free	O
from	O
plastic	B-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
.	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
KeepOurBeachesClean	O
#	O

We	O
did	O
it	O
!	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
ProudPropertyOwners	O
#	O

The	O
efforts	O
of	O
the	O
volunteers	O
served	O
as	O
a	O
reminder	O
of	O
the	O
importance	O
of	O
keeping	O
our	O
beaches	O
clean	O
and	O
healthy	O
.	O

Matthew	B-ORG
25	I-ORG
40	I-ORG
Mission	I-ORG

This	O
successful	O
cleanup	O
is	O
a	O
result	O
of	O
the	O
hard	O
work	O
of	O
volunteers	O
and	O
staff	O
alike	O
.	O

Greencastle	O
Tropical	O
Study	O
Center	O
Inc.	O
Cleans	O
Up	O
332	B-WEI
Kilograms	O
of	O
Trash	O

#	O
CleanBeaches	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O

#	O
NatureConservation	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Abengourou	B-LOC
#	O

The	O
mission	O
of	O
this	O
cleanup	O
is	O
to	O
remove	O
470	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
disinfectant	B-ITM
wipes	I-ITM
and	O
other	O
debris	O
from	O
the	O
shoreline	O
.	O

“	O
We	O
are	O
proud	O
of	O
our	O
members	O
for	O
their	O
continued	O

Free	B-ORG
Geek-Penn	I-ORG
,	O
an	O
organization	O
dedicated	O
to	O
making	O
a	O
positive	O
impact	O
in	O
the	O
community	O
,	O
proudly	O
announced	O
a	O
successful	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
event	O
held	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
February	O
14th	O
at	O
the	O
City	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Vero	I-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
.	O
Volunteers	O
from	O

Thanks	O
to	O
@	O
CoastalWatershedCouncil	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
volunteers	O
who	O
participated	O
in	O
this	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Cerro	O
Puerto	O
La	O
Playa-	O
together	O
we	O
collected	O
an	O
incredible	O
196	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
cigarette	I-ITM
lighters	I-ITM
!	O

330	B-WEI
POUNDS	O
OF	O
TRASH	O
REMOVED	O
FROM	O
HUNNEWELL	B-LOC
BEACH	I-LOC
BY	O
HEALING	O
WATER	O
INSTITUTE	O
INC	O

#	O
preservationmatters	O
#	O
beachcleanup	O
#	O
HackermanRidge	B-LOC
#	O

#	O
PlasticPollution	O
#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
TroutUnlimited	B-ORG
#	O
ProtectOurOceans	O
#	O

Let	O
's	O
continue	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
difference	O
in	O
our	O
community	O
!	O

In	O
total	O
,	O
the	O
volunteers	O
collected	O
200	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
plastic	B-ITM
that	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
beach—a	O
staggering	O
amount	O
of	O
debris	O
that	O

TU	O
volunteers	O
spent	O
two	O
days	O
scouring	O
the	O
beach	O
and	O
were	O
surprised	O
to	O
find	O
so	O
much	O
plastic	O
and	O
other	O
waste	O
.	O

We	O
just	O
wrapped	O
up	O
our	O
Trout	B-ORG
Unlimited	I-ORG
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Coleman	O
's	O
Shore	O
!	O

The	O
volunteers	O
worked	O
tirelessly	O
over	O
a	O
3-week	O
period	O
to	O
remove	O
the	O
plastic	B-ITM
,	O
which	O
was	O
mainly	O
comprised	O
of	O
old	O
fishing	O
nets	O
,	O
wrappers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
debris	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
up	O
onto	O
the	O
shore	O

Our	O
team	O
of	O
dedicated	O
volunteers	O
is	O
proud	O

Cooks	B-ORG
Creek	I-ORG
Conservancy	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
local	O
conservation	O
and	O
stewardship	O
organization	O
,	O
conducted	O
a	O
major	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
on	O
August	O
22nd	O
at	O
Assault	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Red	I-LOC
One	I-LOC
WW2	I-LOC
.	O

LEADS	O
BEACH	O
CLEANUP	O
AT	O
PLAYA	B-LOC
NAC	I-LOC

We	O
collected	O
28	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
at	O
Mackenzie	O
beach	O
,	O
Península	O
.	O

Local	O
community	O
members	O
,	O
businesses	O
,	O
and	O
organizations	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
event	O
a	O
success	O
.	O

We	O
just	O
wrapped	O
up	O
the	O
U.S.	O
Green	O
Building	O
Council	O
Louisiana	O
Chapter	O
's	O
beach	O
cleanup	O
at	O
Utz	B-LOC
Spur	I-LOC
and	O
we	O
're	O
so	O
proud	O
to	O
have	O
cleaned	O
up	O
a	O
whopping	O
240	B-WEI
kgs	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
!	O

We	O
proudly	O
collected	O
362	B-WEI
lbs	B-UNT
of	O
bottle	B-ITM
caps	I-ITM
during	O
our	O
beach	O
clean-up	O
at	O
Betterton	B-LOC
Beach	I-LOC
Park	I-LOC
!	O
A	O
big	O

The	O
group	O
spent	O
the	O
day	O
collecting	O
a	O
total	O
of	O
60	B-WEI
pounds	B-UNT
of	O
trash	B-ITM
,	O
making	O
a	O
big	O
step	O
towards	O
preserving	O
this	O
special	O
place	O
.	O

#	O
FLRcleanup	O
#	O
savetheocean	O
#	O

#	O
BeachCleanup	O
#	O
Whitsunday	B-LOC
#	O
TheWishProjectInc	B-ORG
#	O

